{"text":"7:00:13 PM [info] Activating VS Code Recorder\n","file":"extension-output-MattiaConsiglio.vs-code-recorder-#1-VS Code Recorder","language":"Log"}
{"text":"7:00:13 PM [info] Activating VS Code Recorder\n7:00:15 PM [info] Recording started\n","file":"extension-output-MattiaConsiglio.vs-code-recorder-#1-VS Code Recorder","language":"Log"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() \n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"lockfileVersion\": 2,\n  \"requires\": true,\n  \"packages\": {\n    \"\": {\n      \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"license\": \"ISC\",\n      \"devDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@ampproject/remapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@ampproject/remapping/-/remapping-2.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-30iZtAPgz+LTIYoeivqYo853f02jBYSd5uGnGpkFV0M3xOt9aN73erkgYAmZU43x4VfqcnLxW9Kpg3R5LC4YYw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": \"^0.3.5\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.24\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/code-frame\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/code-frame/-/code-frame-7.26.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RJlIHRueQgwWitWgF8OdFYGZX328Ax5BCemNGlqHfplnRT9ESi8JkFlvaVYbS+UubVY6dpv87Fs2u5M29iNFVQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"js-tokens\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"picocolors\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/compat-data\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/compat-data/-/compat-data-7.26.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-oH5UPLMWR3L2wEFLnFJ1TZXqHufiTKAiLfqw5zkhS4dKXLJ10yVztfil/twG8EDTA4F/tvVNw9nOl4ZMslB8rQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/core\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/core/-/core-7.26.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-vMqyb7XCDMPvJFFOaT9kxtiRh42GwlZEg1/uIgtZshS5a/8OaduUfCi7kynKgc3Tw/6Uo2D+db9qBttghhmxwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@ampproject/remapping\": \"^2.2.0\",\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/helper-compilation-targets\": \"^7.26.5\",\n        \"@babel/helper-module-transforms\": \"^7.26.0\",\n        \"@babel/helpers\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.26.9\",\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"debug\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"gensync\": \"^1.0.0-beta.2\",\n        \"json5\": \"^2.2.3\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": {\n        \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n        \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/babel\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/generator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/generator/-/generator-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-VybsKvpiN1gU1sdMZIp7FcqphVVKEwcuj02x73uvcHE0PTihx1nlBcowYWhDwjpoAXRv43+gDzyggGnn1XZhVw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": \"^0.3.5\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.25\",\n        \"jsesc\": \"^3.0.2\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-compilation-targets\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-compilation-targets/-/helper-compilation-targets-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LVk7fbXml0H2xH34dFzKQ7TDZ2G4/rVTOrq9V+icbbadjbVxxeFeDsNHv2SrZeWoA+6ZiTyWYWtScEIW07EAcA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/compat-data\": \"^7.26.8\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-option\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"browserslist\": \"^4.24.0\",\n        \"lru-cache\": \"^5.1.1\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-module-imports\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-module-imports/-/helper-module-imports-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tnUA4RsrmflIM6W6RFTLFSXITtl0wKjgpnLgXyowocVPrbYrLUXSBXDgTs8BlbmIzIdlBySRQjINYs2BAkiLtw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-module-transforms\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-module-transforms/-/helper-module-transforms-7.26.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xO+xu6B5K2czEnQye6BHA7DolFFmS3LB7stHZFaOLb1pAwO1HWLS8fXA+eh0A2yIvltPVmx3eNNDBJA2SLHXFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-module-imports\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-plugin-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-plugin-utils/-/helper-plugin-utils-7.26.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RS+jZcRdZdRFzMyr+wcsaqOmld1/EqTghfaBGQQd/WnRdzdlvSZ//kF7U8VQTxf1ynZ4cjUcYgjVGx13ewNPMg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-string-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-string-parser/-/helper-string-parser-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-4A/SCr/2KLd5jrtOMFzaKjVtAei3+2r/NChoBNoZ3EyP/+GlhoaEGoWOZUmFmoITP7zOJyHIMm+DYRd8o3PvHA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-validator-identifier/-/helper-validator-identifier-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Ed61U6XJc3CVRfkERJWDz4dJwKe7iLmmJsbOGu9wSloNSFttHV0I8g6UAgb7qnK5ly5bGLPd4oXZlxCdANBOWQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-validator-option\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-validator-option/-/helper-validator-option-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-e/zv1co8pp55dNdEcCynfj9X7nyUKUXoUEwfXqaZt0omVOmDe9oOTdKStH4GmAw6zxMFs50ZayuMfHDKlO7Tfw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helpers\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helpers/-/helpers-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-U5eyP/CTFPuNE3qk+WZMxFkp/4zUzdceQlfzf7DdGdhp+Fezd7HD+i8Y24ZuTMKX3wQBld449jijbGq6OdGNQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/parser/-/parser-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iaepho73/2Pz7w2eMS0Q5f83+0RKI7i4xmiYeBmDzfRVbQtTOG7Ts0S4HzJVsTMGI9keU8rNfuZr8DKfSt7Yyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators/-/plugin-syntax-async-generators-7.8.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tycmZxkGfZaxhMRbXlPXuVFpdWlXpir2W4AMhSJgRKzk/eDlIXOhb2LHWoLpDF7TEHylV5zNhykX6KAgHJmTNw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint/-/plugin-syntax-bigint-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wnTnFlG+YxQm3vDxpGE57Pj0srRU4sHE/mDkt1qv2YJJSeUAec2ma4WLUnUPeKjyrfntVwe/N6dCXpU+zL3Npg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.12.13\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties/-/plugin-syntax-class-properties-7.12.13.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fm4idjKla0YahUNgFNLCB0qySdsoPiZP3iQE3rky0mBUtMZ23yDJ9SJdg6dXTSDnulOVqiF3Hgr9nbXvXTQZYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block/-/plugin-syntax-class-static-block-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-b+YyPmr6ldyNnM6sqYeMWE+bgJcJpO6yS4QD7ymxgH34GBPNDM/THBh8iunyvKIZztiwLH4CJZ0RxTk9emgpjw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes/-/plugin-syntax-import-attributes-7.26.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-e2dttdsJ1ZTpi3B9UYGLw41hifAubg19AtCu/2I/F1QNVclOBr1dYpTdmdyZ84Xiz43BS/tCUkMAZNLv12Pi+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta/-/plugin-syntax-import-meta-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Yqfm+XDx0+Prh3VSeEQCPU81yC+JWZ2pDPFSS4ZdpfZhp4MkFMaDC1UqseovEKwSUpnIL7+vK+Clp7bfh0iD7g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings/-/plugin-syntax-json-strings-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lY6kdGpWHvjoe2vk4WrAapEuBR69EMxZl+RoGRhrFGNYVK8mOPAW8VfbT/ZgrFbXlDNiiaxQnAtgVCZ6jv30EA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx/-/plugin-syntax-jsx-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ld6oezHQMZsZfp6pWtbjaNDF2tiiCYYDqQszHt5VV437lewP9aSi2Of99CK0D0XB21k7FLgnLcmQKyKzynfeAA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators/-/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-d8waShlpFDinQ5MtvGU9xDAOzKH47+FFoney2baFIoMr952hKOLp1HR7VszoZvOsV/4+RRszNY7D17ba0te0ig==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator/-/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-aSff4zPII1u2QD7y+F8oDsz19ew4IGEJg9SVW+bqwpwtfFleiQDMdzA/R+UlWDzfnHFCxxleFT0PMIrR36XLNQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator/-/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9H6YdfkcK/uOnY/K7/aA2xpzaAgkQn37yzWUMRK7OaPOqOpGS1+n0H5hxT9AUw9EsSjPW8SVyMJwYRtWs3X3ug==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread/-/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XoqMijGZb9y3y2XskN+P1wUGiVwWZ5JmoDRwx5+3GmEplNyVM2s2Dg8ILFQm8rWM48orGy5YpI5Bl8U1y7ydlA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding/-/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6VPD0Pc1lpTqw0aKoeRTMiB+kWhAoT24PA+ksWSBrFtl5SIRVpZlwN3NNPQjehA2E/91FV3RjLWoVTglWcSV3Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining/-/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KoK9ErH1MBlCPxV0VANkXW2/dw4vlbGDrFgz8bmUsBGYkFRcbRwMh6cIJubdPrkxRwuGdtCk0v/wPTKbQgBjkg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object/-/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0wVnp9dxJ72ZUJDV27ZfbSj6iHLoytYZmh3rFcxNnvsJF3ktkzLDZPy/mA17HGsaQT3/DQsWYX1f1QGWkCoVUg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await/-/plugin-syntax-top-level-await-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hx++upLv5U1rgYfwe1xBQUhRmU41NEvpUvrp8jkrSCdvGSnM5/qdRMtylJ6PG5OFkBaHkbTAKTnd3/YyESRHFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript/-/plugin-syntax-typescript-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hjMgRy5hb8uJJjUcdWunWVcoi9bGpJp8p5Ol1229PoN6aytsLwNMgmdftO23wnCLMfVmTwZDWMPNq/D1SY60JQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/template\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/template/-/template-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2ncevenBqXI6qRMukPlXwHKHchC7RyMuu4xv5JBXRfOGVcTy1mXCD12qrp7Jsoxll1EV3+9sE4GugBVRjT2jFA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/traverse\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/traverse/-/traverse-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-19lYZFzYVQkkHkl4Cy4WrAVcqBkgvV2YM2TU3xG6DIwO7O3ecbDPfW3yM3bjAGcqcQHi+CCtjMR3dIEHxsd6bA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"debug\": \"^4.3.1\",\n        \"globals\": \"^11.1.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/types\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/types/-/types-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-H45s8fVLYjbhFH62dIJ3WtmJ6RSPt/3DRO0ZcT2SUiYiQyz3BLVb9ADEnLl91m74aQPS3AzzeajZHYOalWe3bg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-string-parser\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@bcoe/v8-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@bcoe/v8-coverage/-/v8-coverage-0.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0hYQ8SB4Db5zvZB4axdMHGwEaQjkZzFjQiN9LVYvIFB2nSUHW9tYpxWriPrWDASIxiaXax83REcLxuSdnGPZtw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config/-/load-nyc-config-1.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-VjeHSlIzpv/NyD3N0YuHfXOPDIixcA1q2ZV98wsMqcYlPmv2n3Yb2lYP9XMElnaFVXg5A7YLTeLu6V84uQDjmQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"camelcase\": \"^5.3.1\",\n        \"find-up\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"get-package-type\": \"^0.1.0\",\n        \"js-yaml\": \"^3.13.1\",\n        \"resolve-from\": \"^5.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@istanbuljs/schema\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@istanbuljs/schema/-/schema-0.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ZXRY4jNvVgSVQ8DL3LTcakaAtXwTVUxE81hslsyD2AtoXW/wVob10HkOJ1X/pAlcI7D+2YoZKg5do8G/w6RYgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/console\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/console/-/console-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-5Ni4CU7XHQi32IJ398EEP4RrB8eV09sXP2ROqD4bksHrnTree52PsxvX8tpL8LvTZ3pFzXyPbNQReSN41CAhOg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/core\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/core/-/core-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-n7aeXWKMnGtDA48y8TLWJPJmLmmZ642Ceo78cYWEpiD7FzDgmNDV/GCVRorPABdXLJZ/9wzzgZAlHjXjxDHGsg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/reporters\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"ansi-escapes\": \"^4.2.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-changed-files\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-resolve-dependencies\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runner\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-watcher\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/environment\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/environment/-/environment-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-aQIfHDq33ExsN4jP1NWGXhxgQ/wixs60gDiKO+XVMd8Mn0NWPWgc34ZQDTb2jKaUWQ7MuwoitXAsN2XVXNMpAw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/expect\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/expect/-/expect-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-8uMeAMycttpva3P1lBHB8VciS9V0XAr3GymPpipdyQXbBcuhkLQOSe8E/p92RyAdToS6ZD1tFkX+CkhoECE0dQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/expect-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/expect-utils/-/expect-utils-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GlsNBWiFQFCVi9QVSx7f5AgMeLxe9YCCs5PuP2O2LdjDAA8Jh9eX7lA1Jq/xdXw3Wb3hyvlFNfZIfcRetSzYcA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/fake-timers\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/fake-timers/-/fake-timers-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-q4DH1Ha4TTFPdxLsqDXK1d3+ioSL7yL5oCMJZgDYm6i+6CygW5E5xVr/D1HdsGxjt1ZWSfUAs9OxSB/BNelWrQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@sinonjs/fake-timers\": \"^10.0.2\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/globals\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/globals/-/globals-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-mpiz3dutLbkW2MNFubUGUEVLkTGiqW6yLVTA+JbP6fI6J5iL9Y0Nlg8k95pcF8ctKwCS7WVxteBs29hhfAotzQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/reporters\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/reporters/-/reporters-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DApq0KJbJOEzAFYjHADNNxAE3KbhxQB1y5Kplb5Waqw6zVbuWatSnMjE5gs8FUgEPmNsnZA3NCWl9NG0ia04Pg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@bcoe/v8-coverage\": \"^0.2.3\",\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-report\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-source-maps\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-reports\": \"^3.1.3\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"string-length\": \"^4.0.1\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"v8-to-istanbul\": \"^9.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/schemas\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/schemas/-/schemas-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-mo5j5X+jIZmJQveBKeS/clAueipV7KgiX1vMgCxam1RNYiqE1w62n0/tJJnHtjW8ZHcQco5gY85jA3mi0L+nSA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/source-map/-/source-map-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MHjT95QuipcPrpLM+8JMSzFx6eHp5Bm+4XeFDJlwsvVBjmKNiIAvasGK2fxz2WbGRlnvqehFbh07MMa7n3YJnw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"callsites\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/test-result\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/test-result/-/test-result-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Fdx+tv6x1zlkJPcWXmMDAG2HBnaR9XPSd5aDWQVsfrZmLVT3lU1cwyxLgRmXR9yrq4NBoEm9BMsfgFzTQAbJYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/test-sequencer\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/test-sequencer/-/test-sequencer-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GQwJ5WZVrKnOJuiYiAF52UNUJXgTZx1NHjFSEB0qEMmSZKAkdMoIzw/Cj6x6NF4AvV23AUqDpFzQkN/eYCYTxw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/transform\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/transform/-/transform-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ok/BTPFzFKVMwO5eOHRrvnBVHdRy9IrsrW1GpMaQ9MCnilNLXQKmAX8s1YXDFaai9xJpac2ySzV0YeRRECr2Vw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": \"^6.1.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"fast-json-stable-stringify\": \"^2.1.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pirates\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"write-file-atomic\": \"^4.0.2\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/types\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/types/-/types-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-u3UPsIilWKOM3F9CXtrG8LEJmNxwoCQC/XVj4IKYXvvpx7QIi/Kg1LI5uDmDpKlac62NUtX7eLjRh+jVZcLOzw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/schemas\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-reports\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/yargs\": \"^17.0.8\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.3.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/gen-mapping/-/gen-mapping-0.3.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-imAbBGkb+ebQyxKgzv5Hu2nmROxoDOXHh80evxdoXNOrvAnVx7zimzc1Oo5h9RlfV4vPXaE2iM5pOFbvOCClWA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/set-array\": \"^1.2.1\",\n        \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": \"^1.4.10\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.24\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/resolve-uri\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/resolve-uri/-/resolve-uri-3.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bRISgCIjP20/tbWSPWMEi54QVPRZExkuD9lJL+UIxUKtwVJA8wW1Trb1jMs1RFXo1CBTNZ/5hpC9QvmKWdopKw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/set-array\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/set-array/-/set-array-1.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R8gLRTZeyp03ymzP/6Lil/28tGeGEzhx1q2k703KGWRAI1VdvPIXdG70VJc2pAMw3NA6JKL5hhFu1sJX0Mnn/A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec/-/sourcemap-codec-1.5.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gv3ZRaISU3fjPAgNsriBRqGWQL6quFx04YMPW/zD8XMLsU32mhCCbfbO6KZFLjvYpCZ8zyDEgqsgf+PwPaM7GQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.3.25\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/trace-mapping/-/trace-mapping-0.3.25.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-vNk6aEwybGtawWmy/PzwnGDOjCkLWSD2wqvjGGAgOAwCGWySYXfYoxt00IJkTF+8Lb57DwOb3Aa0o9CApepiYQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/resolve-uri\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": \"^1.4.14\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@sinclair/typebox\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.27.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinclair/typebox/-/typebox-0.27.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+Fj43pSMwJs4KRrH/938Uf+uAELIgVBmQzg/q1YG10djyfA3TnrU8N8XzqCh/okZdszqBQTZf96idMfE5lnwTA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@sinonjs/commons\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinonjs/commons/-/commons-3.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-K3mCHKQ9sVh8o1C9cxkwxaOmXoAMlDxC1mYyHrjqOWEcBjYr76t96zL2zlj5dUGZ3HSw240X1qgH3Mjf1yJWpQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@sinonjs/fake-timers\": {\n      \"version\": \"10.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinonjs/fake-timers/-/fake-timers-10.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-V4BG07kuYSUkTCSBHG8G8TNhM+F19jXFWnQtzj+we8DrkpSBCee9Z3Ms8yiGer/dlmhe35/Xdgyo3/0rQKg7YA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/babel__core\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.20.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__core/-/babel__core-7.20.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qoQprZvz5wQFJwMDqeseRXWv3rqMvhgpbXFfVyWhbx9X47POIA6i/+dXefEmZKoAgOaTdaIgNSMqMIU61yRyzA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.20.7\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.20.7\",\n        \"@types/babel__generator\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/babel__template\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/babel__traverse\": \"*\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/babel__generator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__generator/-/babel__generator-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ufFd2Xi92OAVPYsy+P4n7/U7e68fex0+Ee8gSG9KX7eo084CWiQ4sdxktvdl0bOPupXtVJPY19zk6EwWqUQ8lg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/babel__template\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.4.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__template/-/babel__template-7.4.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-h/NUaSyG5EyxBIp8YRxo4RMe2/qQgvyowRwVMzhYhBCONbW8PUsg4lkFMrhgZhUe5z3L3MiLDuvyJ/CaPa2A8A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.1.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/babel__traverse\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.20.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__traverse/-/babel__traverse-7.20.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-dkO5fhS7+/oos4ciWxyEyjWe48zmG6wbCheo/G2ZnHx4fs3EU6YC6UM8rk56gAjNJ9P3MTH2jo5jb92/K6wbng==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/graceful-fs\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/graceful-fs/-/graceful-fs-4.1.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-olP3sd1qOEe5dXTSaFvQG+02VdRXcdytWLAZsAq1PecU8uqQAhkrnbli7DagjtXKW/Bl7YJbUsa8MPcuc8LHEQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-lib-coverage/-/istanbul-lib-coverage-2.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2QF/t/auWm0lsy8XtKVPG19v3sSOQlJe/YHZgfjb/KBBHOGSV+J2q/S671rcq9uTBrLAXmZpqJiaQbMT+zNU1w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/istanbul-lib-report\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-lib-report/-/istanbul-lib-report-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NQn7AHQnk/RSLOxrBbGyJM/aVQ+pjj5HCgasFxc0K/KhoATfQ/47AyUl15I2yBUpihjmas+a+VJBOqecrFH+uA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/istanbul-reports\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-reports/-/istanbul-reports-3.0.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pk2B1NWalF9toCRu6gjBzR69syFjP4Od8WRAX+0mmf9lAjCRicLOWc+ZrxZHx/0XRjotgkF9t6iaMJ+aXcOdZQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/node\": {\n      \"version\": \"22.14.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/node/-/node-22.14.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-u0HuPQwe/dHrItgHHpmw3N2fYCR6x4ivMNbPHRkBVP4CvN+kiRrKHWk3i8tXiO/joPwXLMYvF9TTF0eqgHIuOw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/stack-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/stack-utils/-/stack-utils-2.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9aEbYZ3TbYMznPdcdr3SmIrLXwC/AKZXQeCf9Pgao5CKb8CyHuEX5jzWPTkvregvhRJHcpRO6BFoGW9ycaOkYw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/yargs\": {\n      \"version\": \"17.0.33\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/yargs/-/yargs-17.0.33.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WpxBCKWPLr4xSsHgz511rFJAM+wS28w2zEO1QDNY5zM/S8ok70NNfztH0xwhqKyaK0OHCbN98LDAZuy1ctxDkA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/yargs-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"21.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/yargs-parser/-/yargs-parser-21.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-I4q9QU9MQv4oEOz4tAHJtNz1cwuLxn2F3xcc2iV5WdqLPpUnj30aUuxt1mAxYTG+oe8CZMV/+6rU4S4gRDzqtQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/ansi-escapes\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-escapes/-/ansi-escapes-4.3.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gKXj5ALrKWQLsYG9jlTRmR/xKluxHV+Z9QEwNIgCfM1/uwPMCuzVVnh5mwTd+OuBZcwSIMbqssNWRm1lE51QaQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/ansi-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-regex/-/ansi-regex-5.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-quJQXlTSUGL2LH9SUXo8VwsY4soanhgo6LNSm84E1LBcE8s3O0wpdiRzyR9z/ZZJMlMWv37qOOb9pdJlMUEKFQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/ansi-styles\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-styles/-/ansi-styles-4.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zbB9rCJAT1rbjiVDb2hqKFHNYLxgtk8NURxZ3IZwD3F6NtxbXZQCnnSi1Lkx+IDohdPlFp222wVALIheZJQSEg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/anymatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/anymatch/-/anymatch-3.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KMReFUr0B4t+D+OBkjR3KYqvocp2XaSzO55UcB6mgQMd3KbcE+mWTyvVV7D/zsdEbNnV6acZUutkiHQXvTr1Rw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"normalize-path\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"picomatch\": \"^2.0.4\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/argparse\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/argparse/-/argparse-1.0.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-o5Roy6tNG4SL/FOkCAN6RzjiakZS25RLYFrcMttJqbdd8BWrnA+fGz57iN5Pb06pvBGvl5gQ0B48dJlslXvoTg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-jest/-/babel-jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BrvGY3xZSwEcCzKvKsCi2GgHqDqsYkOP4/by5xCgIwGXQxIEh+8ew3gmrE1y7XRR6LHZIj6yLYnUi/mm2KXKBg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@types/babel__core\": \"^7.1.14\",\n        \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": \"^6.1.1\",\n        \"babel-preset-jest\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-plugin-istanbul\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-plugin-istanbul/-/babel-plugin-istanbul-6.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Y1IQok9821cC9onCx5otgFfRm7Lm+I+wwxOx738M/WLPZ9Q42m4IG5W0FNX8WLL2gYMZo3JkuXIH2DOpWM+qwA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-plugin-utils\": \"^7.0.0\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": \"^5.0.4\",\n        \"test-exclude\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-plugin-istanbul/node_modules/istanbul-lib-instrument\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-instrument/-/istanbul-lib-instrument-5.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pzqtp31nLv/XFOzXGuvhCb8qhjmTVo5vjVk19XE4CRlSWz0KoeJ3bw9XsA7nOp9YBf4qHjwBxkDzKcME/J29Yg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.12.3\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.14.7\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-plugin-jest-hoist\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-plugin-jest-hoist/-/babel-plugin-jest-hoist-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ESAc/RJvGTFEzRwOTT4+lNDk/GNHMkKbNzsvT0qKRfDyyYTskxB5rnU2njIDYVxXCBHHEI1c0YwHob3WaYujOg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@types/babel__core\": \"^7.1.14\",\n        \"@types/babel__traverse\": \"^7.0.6\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-preset-current-node-syntax/-/babel-preset-current-node-syntax-1.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ldYss8SbBlWva1bs28q78Ju5Zq1F+8BrqBZZ0VFhLBvhh6lCpC2o3gDJi/5DRLs9FgYZCnmPYIVFU4lRXCkyUw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators\": \"^7.8.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties\": \"^7.12.13\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block\": \"^7.14.5\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes\": \"^7.24.7\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object\": \"^7.14.5\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await\": \"^7.14.5\"\n      },\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-preset-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-preset-jest/-/babel-preset-jest-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0B3bhxR6snWXJZtR/RliHTDPRgn1sNHOR0yVtq/IiQFyuOVjFS+wuio/R4gSNkyYmKmJB4wGZv2NZanmKmTnNA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"babel-plugin-jest-hoist\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/balanced-match\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/balanced-match/-/balanced-match-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3oSeUO0TMV67hN1AmbXsK4yaqU7tjiHlbxRDZOpH0KW9+CeX4bRAaX0Anxt0tx2MrpRpWwQaPwIlISEJhYU5Pw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/brace-expansion\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.11\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/brace-expansion/-/brace-expansion-1.1.11.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iCuPHDFgrHX7H2vEI/5xpz07zSHB00TpugqhmYtVmMO6518mCuRMoOYFldEBl0g187ufozdaHgWKcYFb61qGiA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"balanced-match\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"concat-map\": \"0.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/braces\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/braces/-/braces-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-yQbXgO/OSZVD2IsiLlro+7Hf6Q18EJrKSEsdoMzKePKXct3gvD8oLcOQdIzGupr5Fj+EDe8gO/lxc1BzfMpxvA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/browserslist\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.24.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/browserslist/-/browserslist-4.24.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KDi1Ny1gSePi1vm0q4oxSF8b4DR44GF4BbmS2YdhPLOEqd8pDviZOGH/GsmRwoWJ2+5Lr085X7naowMwKHDG1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n          \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"tidelift\",\n          \"url\": \"https://tidelift.com/funding/github/npm/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"github\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/ai\"\n        }\n      ],\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"caniuse-lite\": \"^1.0.30001688\",\n        \"electron-to-chromium\": \"^1.5.73\",\n        \"node-releases\": \"^2.0.19\",\n        \"update-browserslist-db\": \"^1.1.1\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": {\n        \"node\": \"^6 || ^7 || ^8 || ^9 || ^10 || ^11 || ^12 || >=13.7\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/bser\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/bser/-/bser-2.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gQxTNE/GAfIIrmHLUE3oJyp5FO6HRBfhjnw4/wMmA63ZGDJnWBmgY/lyQBpnDUkGmAhbSe39tx2d/iTOAfglwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/buffer-from\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/buffer-from/-/buffer-from-1.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-E+XQCRwSbaaiChtv6k6Dwgc+bx+Bs6vuKJHHl5kox/BaKbhiXzqQOwK4cO22yElGp2OCmjwVhT3HmxgyPGnJfQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/callsites\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/callsites/-/callsites-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-P8BjAsXvZS+VIDUI11hHCQEv74YT67YUi5JJFNWIqL235sBmjX4+qx9Muvls5ivyNENctx46xQLQ3aTuE7ssaQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/camelcase\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/camelcase/-/camelcase-5.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-L28STB170nwWS63UjtlEOE3dldQApaJXZkOI1uMFfzf3rRuPegHaHesyee+YxQ+W6SvRDQV6UrdOdRiR153wJg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/caniuse-lite\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.30001715\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/caniuse-lite/-/caniuse-lite-1.0.30001715.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7ptkFGMm2OAOgvZpwgA4yjQ5SQbrNVGdRjzH0pBdy1Fasvcr+KAeECmbCAECzTuDuoX0FCY8KzUxjf9+9kfZEw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n          \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"tidelift\",\n          \"url\": \"https://tidelift.com/funding/github/npm/caniuse-lite\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"github\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/ai\"\n        }\n      ]\n    },\n    \"node_modules/chalk\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/chalk/-/chalk-4.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-oKnbhFyRIXpUuez8iBMmyEa4nbj4IOQyuhc/wy9kY7/WVPcwIO9VA668Pu8RkO7+0G76SLROeyw9CpQ061i4mA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^7.1.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/char-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/char-regex/-/char-regex-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kWWXztvZ5SBQV+eRgKFeh8q5sLuZY2+8WUIzlxWVTg+oGwY14qylx1KbKzHd8P6ZYkAg0xyIDU9JMHhyJMZ1jw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/ci-info\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.9.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ci-info/-/ci-info-3.9.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NIxF55hv4nSqQswkAeiOi1r83xy8JldOFDTWiug55KBu9Jnblncd2U6ViHmYgHf01TPZS77NJBhBMKdWj9HQMQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"github\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/sibiraj-s\"\n        }\n      ],\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/cjs-module-lexer\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cjs-module-lexer/-/cjs-module-lexer-1.4.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9z8TZaGM1pfswYeXrUpzPrkx8UnWYdhJclsiYMm6x/w5+nN+8Tf/LnAgfLGQCm59qAOxU8WwHEq2vNwF6i4j+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/cliui\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cliui/-/cliui-8.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BSeNnyus75C4//NQ9gQt1/csTXyo/8Sb+afLAkzAptFuMsod9HFokGNudZpi/oQV73hnVK+sR+5PVRMd+Dr7YQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.2.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.1\",\n        \"wrap-ansi\": \"^7.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/co\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.6.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/co/-/co-4.6.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-QVb0dM5HvG+uaxitm8wONl7jltx8dqhfU33DcqtOZcLSVIKSDDLDi7+0LbAKiyI8hD9u42m2YxXSkMGWThaecQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/collect-v8-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/collect-v8-coverage/-/collect-v8-coverage-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lHl4d5/ONEbLlJvaJNtsF/Lz+WvB07u2ycqTYbdrq7UypDXailES4valYb2eWiJFxZlVmpGekfqoxQhzyFdT4Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/color-convert\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/color-convert/-/color-convert-2.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RRECPsj7iu/xb5oKYcsFHSppFNnsj/52OVTRKb4zP5onXwVF3zVmmToNcOfGC+CRDpfK/U584fMg38ZHCaElKQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/color-name\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/color-name/-/color-name-1.1.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-dOy+3AuW3a2wNbZHIuMZpTcgjGuLU/uBL/ubcZF9OXbDo8ff4O8yVp5Bf0efS8uEoYo5q4Fx7dY9OgQGXgAsQA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/concat-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/concat-map/-/concat-map-0.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/Srv4dswyQNBfohGpz9o6Yb3Gz3SrUDqBH5rTuhGR7ahtlbYKnVxw2bCFMRljaA7EXHaXZ8wsHdodFvbkhKmqg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/convert-source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/convert-source-map/-/convert-source-map-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Kvp459HrV2FEJ1CAsi1Ku+MY3kasH19TFykTz2xWmMeq6bk2NU3XXvfJ+Q61m0xktWwt+1HSYf3JZsTms3aRJg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/create-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/create-jest/-/create-jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Adz2bdH0Vq3F53KEMJOoftQFutWCukm6J24wbPWRO4k1kMY7gS7ds/uoJkNuV8wDCtWWnuwGcJwpWcih+zEW1Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"prompts\": \"^2.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/cross-spawn\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cross-spawn/-/cross-spawn-7.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-uV2QOWP2nWzsy2aMp8aRibhi9dlzF5Hgh5SHaB9OiTGEyDTiJJyx0uy51QXdyWbtAHNua4XJzUKca3OzKUd3vA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"path-key\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"shebang-command\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"which\": \"^2.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/debug\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/debug/-/debug-4.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6WTZ/IxCY/T6BALoZHaE4ctp9xm+Z5kY/pzYaCHRFeyVhojxlrm+46y68HA6hr0TcwEssoxNiDEUJQjfPZ/RYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/dedent\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/dedent/-/dedent-1.5.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NHQtfOOW68WD8lgypbLA5oT+Bt0xXJhiYvoR6SmmNXZfpzOGXwdKWmcwG8N7PwVVWV3eF/68nmD9BaJSsTBhyQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/deepmerge\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/deepmerge/-/deepmerge-4.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3sUqbMEc77XqpdNO7FRyRog+eW3ph+GYCbj+rK+uYyRMuwsVy0rMiVtPn+QJlKFvWP/1PYpapqYn0Me2knFn+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/detect-newline\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/detect-newline/-/detect-newline-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TLz+x/vEXm/Y7P7wn1EJFNLxYpUD4TgMosxY6fAVJUnJMbupHBOncxyWUG9OpTaH9EBD7uFI5LfEgmMOc54DsA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/diff-sequences\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/diff-sequences/-/diff-sequences-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-EjePK1srD3P08o2j4f0ExnylqRs5B9tJjcp9t1krH2qRi8CCdsYfwe9JgSLurFBWwq4uOlipzfk5fHNvwFKr8Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/electron-to-chromium\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.140\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/electron-to-chromium/-/electron-to-chromium-1.5.140.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-o82Rj+ONp4Ip7Cl1r7lrqx/pXhbp/lh9DpKcMNscFJdh8ebyRofnc7Sh01B4jx403RI0oqTBvlZ7OBIZLMr2+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/emittery\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.13.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/emittery/-/emittery-0.13.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DeWwawk6r5yR9jFgnDKYt4sLS0LmHJJi3ZOnb5/JdbYwj3nW+FxQnHIjhBKz8YLC7oRNPVM9NQ47I3CVx34eqQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": {\n        \"url\": \"https://github.com/sindresorhus/emittery?sponsor=1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/emoji-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/emoji-regex/-/emoji-regex-8.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MSjYzcWNOA0ewAHpz0MxpYFvwg6yjy1NG3xteoqz644VCo/RPgnr1/GGt+ic3iJTzQ8Eu3TdM14SawnVUmGE6A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/error-ex\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.3.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/error-ex/-/error-ex-1.3.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7dFHNmqeFSEt2ZBsCriorKnn3Z2pj+fd9kmI6QoWw4//DL+icEBfc0U7qJCisqrTsKTjw4fNFy2pW9OqStD84g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/escalade\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/escalade/-/escalade-3.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WUj2qlxaQtO4g6Pq5c29GTcWGDyd8itL8zTlipgECz3JesAiiOKotd8JU6otB3PACgG6xkJUyVhboMS+bje/jA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/escape-string-regexp\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/escape-string-regexp/-/escape-string-regexp-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UpzcLCXolUWcNu5HtVMHYdXJjArjsF9C0aNnquZYY4uW/Vu0miy5YoWvbV345HauVvcAUnpRuhMMcqTcGOY2+w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/esprima\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/esprima/-/esprima-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eGuFFw7Upda+g4p+QHvnW0RyTX/SVeJBDM/gCtMARO0cLuT2HcEKnTPvhjV6aGeqrCB/sbNop0Kszm0jsaWU4A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": {\n        \"esparse\": \"bin/esparse.js\",\n        \"esvalidate\": \"bin/esvalidate.js\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/execa\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/execa/-/execa-5.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-8uSpZZocAZRBAPIEINJj3Lo9HyGitllczc27Eh5YYojjMFMn8yHMDMaUHE2Jqfq05D/wucwI4JGURyXt1vchyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"cross-spawn\": \"^7.0.3\",\n        \"get-stream\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"human-signals\": \"^2.1.0\",\n        \"is-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"merge-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"npm-run-path\": \"^4.0.1\",\n        \"onetime\": \"^5.1.2\",\n        \"signal-exit\": \"^3.0.3\",\n        \"strip-final-newline\": \"^2.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/exit\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/exit/-/exit-0.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Zk/eNKV2zbjpKzrsQ+n1G6poVbErQxJ0LBOJXaKZ1EViLzH+hrLu9cdXI4zw9dBQJslwBEpbQ2P1oS7nDxs6jQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/expect\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/expect/-/expect-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2Zks0hf1VLFYI1kbh0I5jP3KHHyCHpkfyHBzsSXRFgl/Bg9mWYfMW8oD+PdMPlEwy5HNsR9JutYy6pMeOh61nw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/expect-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/fast-json-stable-stringify\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fast-json-stable-stringify/-/fast-json-stable-stringify-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lhd/wF+Lk98HZoTCtlVraHtfh5XYijIjalXck7saUtuanSDyLMxnHhSXEDJqHxD7msR8D0uCmqlkwjCV8xvwHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/fb-watchman\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fb-watchman/-/fb-watchman-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-p5161BqbuCaSnB8jIbzQHOlpgsPmK5rJVDfDKO91Axs5NC1uu3HRQm6wt9cd9/+GtQQIO53JdGXXoyDpTAsgYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/fill-range\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fill-range/-/fill-range-7.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-YsGpe3WHLK8ZYi4tWDg2Jy3ebRz2rXowDxnld4bkQB00cc/1Zw9AWnC0i9ztDJitivtQvaI9KaLyKrc+hBW0yg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/find-up\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/find-up/-/find-up-4.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-PpOwAdQ/YlXQ2vj8a3h8IipDuYRi3wceVQQGYWxNINccq40Anw7BlsEXCMbt1Zt+OLA6Fq9suIpIWD0OsnISlw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"locate-path\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"path-exists\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/fs.realpath\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fs.realpath/-/fs.realpath-1.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OO0pH2lK6a0hZnAdau5ItzHPI6pUlvI7jMVnxUQRtw4owF2wk8lOSabtGDCTP4Ggrg2MbGnWO9X8K1t4+fGMDw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/fsevents\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fsevents/-/fsevents-2.3.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-5xoDfX+fL7faATnagmWPpbFtwh/R77WmMMqqHGS65C3vvB0YHrgF+B1YmZ3441tMj5n63k0212XNoJwzlhffQw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"hasInstallScript\": true,\n      \"optional\": true,\n      \"os\": [\n        \"darwin\"\n      ],\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/function-bind\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/function-bind/-/function-bind-1.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7XHNxH7qX9xG5mIwxkhumTox/MIRNcOgDrxWsMt2pAr23WHp6MrRlN7FBSFpCpr+oVO0F744iUgR82nJMfG2SA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/gensync\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0-beta.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/gensync/-/gensync-1.0.0-beta.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3hN7NaskYvMDLQY55gnW3NQ+mesEAepTqlg+VEbj7zzqEMBVNhzcGYYeqFo/TlYz6eQiFcp1HcsCZO+nGgS8zg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/get-caller-file\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-caller-file/-/get-caller-file-2.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DyFP3BM/3YHTQOCUL/w0OZHR0lpKeGrxotcHWcqNEdnltqFwXVfhEBQ94eIo34AfQpo0rGki4cyIiftY06h2Fg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/get-package-type\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-package-type/-/get-package-type-0.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pjzuKtY64GYfWizNAJ0fr9VqttZkNiK2iS430LtIHzjBEr6bX8Am2zm4sW4Ro5wjWW5cAlRL1qAMTcXbjNAO2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/get-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-stream/-/get-stream-6.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ts6Wi+2j3jQjqi70w5AlN8DFnkSwC+MqmxEzdEALB2qXZYV3X/b1CTfgPLGJNMeAWxdPfU8FO1ms3NUfaHCPYg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/glob\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/glob/-/glob-7.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-nFR0zLpU2YCaRxwoCJvL6UvCH2JFyFVIvwTLsIf21AuHlMskA1hhTdk+LlYJtOlYt9v6dvszD2BGRqBL+iQK9Q==\",\n      \"deprecated\": \"Glob versions prior to v9 are no longer supported\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"fs.realpath\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"inflight\": \"^1.0.4\",\n        \"inherits\": \"2\",\n        \"minimatch\": \"^3.1.1\",\n        \"once\": \"^1.3.0\",\n        \"path-is-absolute\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/globals\": {\n      \"version\": \"11.12.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/globals/-/globals-11.12.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WOBp/EEGUiIsJSp7wcv/y6MO+lV9UoncWqxuFfm8eBwzWNgyfBd6Gz+IeKQ9jCmyhoH99g15M3T+QaVHFjizVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/graceful-fs\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.11\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/graceful-fs/-/graceful-fs-4.2.11.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RbJ5/jmFcNNCcDV5o9eTnBLJ/HszWV0P73bc+Ff4nS/rJj+YaS6IGyiOL0VoBYX+l1Wrl3k63h/KrH+nhJ0XvQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/has-flag\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/has-flag/-/has-flag-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-EykJT/Q1KjTWctppgIAgfSO0tKVuZUjhgMr17kqTumMl6Afv3EISleU7qZUzoXDFTAHTDC4NOoG/ZxU3EvlMPQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/hasown\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/hasown/-/hasown-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0hJU9SCPvmMzIBdZFqNPXWa6dqh7WdH0cII9y+CyS8rG3nL48Bclra9HmKhVVUHyPWNH5Y7xDwAB7bfgSjkUMQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/html-escaper\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/html-escaper/-/html-escaper-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-H2iMtd0I4Mt5eYiapRdIDjp+XzelXQ0tFE4JS7YFwFevXXMmOp9myNrUvCg0D6ws8iqkRPBfKHgbwig1SmlLfg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/human-signals\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/human-signals/-/human-signals-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-B4FFZ6q/T2jhhksgkbEW3HBvWIfDW85snkQgawt07S7J5QXTk6BkNV+0yAeZrM5QpMAdYlocGoljn0sJ/WQkFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/import-local\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/import-local/-/import-local-3.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2SPlun1JUPWoM6t3F0dw0FkCF/jWY8kttcY4f599GLTSjh2OCuuhdTkJQsEcZzBqbXZGKMK2OqW1oZsjtf/gQA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/imurmurhash\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/imurmurhash/-/imurmurhash-0.1.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JmXMZ6wuvDmLiHEml9ykzqO6lwFbof0GG4IkcGaENdCRDDmMVnny7s5HsIgHCbaq0w2MyPhDqkhTUgS2LU2PHA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/inflight\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/inflight/-/inflight-1.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-k92I/b08q4wvFscXCLvqfsHCrjrF7yiXsQuIVvVE7N82W3+aqpzuUdBbfhWcy/FZR3/4IgflMgKLOsvPDrGCJA==\",\n      \"deprecated\": \"This module is not supported, and leaks memory. Do not use it. Check out lru-cache if you want a good and tested way to coalesce async requests by a key value, which is much more comprehensive and powerful.\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/inherits\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/inherits/-/inherits-2.0.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-k/vGaX4/Yla3WzyMCvTQOXYeIHvqOKtnqBduzTHpzpQZzAskKMhZ2K+EnBiSM9zGSoIFeMpXKxa4dYeZIQqewQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-arrayish\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-arrayish/-/is-arrayish-0.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zz06S8t0ozoDXMG+ube26zeCTNXcKIPJZJi8hBrF4idCLms4CG9QtK7qBl1boi5ODzFpjswb5JPmHCbMpjaYzg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-core-module\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.16.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-core-module/-/is-core-module-2.16.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UfoeMA6fIJ8wTYFEUjelnaGI67v6+N7qXJEvQuIGa99l4xsCruSYOVSQ0uPANn4dAzm8lkYPaKLrrijLq7x23w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-fullwidth-code-point\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-fullwidth-code-point/-/is-fullwidth-code-point-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zymm5+u+sCsSWyD9qNaejV3DFvhCKclKdizYaJUuHA83RLjb7nSuGnddCHGv0hk+KY7BMAlsWeK4Ueg6EV6XQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-generator-fn\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-generator-fn/-/is-generator-fn-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-cTIB4yPYL/Grw0EaSzASzg6bBy9gqCofvWN8okThAYIxKJZC+udlRAmGbM0XLeniEJSs8uEgHPGuHSe1XsOLSQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-number\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-number/-/is-number-7.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-41Cifkg6e8TylSpdtTpeLVMqvSBEVzTttHvERD741+pnZ8ANv0004MRL43QKPDlK9cGvNp6NZWZUBlbGXYxxng==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-stream/-/is-stream-2.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hFoiJiTl63nn+kstHGBtewWSKnQLpyb155KHheA1l39uvtO9nWIop1p3udqPcUd/xbF1VLMO4n7OI6p7RbngDg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/isexe\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/isexe/-/isexe-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RHxMLp9lnKHGHRng9QFhRCMbYAcVpn69smSGcq3f36xjgVVWThj4qqLbTLlq7Ssj8B+fIQ1EuCEGI2lKsyQeIw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-coverage/-/istanbul-lib-coverage-3.2.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-O8dpsF+r0WV/8MNRKfnmrtCWhuKjxrq2w+jpzBL5UZKTi2LeVWnWOmWRxFlesJONmc+wLAGvKQZEOanko0LFTg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-instrument\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-instrument/-/istanbul-lib-instrument-6.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Vtgk7L/R2JHyyGW07spoFlB8/lpjiOLTjMdms6AFMraYt3BaJauod/NGrfnVG/y4Ix1JEuMRPDPEj2ua+zz1/Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.23.9\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.23.9\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.3\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^7.5.4\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-instrument/node_modules/semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-report\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-report/-/istanbul-lib-report-3.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GCfE1mtsHGOELCU8e/Z7YWzpmybrx/+dSTfLrvY8qRmaY6zXTKWn6WQIjaAFw069icm6GVMNkgu0NzI4iPZUNw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"make-dir\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^7.1.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-source-maps\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-source-maps/-/istanbul-lib-source-maps-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-n3s8EwkdFIJCG3BPKBYvskgXGoy88ARzvegkitk60NxRdwltLOTaH7CUiMRXvwYorl0Q712iEjcWB+fK/MrWVw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"debug\": \"^4.1.1\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"source-map\": \"^0.6.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-reports\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-reports/-/istanbul-reports-3.1.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BewmUXImeuRk2YY0PVbxgKAysvhRPUQE0h5QRM++nVWyubKGV0l8qQ5op8+B2DOmwSe63Jivj0BjkPQVf8fP5g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"html-escaper\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-report\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest/-/jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NIy3oAFp9shda19hy4HK0HRTWKtPJmGdnvywu01nOqNC2vZg+Z+fvJDxpMQA88eb2I9EcafcdjYgsDthnYTvGw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/core\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"import-local\": \"^3.0.2\",\n        \"jest-cli\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-changed-files\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-changed-files/-/jest-changed-files-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fEArFiwf1BpQ+4bXSprcDc3/x4HSzL4al2tozwVpDFpsxALjLYdyiIK4e5Vz66GQJIbXJ82+35PtysofptNX2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"execa\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-circus\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-circus/-/jest-circus-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3E1nCMgipcTkCocFwM90XXQab9bS+GMsjdpmPrlelaxwD93Ad8iVEjX/vvHPdLPnFf+L40u+5+iutRdA1N9myw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"co\": \"^4.6.0\",\n        \"dedent\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"is-generator-fn\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"jest-each\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"pure-rand\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"stack-utils\": \"^2.0.3\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-cli\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-cli/-/jest-cli-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OVVobw2IubN/GSYsxETi+gOe7Ka59EFMR/twOU3Jb2GnKKeMGJB5SGUUrEz3SFVmJASUdZUzy83sLNNQ2gZslg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/core\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"create-jest\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"import-local\": \"^3.0.2\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"yargs\": \"^17.3.1\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-config\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-config/-/jest-config-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-uXbpfeQ7R6TZBqI3/TxCU4q4ttk3u0PJeC+E0zbfSoSjq6bJ7buBPxzQPL0ifrkY4DNu4JUdk0ImlBUYi840eQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@jest/test-sequencer\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-jest\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"deepmerge\": \"^4.2.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-circus\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-environment-node\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runner\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"parse-json\": \"^5.2.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-json-comments\": \"^3.1.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": ,\n        \"ts-node\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-diff\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-diff/-/jest-diff-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LMIgiIrhigmPrs03JHpxUh2yISK3vLFPkAodPeo0+BuF7wA2FoQbkEg1u8gBYBThncu7e1oEDUfIXVuTqLRUjw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"diff-sequences\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-docblock\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-docblock/-/jest-docblock-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-q617Auw3A612guyaFgsbFeYpNP5t2aoUNLwBUbc/0kD1R4t9ixDbyFTHd1nok4epoVFpr7PmeWHrhvuV3XaJ4g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-each\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-each/-/jest-each-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gns+Er14+ZrEoC5fhOfYCY1LOHHr0TI+rQUHZS8Ttw2l7gl+80eHc/gFf2Ktkw0+SIACDTeWvpFcv3B04VembQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-environment-node\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-environment-node/-/jest-environment-node-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DOSwCRqXirTOyheM+4d5YZOrWcdu0LNZ87ewUoywbcb2XR4wKgqiG8vNeYwhjFMbEkfju7wx2GYH0P2gevGvFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-get-type\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-get-type/-/jest-get-type-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zrteXnqYxfQh7l5FHyL38jL39di8H8rHoecLH3JNxH3BwOrBsNeabdap5e0I23lD4HHI8W5VFBZqG4Eaq5LNcw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-haste-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-haste-map/-/jest-haste-map-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fP8u2pyfqx0K1rGn1R9pyE0/KTn+G7PxktWidOBTqFPLYX0b9ksaMFkhK5vrS3DVun09pckLdlx90QthlW7AmA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/graceful-fs\": \"^4.1.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"anymatch\": \"^3.0.3\",\n        \"fb-watchman\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"walker\": \"^1.0.8\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"optionalDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-leak-detector\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-leak-detector/-/jest-leak-detector-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kYA8IJcSYtST2BY9I+SMC32nDpBT3J2NvWJx8+JCuCdl/CR1I4EKUJROiP8XtCcxqgTTBGJNdbB1A8XRKbTetw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-matcher-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-matcher-utils/-/jest-matcher-utils-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-sBkD+Xi9DtcChsI3L3u0+N0opgPYnCRPtGcQYrgXmR+hmt/fYfWAL0xRXYU8eWOdfuLgBe0YCW3AFtnRLagq/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-diff\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-message-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-message-util/-/jest-message-util-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GBEV4GRADeP+qtB2+6u61stea8mGcOT4mCtrYISZwfu9/ISHFJ/5zOMXYbpBE9RsS5+Gb63DW4FgmnKJ79Kf6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.12.13\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/stack-utils\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"stack-utils\": \"^2.0.3\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-mock\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-mock/-/jest-mock-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ITOMZn+UkYS4ZFh83xYAOzWStloNzJFO2s8DWrE4lhtGD+AorgnbkiKERe4wQVBydIGPx059g6riW5Btp6Llnw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-pnp-resolver\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-pnp-resolver/-/jest-pnp-resolver-1.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+3NpwQEnRoIBtx4fyhblQDPgJI0H1IEIkX7ShLUjPGA7TtUTvI1oiKi3SR4oBR0hQhQR80l4WAe5RrXBwWMA8w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-regex-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-regex-util/-/jest-regex-util-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KJJBsRCyyLNWCNBOvZyRDnAIfUiRJ8v+hOBQYGn8gDyF3UegwiP4gwRR3/SDa42g1YbVycTidUF3rKjyLFDWbg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-resolve\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-resolve/-/jest-resolve-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-IOVhZSrg+UvVAshDSDtHyFCCBUl/Q3AAJv8iZ6ZjnZ74xzvwuzLXid9IIIPgTnY62SJjfuupMKZsZQRsCvxEgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-pnp-resolver\": \"^1.2.2\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"resolve\": \"^1.20.0\",\n        \"resolve.exports\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-resolve-dependencies\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-resolve-dependencies/-/jest-resolve-dependencies-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-un0zD/6qxJ+S0et7WxeI3H5XSe9lTBBR7bOHCHXkKR6luG5mwDDlIzVQ0V5cZCuoTgEdcdwzTghYkTWfubi+nA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-runner\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-runner/-/jest-runner-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fsc4N6cPCAahybGBfTRcq5wFR6fpLznMg47sY5aDpsoejOcVYFb07AHuSnR0liMcPTgBsA3ZJL6kFOjPdoNipQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"emittery\": \"^0.13.1\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-docblock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-environment-node\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-leak-detector\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-watcher\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"source-map-support\": \"0.5.13\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-runtime\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-runtime/-/jest-runtime-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gUnLjgwdGqW7B4LvOIkbKs9WGbn+QLqRQQ9juC6HndeDiezIwhDP+mhMwHWCEcfQ5RUXa6OPnFF8BJh5xegwwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/globals\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/source-map\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"cjs-module-lexer\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-bom\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-snapshot\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-snapshot/-/jest-snapshot-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Rm0BMWtxBcioHr1/OX5YCP8Uov4riHvKPknOGs804Zg9JGZgmIBkbtlxJC/7Z4msKYVbIJtfU+tKb8xlYNfdkw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@jest/expect-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-diff\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"natural-compare\": \"^1.4.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^7.5.3\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-snapshot/node_modules/semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-util/-/jest-util-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-z6EbKajIpqGKU56y5KBUgy1dt1ihhQJgWzUlZHArA/+X2ad7Cb5iF+AK1EWVL/Bo7Rz9uurpqw6SiBCefUbCGA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"picomatch\": \"^2.2.3\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-validate\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-validate/-/jest-validate-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ZB7wHqaRGVw/9hST/OuFUReG7M8vKeq0/J2egIGLdvjHCmYqGARhzXmtgi+gVeZ5uXFF219aOc3Ls2yLg27tkw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"camelcase\": \"^6.2.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"leven\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-validate/node_modules/camelcase\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/camelcase/-/camelcase-6.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Gmy6FhYlCY7uOElZUSbxo2UCDH8owEk996gkbrpsgGtrJLM3J7jGxl9Ic7Qwwj4ivOE5AWZWRMecDdF7hqGjFA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-watcher\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-watcher/-/jest-watcher-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-49Fg7WXkU3Vl2h6LbLtMQ/HyB6rXSIX7SqvBLQmssRBGN9I0PNvPmAmCWSOY6SOvrjhI/F7/bGAv9RtnsPA03g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"ansi-escapes\": \"^4.2.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"emittery\": \"^0.13.1\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"string-length\": \"^4.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-worker\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-worker/-/jest-worker-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eIz2msL/EzL9UFTFFx7jBTkeZfku0yUAyZZZmJ93H2TYEiroIx2PQjEXcwYtYl8zXCxb+PAmA2hLIt/6ZEkPHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"merge-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^8.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-worker/node_modules/supports-color\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-color/-/supports-color-8.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MpUEN2OodtUzxvKQl72cUF7RQ5EiHsGvSsVG0ia9c5RbWGL2CI4C7EpPS8UTBIplnlzZiNuV56w+FuNxy3ty2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/js-tokens\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/js-tokens/-/js-tokens-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RdJUflcE3cUzKiMqQgsCu06FPu9UdIJO0beYbPhHN4k6apgJtifcoCtT9bcxOpYBtpD2kCM6Sbzg4CausW/PKQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/js-yaml\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.14.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/js-yaml/-/js-yaml-3.14.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-okMH7OXXJ7YrN9Ok3/SXrnu4iX9yOk+25nqX4imS2npuvTYDmo/QEZoqwZkYaIDk3jVvBOTOIEgEhaLOynBS9g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jsesc\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jsesc/-/jsesc-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/sM3dO2FOzXjKQhJuo0Q173wf2KOo8t4I8vHy6lF9poUp7bKT0/NHE8fPX23PwfhnykfqnC2xRxOnVw5XuGIaA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/json-parse-even-better-errors\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/json-parse-even-better-errors/-/json-parse-even-better-errors-2.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xyFwyhro/JEof6Ghe2iz2NcXoj2sloNsWr/XsERDK/oiPCfaNhl5ONfp+jQdAZRQQ0IJWNzH9zIZF7li91kh2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/json5\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/json5/-/json5-2.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XmOWe7eyHYH14cLdVPoyg+GOH3rYX++KpzrylJwSW98t3Nk+U8XOl8FWKOgwtzdb8lXGf6zYwDUzeHMWfxasyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/kleur\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/kleur/-/kleur-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eTIzlVOSUR+JxdDFepEYcBMtZ9Qqdef+rnzWdRZuMbOywu5tO2w2N7rqjoANZ5k9vywhL6Br1VRjUIgTQx4E8w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/leven\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/leven/-/leven-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qsda+H8jTaUaN/x5vzW2rzc+8Rw4TAQ/4KjB46IwK5VH+IlVeeeje/EoZRpiXvIqjFgK84QffqPztGI3VBLG1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/lines-and-columns\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/lines-and-columns/-/lines-and-columns-1.2.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7ylylesZQ/PV29jhEDl3Ufjo6ZX7gCqJr5F7PKrqc93v7fzSymt1BpwEU8nAUXs8qzzvqhbjhK5QZg6Mt/HkBg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/locate-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/locate-path/-/locate-path-5.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-t7hw9pI+WvuwNJXwk5zVHpyhIqzg2qTlklJOf0mVxGSbe3Fp2VieZcduNYjaLDoy6p9uGpQEGWG87WpMKlNq8g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/lru-cache\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/lru-cache/-/lru-cache-5.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KpNARQA3Iwv+jTA0utUVVbrh+Jlrr1Fv0e56GGzAFOXN7dk/FviaDW8LHmK52DlcH4WP2n6gI8vN1aesBFgo9w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/make-dir\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/make-dir/-/make-dir-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hXdUTZYIVOt1Ex//jAQi+wTZZpUpwBj/0QsOzqegb3rGMMeJiSEu5xLHnYfBrRV4RH2+OCSOO95Is/7x1WJ4bw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/make-dir/node_modules/semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/makeerror\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.12\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/makeerror/-/makeerror-1.0.12.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JmqCvUhmt43madlpFzG4BQzG2Z3m6tvQDNKdClZnO3VbIudJYmxsT0FNJMeiB2+JTSlTQTSbU8QdesVmwJcmLg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/merge-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/merge-stream/-/merge-stream-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-abv/qOcuPfk3URPfDzmZU1LKmuw8kT+0nIHvKrKgFrwifol/doWcdA4ZqsWQ8ENrFKkd67Mfpo/LovbIUsbt3w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/micromatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/micromatch/-/micromatch-4.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-PXwfBhYu0hBCPw8Dn0E+WDYb7af3dSLVWKi3HGv84IdF4TyFoC0ysxFd0Goxw7nSv4T/PzEJQxsYsEiFCKo2BA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/mimic-fn\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/mimic-fn/-/mimic-fn-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OqbOk5oEQeAZ8WXWydlu9HJjz9WVdEIvamMCcXmuqUYjTknH/sqsWvhQ3vgwKFRR1HpjvNBKQ37nbJgYzGqGcg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/minimatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/minimatch/-/minimatch-3.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-J7p63hRiAjw1NDEww1W7i37+ByIrOWO5XQQAzZ3VOcL0PNybwpfmV/N05zFAzwQ9USyEcX6t3UO+K5aqBQOIHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/ms\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ms/-/ms-2.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6FlzubTLZG3J2a/NVCAleEhjzq5oxgHyaCU9yYXvcLsvoVaHJq/s5xXI6/XXP6tz7R9xAOtHnSO/tXtF3WRTlA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/natural-compare\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/natural-compare/-/natural-compare-1.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OWND8ei3VtNC9h7V60qff3SVobHr996CTwgxubgyQYEpg290h9J0buyECNNJexkFm5sOajh5G116RYA1c8ZMSw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/node-int64\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/node-int64/-/node-int64-0.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-O5lz91xSOeoXP6DulyHfllpq+Eg00MWitZIbtPfoSEvqIHdl5gfcY6hYzDWnj0qD5tz52PI08u9qUvSVeUBeHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/node-releases\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.19\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/node-releases/-/node-releases-2.0.19.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xxOWJsBKtzAq7DY0J+DTzuz58K8e7sJbdgwkbMWQe8UYB6ekmsQ45q0M/tJDsGaZmbC+l7n57UV8Hl5tHxO9uw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/normalize-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/normalize-path/-/normalize-path-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6eZs5Ls3WtCisHWp9S2GUy8dqkpGi4BVSz3GaqiE6ezub0512ESztXUwUB6C6IKbQkY2Pnb/mD4WYojCRwcwLA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/npm-run-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/npm-run-path/-/npm-run-path-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-S48WzZW777zhNIrn7gxOlISNAqi9ZC/uQFnRdbeIHhZhCA6UqpkOT8T1G7BvfdgP4Er8gF4sUbaS0i7QvIfCWw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/once\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/once/-/once-1.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lNaJgI+2Q5URQBkccEKHTQOPaXdUxnZZElQTZY0MFUAuaEqe1E+Nyvgdz/aIyNi6Z9MzO5dv1H8n58/GELp3+w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/onetime\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/onetime/-/onetime-5.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kbpaSSGJTWdAY5KPVeMOKXSrPtr8C8C7wodJbcsd51jRnmD+GZu8Y0VoU6Dm5Z4vWr0Ig/1NKuWRKf7j5aaYSg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/p-limit\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-limit/-/p-limit-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TYOanM3wGwNGsZN2cVTYPArw454xnXj5qmWF1bEoAc4+cU/ol7GVh7odevjp1FNHduHc3KZMcFduxU5Xc6uJRQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/p-locate\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-locate/-/p-locate-4.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R79ZZ/0wAxKGu3oYMlz8jy/kbhsNrS7SKZ7PxEHBgJ5+F2mtFW2fK2cOtBh1cHYkQsbzFV7I+EoRKe6Yt0oK7A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/p-locate/node_modules/p-limit\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-limit/-/p-limit-2.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-//88mFWSJx8lxCzwdAABTJL2MyWB12+eIY7MDL2SqLmAkeKU9qxRvWuSyTjm3FUmpBEMuFfckAIqEaVGUDxb6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/p-try\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-try/-/p-try-2.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R4nPAVTAU0B9D35/Gk3uJf/7XYbQcyohSKdvAxIRSNghFl4e71hVoGnBNQz9cWaXxO2I10KTC+3jMdvvoKw6dQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/parse-json\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/parse-json/-/parse-json-5.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ayCKvm/phCGxOkYRSCM82iDwct8/EonSEgCSxWxD7ve6jHggsFl4fZVQBPRNgQoKiuV/odhFrGzQXZwbifC8Rg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.0.0\",\n        \"error-ex\": \"^1.3.1\",\n        \"json-parse-even-better-errors\": \"^2.3.0\",\n        \"lines-and-columns\": \"^1.1.6\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/path-exists\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-exists/-/path-exists-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ak9Qy5Q7jYb2Wwcey5Fpvg2KoAc/ZIhLSLOSBmRmygPsGwkVVt0fZa0qrtMz+m6tJTAHfZQ8FnmB4MG4LWy7/w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/path-is-absolute\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-is-absolute/-/path-is-absolute-1.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-AVbw3UJ2e9bq64vSaS9Am0fje1Pa8pbGqTTsmXfaIiMpnr5DlDhfJOuLj9Sf95ZPVDAUerDfEk88MPmPe7UCQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/path-key\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-key/-/path-key-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ojmeN0qd+y0jszEtoY48r0Peq5dwMEkIlCOu6Q5f41lfkswXuKtYrhgoTpLnyIcHm24Uhqx+5Tqm2InSwLhE6Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/path-parse\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-parse/-/path-parse-1.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LDJzPVEEEPR+y48z93A0Ed0yXb8pAByGWo/k5YYdYgpY2/2EsOsksJrq7lOHxryrVOn1ejG6oAp8ahvOIQD8sw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/picocolors\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/picocolors/-/picocolors-1.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xceH2snhtb5M9liqDsmEw56le376mTZkEX/jEb/RxNFyegNul7eNslCXP9FDj/Lcu0X8KEyMceP2ntpaHrDEVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/picomatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/picomatch/-/picomatch-2.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JU3teHTNjmE2VCGFzuY8EXzCDVwEqB2a8fsIvwaStHhAWJEeVd1o1QD80CU6+ZdEXXSLbSsuLwJjkCBWqRQUVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pirates\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pirates/-/pirates-4.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TfySrs/5nm8fQJDcBDuUng3VOUKsd7S+zqvbOTiGXHfxX4wK31ard+hoNuvkicM/2YFzlpDgABOevKSsB4G/FA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pkg-dir\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pkg-dir/-/pkg-dir-4.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-HRDzbaKjC+AOWVXxAU/x54COGeIv9eb+6CkDSQoNTt4XyWoIJvuPsXizxu/Fr23EiekbtZwmh1IcIG/l/a10GQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pretty-format\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pretty-format/-/pretty-format-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Pdlw/oPxN+aXdmM9R00JVC9WVFoCLTKJvDVLgmJ+qAffBMxsV85l/Lu7sNx4zSzPyoL2euImuEwHhOXdEgNFZQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/schemas\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"react-is\": \"^18.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pretty-format/node_modules/ansi-styles\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-styles/-/ansi-styles-5.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Cxwpt2SfTzTtXcfOlzGEee8O+c+MmUgGrNiBcXnuWxuFJHe6a5Hz7qwhwe5OgaSYI0IJvkLqWX1ASG+cJOkEiA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/prompts\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.4.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/prompts/-/prompts-2.4.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NxNv/kLguCA7p3jE8oL2aEBsrJWgAakBpgmgK6lpPWV+WuOmY6r2/zbAVnP+T8bQlA0nzHXSJSJW0Hq7ylaD2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pure-rand\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pure-rand/-/pure-rand-6.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bVWawvoZoBYpp6yIoQtQXHZjmz35RSVHnUOTefl8Vcjr8snTPY1wnpSPMWekcFwbxI6gtmT7rSYPFvz71ldiOA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"individual\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/dubzzz\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n          \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/fast-check\"\n        }\n      ]\n    },\n    \"node_modules/react-is\": {\n      \"version\": \"18.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/react-is/-/react-is-18.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/LLMVyas0ljjAtoYiPqYiL8VWXzUUdThrmU5+n20DZv+a+ClRoevUzw5JxU+Ieh5/c87ytoTBV9G1FiKfNJdmg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/require-directory\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/require-directory/-/require-directory-2.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fGxEI7+wsG9xrvdjsrlmL22OMTTiHRwAMroiEeMgq8gzoLC/PQr7RsRDSTLUg/bZAZtF+TVIkHc6/4RIKrui+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/resolve\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.22.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve/-/resolve-1.22.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NPRy+/ncIMeDlTAsuqwKIiferiawhefFJtkNSW0qZJEqMEb+qBt/77B/jGeeek+F0uOeN05CDa6HXbbIgtVX4w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"is-core-module\": \"^2.16.0\",\n        \"path-parse\": \"^1.0.7\",\n        \"supports-preserve-symlinks-flag\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/resolve-cwd\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve-cwd/-/resolve-cwd-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OrZaX2Mb+rJCpH/6CpSqt9xFVpN++x01XnN2ie9g6P5/3xelLAkXWVADpdz1IHD/KFfEXyE6V0U01OQ3UO2rEg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/resolve-from\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve-from/-/resolve-from-5.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qYg9KP24dD5qka9J47d0aVky0N+b4fTU89LN9iDnjB5waksiC49rvMB0PrUJQGoTmH50XPiqOvAjDfaijGxYZw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/resolve.exports\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve.exports/-/resolve.exports-2.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OcXjMsGdhL4XnbShKpAcSqPMzQoYkYyhbEaeSko47MjRP9NfEQMhZkXL1DoFlt9LWQn4YttrdnV6X2OiyzBi+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-6.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BR7VvDCVHO+q2xBEWskxS6DJE1qRnb7DxzUrogb71CWoSficBxYsiAGd+Kl0mmq/MprG9yArRkyrQxTO6XjMzA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/shebang-command\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/shebang-command/-/shebang-command-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kHxr2zZpYtdmrN1qDjrrX/Z1rR1kG8Dx+gkpK1G4eXmvXswmcE1hTWBWYUzlraYw1/yZp6YuDY77YtvbN0dmDA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/shebang-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/shebang-regex/-/shebang-regex-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7++dFhtcx3353uBaq8DDR4NuxBetBzC7ZQOhmTQInHEd6bSrXdiEyzCvG07Z44UYdLShWUyXt5M/yhz8ekcb1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/signal-exit\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/signal-exit/-/signal-exit-3.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wnD2ZE+l+SPC/uoS0vXeE9L1+0wuaMqKlfz9AMUo38JsyLSBWSFcHR1Rri62LZc12vLr1gb3jl7iwQhgwpAbGQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/sisteransi\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/sisteransi/-/sisteransi-1.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bLGGlR1QxBcynn2d5YmDX4MGjlZvy2MRBDRNHLJ8VI6l6+9FUiyTFNJ0IveOSP0bcXgVDPRcfGqA0pjaqUpfVg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/slash\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/slash/-/slash-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-g9Q1haeby36OSStwb4ntCGGGaKsaVSjQ68fBxoQcutl5fS1vuY18H3wSt3jFyFtrkx+Kz0V1G85A4MyAdDMi2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.6.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/source-map/-/source-map-0.6.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UjgapumWlbMhkBgzT7Ykc5YXUT46F0iKu8SGXq0bcwP5dz/h0Plj6enJqjz1Zbq2l5WaqYnrVbwWOWMyF3F47g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/source-map-support\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.5.13\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/source-map-support/-/source-map-support-0.5.13.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-SHSKFHadjVA5oR4PPqhtAVdcBWwRYVd6g6cAXnIbRiIwc2EhPrTuKUBdSLvlEKyIP3GCf89fltvcZiP9MMFA1w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"buffer-from\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"source-map\": \"^0.6.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/sprintf-js\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/sprintf-js/-/sprintf-js-1.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-D9cPgkvLlV3t3IzL0D0YLvGA9Ahk4PcvVwUbN0dSGr1aP0Nrt4AEnTUbuGvquEC0mA64Gqt1fzirlRs5ibXx8g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/stack-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/stack-utils/-/stack-utils-2.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XlkWvfIm6RmsWtNJx+uqtKLS8eqFbxUg0ZzLXqY0caEy9l7hruX8IpiDnjsLavoBgqCCR71TqWO8MaXYheJ3RQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/string-length\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/string-length/-/string-length-4.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+l6rNN5fYHNhZZy41RXsYptCjA2Igmq4EG7kZAYFQI1E1VTXarr6ZPXBg6eq7Y6eK4FEhY6AJlyuFIb/v/S0VQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"char-regex\": \"^1.0.2\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/string-width\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/string-width/-/string-width-4.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wKyQRQpjJ0sIp62ErSZdGsjMJWsap5oRNihHhu6G7JVO/9jIB6UyevL+tXuOqrng8j/cxKTWyWUwvSTriiZz/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"emoji-regex\": \"^8.0.0\",\n        \"is-fullwidth-code-point\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/strip-ansi\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-ansi/-/strip-ansi-6.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Y38VPSHcqkFrCpFnQ9vuSXmquuv5oXOKpGeT6aGrr3o3Gc9AlVa6JBfUSOCnbxGGZF+/0ooI7KrPuUSztUdU5A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/strip-bom\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-bom/-/strip-bom-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3xurFv5tEgii33Zi8Jtp55wEIILR9eh34FAW00PZf+JnSsTmV/ioewSgQl97JHvgjoRGwPShsWm+IdrxB35d0w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/strip-final-newline\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-final-newline/-/strip-final-newline-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BrpvfNAE3dcvq7ll3xVumzjKjZQ5tI1sEUIKr3Uoks0XUl45St3FlatVqef9prk4jRDzhW6WZg+3bk93y6pLjA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/strip-json-comments\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-json-comments/-/strip-json-comments-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6fPc+R4ihwqP6N/aIv2f1gMH8lOVtWQHoqC4yK6oSDVVocumAsfCqjkXnqiYMhmMwS/mEHLp7Vehlt3ql6lEig==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/supports-color\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-color/-/supports-color-7.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qpCAvRl9stuOHveKsn7HncJRvv501qIacKzQlO/+Lwxc9+0q2wLyv4Dfvt80/DPn2pqOBsJdDiogXGR9+OvwRw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag/-/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag-1.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ot0WnXS9fgdkgIcePe6RHNk1WA8+muPa6cSjeR3V8K27q9BB1rTE3R1p7Hv0z1ZyAc8s6Vvv8DIyWf681MAt0w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/test-exclude\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/test-exclude/-/test-exclude-6.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-cAGWPIyOHU6zlmg88jwm7VRyXnMN7iV68OGAbYDk/Mh/xC/pzVPlQtY6ngoIH/5/tciuhGfvESU8GrHrcxD56w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.4\",\n        \"minimatch\": \"^3.0.4\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/tmpl\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/tmpl/-/tmpl-1.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3f0uOEAQwIqGuWW2MVzYg8fV/QNnc/IpuJNG837rLuczAaLVHslWHZQj4IGiEl5Hs3kkbhwL9Ab7Hrsmuj+Smw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/to-regex-range\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/to-regex-range/-/to-regex-range-5.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-65P7iz6X5yEr1cwcgvQxbbIw7Uk3gOy5dIdtZ4rDveLqhrdJP+Li/Hx6tyK0NEb+2GCyneCMJiGqrADCSNk8sQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/type-detect\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/type-detect/-/type-detect-4.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0fr/mIH1dlO+x7TlcMy+bIDqKPsw/70tVyeHW787goQjhmqaZe10uwLujubK9q9Lg6Fiho1KUKDYz0Z7k7g5/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/type-fest\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.21.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/type-fest/-/type-fest-0.21.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-t0rzBq87m3fVcduHDUFhKmyyX+9eo6WQjZvf51Ea/M0Q7+T374Jp1aUiyUl0GKxp8M/OETVHSDvmkyPgvX+X2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/undici-types\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.21.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/undici-types/-/undici-types-6.21.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iwDZqg0QAGrg9Rav5H4n0M64c3mkR59cJ6wQp+7C4nI0gsmExaedaYLNO44eT4AtBBwjbTiGPMlt2Md0T9H9JQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/update-browserslist-db\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/update-browserslist-db/-/update-browserslist-db-1.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UxhIZQ+QInVdunkDAaiazvvT/+fXL5Osr0JZlJulepYu6Jd7qJtDZjlur0emRlT71EN3ScPoE7gvsuIKKNavKw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n          \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"tidelift\",\n          \"url\": \"https://tidelift.com/funding/github/npm/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"github\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/ai\"\n        }\n      ],\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/v8-to-istanbul\": {\n      \"version\": \"9.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/v8-to-istanbul/-/v8-to-istanbul-9.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kiGUalWN+rgBJ/1OHZsBtU4rXZOfj/7rKQxULKlIzwzQSvMJUUNgPwJEEh7gU6xEVxC0ahoOBvN2YI8GH6FNgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.12\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.1\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/walker\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/walker/-/walker-1.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ts/8E8l5b7kY0vlWLewOkDXMmPdLcVV4GmOQLyxuSswIJsweeFZtAsMF7k1Nszz+TYBQrlYRmzOnr398y1JemQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/which\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/which/-/which-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BLI3Tl1TW3Pvl70l3yq3Y64i+awpwXqsGBYWkkqMtnbXgrMD+yj7rhW0kuEDxzJaYXGjEW5ogapKNMEKNMjibA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/wrap-ansi\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/wrap-ansi/-/wrap-ansi-7.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-YVGIj2kamLSTxw6NsZjoBxfSwsn0ycdesmc4p+Q21c5zPuZ1pl+NfxVdxPtdHvmNVOQ6XSYG4AUtyt/Fi7D16Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/wrappy\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/wrappy/-/wrappy-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-l4Sp/DRseor9wL6EvV2+TuQn63dMkPjZ/sp9XkghTEbV9KlPS1xUsZ3u7/IQO4wxtcFB4bgpQPRcR3QCvezPcQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/write-file-atomic\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/write-file-atomic/-/write-file-atomic-4.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7KxauUdBmSdWnmpaGFg+ppNjKF8uNLry8LyzjauQDOVONfFLNKrKvQOxZ/VuTIcS/gge/YNahf5RIIQWTSarlg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"imurmurhash\": \"^0.1.4\",\n        \"signal-exit\": \"^3.0.7\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/y18n\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/y18n/-/y18n-5.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0pfFzegeDWJHJIAmTLRP2DwHjdF5s7jo9tuztdQxAhINCdvS+3nGINqPd00AphqJR/0LhANUS6/+7SCb98YOfA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/yallist\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yallist/-/yallist-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-a4UGQaWPH59mOXUYnAG2ewncQS4i4F43Tv3JoAM+s2VDAmS9NsK8GpDMLrCHPksFT7h3K6TOoUNn2pb7RoXx4g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/yargs\": {\n      \"version\": \"17.7.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yargs/-/yargs-17.7.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7dSzzRQ++CKnNI/krKnYRV7JKKPUXMEh61soaHKg9mrWEhzFWhFnxPxGl+69cD1Ou63C13NUPCnmIcrvqCuM6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"cliui\": \"^8.0.1\",\n        \"escalade\": \"^3.1.1\",\n        \"get-caller-file\": \"^2.0.5\",\n        \"require-directory\": \"^2.1.1\",\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.2.3\",\n        \"y18n\": \"^5.0.5\",\n        \"yargs-parser\": \"^21.1.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/yargs-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"21.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yargs-parser/-/yargs-parser-21.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tVpsJW7DdjecAiFpbIB1e3qxIQsE6NoPc5/eTdrbbIC4h0LVsWhnoa3g+m2HclBIujHzsxZ4VJVA+GUuc2/LBw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/yocto-queue\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yocto-queue/-/yocto-queue-0.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-rVksvsnNCdJ/ohGc6xgPwyN8eheCxsiLM8mxuE/t/mOVqJewPuO1miLpTHQiRgTKCLexL4MeAFVagts7HmNZ2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    }\n  },\n  \"dependencies\": {\n    \"@ampproject/remapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@ampproject/remapping/-/remapping-2.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-30iZtAPgz+LTIYoeivqYo853f02jBYSd5uGnGpkFV0M3xOt9aN73erkgYAmZU43x4VfqcnLxW9Kpg3R5LC4YYw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": \"^0.3.5\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.24\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/code-frame\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/code-frame/-/code-frame-7.26.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RJlIHRueQgwWitWgF8OdFYGZX328Ax5BCemNGlqHfplnRT9ESi8JkFlvaVYbS+UubVY6dpv87Fs2u5M29iNFVQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"js-tokens\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"picocolors\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/compat-data\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/compat-data/-/compat-data-7.26.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-oH5UPLMWR3L2wEFLnFJ1TZXqHufiTKAiLfqw5zkhS4dKXLJ10yVztfil/twG8EDTA4F/tvVNw9nOl4ZMslB8rQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/core\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/core/-/core-7.26.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-vMqyb7XCDMPvJFFOaT9kxtiRh42GwlZEg1/uIgtZshS5a/8OaduUfCi7kynKgc3Tw/6Uo2D+db9qBttghhmxwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@ampproject/remapping\": \"^2.2.0\",\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/helper-compilation-targets\": \"^7.26.5\",\n        \"@babel/helper-module-transforms\": \"^7.26.0\",\n        \"@babel/helpers\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.26.9\",\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"debug\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"gensync\": \"^1.0.0-beta.2\",\n        \"json5\": \"^2.2.3\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/generator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/generator/-/generator-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-VybsKvpiN1gU1sdMZIp7FcqphVVKEwcuj02x73uvcHE0PTihx1nlBcowYWhDwjpoAXRv43+gDzyggGnn1XZhVw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": \"^0.3.5\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.25\",\n        \"jsesc\": \"^3.0.2\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-compilation-targets\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-compilation-targets/-/helper-compilation-targets-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LVk7fbXml0H2xH34dFzKQ7TDZ2G4/rVTOrq9V+icbbadjbVxxeFeDsNHv2SrZeWoA+6ZiTyWYWtScEIW07EAcA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/compat-data\": \"^7.26.8\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-option\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"browserslist\": \"^4.24.0\",\n        \"lru-cache\": \"^5.1.1\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-module-imports\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-module-imports/-/helper-module-imports-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tnUA4RsrmflIM6W6RFTLFSXITtl0wKjgpnLgXyowocVPrbYrLUXSBXDgTs8BlbmIzIdlBySRQjINYs2BAkiLtw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-module-transforms\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-module-transforms/-/helper-module-transforms-7.26.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xO+xu6B5K2czEnQye6BHA7DolFFmS3LB7stHZFaOLb1pAwO1HWLS8fXA+eh0A2yIvltPVmx3eNNDBJA2SLHXFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-module-imports\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-plugin-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-plugin-utils/-/helper-plugin-utils-7.26.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RS+jZcRdZdRFzMyr+wcsaqOmld1/EqTghfaBGQQd/WnRdzdlvSZ//kF7U8VQTxf1ynZ4cjUcYgjVGx13ewNPMg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-string-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-string-parser/-/helper-string-parser-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-4A/SCr/2KLd5jrtOMFzaKjVtAei3+2r/NChoBNoZ3EyP/+GlhoaEGoWOZUmFmoITP7zOJyHIMm+DYRd8o3PvHA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-validator-identifier/-/helper-validator-identifier-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Ed61U6XJc3CVRfkERJWDz4dJwKe7iLmmJsbOGu9wSloNSFttHV0I8g6UAgb7qnK5ly5bGLPd4oXZlxCdANBOWQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-validator-option\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-validator-option/-/helper-validator-option-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-e/zv1co8pp55dNdEcCynfj9X7nyUKUXoUEwfXqaZt0omVOmDe9oOTdKStH4GmAw6zxMFs50ZayuMfHDKlO7Tfw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/helpers\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helpers/-/helpers-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-U5eyP/CTFPuNE3qk+WZMxFkp/4zUzdceQlfzf7DdGdhp+Fezd7HD+i8Y24ZuTMKX3wQBld449jijbGq6OdGNQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/parser/-/parser-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iaepho73/2Pz7w2eMS0Q5f83+0RKI7i4xmiYeBmDzfRVbQtTOG7Ts0S4HzJVsTMGI9keU8rNfuZr8DKfSt7Yyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators/-/plugin-syntax-async-generators-7.8.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tycmZxkGfZaxhMRbXlPXuVFpdWlXpir2W4AMhSJgRKzk/eDlIXOhb2LHWoLpDF7TEHylV5zNhykX6KAgHJmTNw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint/-/plugin-syntax-bigint-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wnTnFlG+YxQm3vDxpGE57Pj0srRU4sHE/mDkt1qv2YJJSeUAec2ma4WLUnUPeKjyrfntVwe/N6dCXpU+zL3Npg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.12.13\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties/-/plugin-syntax-class-properties-7.12.13.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fm4idjKla0YahUNgFNLCB0qySdsoPiZP3iQE3rky0mBUtMZ23yDJ9SJdg6dXTSDnulOVqiF3Hgr9nbXvXTQZYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block/-/plugin-syntax-class-static-block-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-b+YyPmr6ldyNnM6sqYeMWE+bgJcJpO6yS4QD7ymxgH34GBPNDM/THBh8iunyvKIZztiwLH4CJZ0RxTk9emgpjw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes/-/plugin-syntax-import-attributes-7.26.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-e2dttdsJ1ZTpi3B9UYGLw41hifAubg19AtCu/2I/F1QNVclOBr1dYpTdmdyZ84Xiz43BS/tCUkMAZNLv12Pi+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta/-/plugin-syntax-import-meta-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Yqfm+XDx0+Prh3VSeEQCPU81yC+JWZ2pDPFSS4ZdpfZhp4MkFMaDC1UqseovEKwSUpnIL7+vK+Clp7bfh0iD7g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings/-/plugin-syntax-json-strings-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lY6kdGpWHvjoe2vk4WrAapEuBR69EMxZl+RoGRhrFGNYVK8mOPAW8VfbT/ZgrFbXlDNiiaxQnAtgVCZ6jv30EA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx/-/plugin-syntax-jsx-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ld6oezHQMZsZfp6pWtbjaNDF2tiiCYYDqQszHt5VV437lewP9aSi2Of99CK0D0XB21k7FLgnLcmQKyKzynfeAA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators/-/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-d8waShlpFDinQ5MtvGU9xDAOzKH47+FFoney2baFIoMr952hKOLp1HR7VszoZvOsV/4+RRszNY7D17ba0te0ig==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator/-/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-aSff4zPII1u2QD7y+F8oDsz19ew4IGEJg9SVW+bqwpwtfFleiQDMdzA/R+UlWDzfnHFCxxleFT0PMIrR36XLNQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator/-/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9H6YdfkcK/uOnY/K7/aA2xpzaAgkQn37yzWUMRK7OaPOqOpGS1+n0H5hxT9AUw9EsSjPW8SVyMJwYRtWs3X3ug==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread/-/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XoqMijGZb9y3y2XskN+P1wUGiVwWZ5JmoDRwx5+3GmEplNyVM2s2Dg8ILFQm8rWM48orGy5YpI5Bl8U1y7ydlA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding/-/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6VPD0Pc1lpTqw0aKoeRTMiB+kWhAoT24PA+ksWSBrFtl5SIRVpZlwN3NNPQjehA2E/91FV3RjLWoVTglWcSV3Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining/-/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KoK9ErH1MBlCPxV0VANkXW2/dw4vlbGDrFgz8bmUsBGYkFRcbRwMh6cIJubdPrkxRwuGdtCk0v/wPTKbQgBjkg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object/-/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0wVnp9dxJ72ZUJDV27ZfbSj6iHLoytYZmh3rFcxNnvsJF3ktkzLDZPy/mA17HGsaQT3/DQsWYX1f1QGWkCoVUg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await/-/plugin-syntax-top-level-await-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hx++upLv5U1rgYfwe1xBQUhRmU41NEvpUvrp8jkrSCdvGSnM5/qdRMtylJ6PG5OFkBaHkbTAKTnd3/YyESRHFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript/-/plugin-syntax-typescript-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hjMgRy5hb8uJJjUcdWunWVcoi9bGpJp8p5Ol1229PoN6aytsLwNMgmdftO23wnCLMfVmTwZDWMPNq/D1SY60JQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/template\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/template/-/template-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2ncevenBqXI6qRMukPlXwHKHchC7RyMuu4xv5JBXRfOGVcTy1mXCD12qrp7Jsoxll1EV3+9sE4GugBVRjT2jFA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/traverse\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/traverse/-/traverse-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-19lYZFzYVQkkHkl4Cy4WrAVcqBkgvV2YM2TU3xG6DIwO7O3ecbDPfW3yM3bjAGcqcQHi+CCtjMR3dIEHxsd6bA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"debug\": \"^4.3.1\",\n        \"globals\": \"^11.1.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/types\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/types/-/types-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-H45s8fVLYjbhFH62dIJ3WtmJ6RSPt/3DRO0ZcT2SUiYiQyz3BLVb9ADEnLl91m74aQPS3AzzeajZHYOalWe3bg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-string-parser\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@bcoe/v8-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@bcoe/v8-coverage/-/v8-coverage-0.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0hYQ8SB4Db5zvZB4axdMHGwEaQjkZzFjQiN9LVYvIFB2nSUHW9tYpxWriPrWDASIxiaXax83REcLxuSdnGPZtw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config/-/load-nyc-config-1.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-VjeHSlIzpv/NyD3N0YuHfXOPDIixcA1q2ZV98wsMqcYlPmv2n3Yb2lYP9XMElnaFVXg5A7YLTeLu6V84uQDjmQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"camelcase\": \"^5.3.1\",\n        \"find-up\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"get-package-type\": \"^0.1.0\",\n        \"js-yaml\": \"^3.13.1\",\n        \"resolve-from\": \"^5.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@istanbuljs/schema\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@istanbuljs/schema/-/schema-0.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ZXRY4jNvVgSVQ8DL3LTcakaAtXwTVUxE81hslsyD2AtoXW/wVob10HkOJ1X/pAlcI7D+2YoZKg5do8G/w6RYgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@jest/console\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/console/-/console-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-5Ni4CU7XHQi32IJ398EEP4RrB8eV09sXP2ROqD4bksHrnTree52PsxvX8tpL8LvTZ3pFzXyPbNQReSN41CAhOg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/core\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/core/-/core-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-n7aeXWKMnGtDA48y8TLWJPJmLmmZ642Ceo78cYWEpiD7FzDgmNDV/GCVRorPABdXLJZ/9wzzgZAlHjXjxDHGsg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/reporters\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"ansi-escapes\": \"^4.2.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-changed-files\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-resolve-dependencies\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runner\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-watcher\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/environment\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/environment/-/environment-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-aQIfHDq33ExsN4jP1NWGXhxgQ/wixs60gDiKO+XVMd8Mn0NWPWgc34ZQDTb2jKaUWQ7MuwoitXAsN2XVXNMpAw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/expect\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/expect/-/expect-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-8uMeAMycttpva3P1lBHB8VciS9V0XAr3GymPpipdyQXbBcuhkLQOSe8E/p92RyAdToS6ZD1tFkX+CkhoECE0dQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/expect-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/expect-utils/-/expect-utils-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GlsNBWiFQFCVi9QVSx7f5AgMeLxe9YCCs5PuP2O2LdjDAA8Jh9eX7lA1Jq/xdXw3Wb3hyvlFNfZIfcRetSzYcA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@jest/fake-timers\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/fake-timers/-/fake-timers-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-q4DH1Ha4TTFPdxLsqDXK1d3+ioSL7yL5oCMJZgDYm6i+6CygW5E5xVr/D1HdsGxjt1ZWSfUAs9OxSB/BNelWrQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@sinonjs/fake-timers\": \"^10.0.2\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/globals\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/globals/-/globals-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-mpiz3dutLbkW2MNFubUGUEVLkTGiqW6yLVTA+JbP6fI6J5iL9Y0Nlg8k95pcF8ctKwCS7WVxteBs29hhfAotzQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/reporters\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/reporters/-/reporters-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DApq0KJbJOEzAFYjHADNNxAE3KbhxQB1y5Kplb5Waqw6zVbuWatSnMjE5gs8FUgEPmNsnZA3NCWl9NG0ia04Pg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@bcoe/v8-coverage\": \"^0.2.3\",\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-report\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-source-maps\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-reports\": \"^3.1.3\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"string-length\": \"^4.0.1\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"v8-to-istanbul\": \"^9.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/schemas\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/schemas/-/schemas-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-mo5j5X+jIZmJQveBKeS/clAueipV7KgiX1vMgCxam1RNYiqE1w62n0/tJJnHtjW8ZHcQco5gY85jA3mi0L+nSA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@jest/source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/source-map/-/source-map-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MHjT95QuipcPrpLM+8JMSzFx6eHp5Bm+4XeFDJlwsvVBjmKNiIAvasGK2fxz2WbGRlnvqehFbh07MMa7n3YJnw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"callsites\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/test-result\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/test-result/-/test-result-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Fdx+tv6x1zlkJPcWXmMDAG2HBnaR9XPSd5aDWQVsfrZmLVT3lU1cwyxLgRmXR9yrq4NBoEm9BMsfgFzTQAbJYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/test-sequencer\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/test-sequencer/-/test-sequencer-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GQwJ5WZVrKnOJuiYiAF52UNUJXgTZx1NHjFSEB0qEMmSZKAkdMoIzw/Cj6x6NF4AvV23AUqDpFzQkN/eYCYTxw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/transform\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/transform/-/transform-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ok/BTPFzFKVMwO5eOHRrvnBVHdRy9IrsrW1GpMaQ9MCnilNLXQKmAX8s1YXDFaai9xJpac2ySzV0YeRRECr2Vw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": \"^6.1.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"fast-json-stable-stringify\": \"^2.1.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pirates\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"write-file-atomic\": \"^4.0.2\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/types\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/types/-/types-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-u3UPsIilWKOM3F9CXtrG8LEJmNxwoCQC/XVj4IKYXvvpx7QIi/Kg1LI5uDmDpKlac62NUtX7eLjRh+jVZcLOzw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/schemas\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-reports\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/yargs\": \"^17.0.8\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.3.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/gen-mapping/-/gen-mapping-0.3.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-imAbBGkb+ebQyxKgzv5Hu2nmROxoDOXHh80evxdoXNOrvAnVx7zimzc1Oo5h9RlfV4vPXaE2iM5pOFbvOCClWA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/set-array\": \"^1.2.1\",\n        \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": \"^1.4.10\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.24\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/resolve-uri\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/resolve-uri/-/resolve-uri-3.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bRISgCIjP20/tbWSPWMEi54QVPRZExkuD9lJL+UIxUKtwVJA8wW1Trb1jMs1RFXo1CBTNZ/5hpC9QvmKWdopKw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/set-array\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/set-array/-/set-array-1.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R8gLRTZeyp03ymzP/6Lil/28tGeGEzhx1q2k703KGWRAI1VdvPIXdG70VJc2pAMw3NA6JKL5hhFu1sJX0Mnn/A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec/-/sourcemap-codec-1.5.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gv3ZRaISU3fjPAgNsriBRqGWQL6quFx04YMPW/zD8XMLsU32mhCCbfbO6KZFLjvYpCZ8zyDEgqsgf+PwPaM7GQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.3.25\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/trace-mapping/-/trace-mapping-0.3.25.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-vNk6aEwybGtawWmy/PzwnGDOjCkLWSD2wqvjGGAgOAwCGWySYXfYoxt00IJkTF+8Lb57DwOb3Aa0o9CApepiYQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/resolve-uri\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": \"^1.4.14\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@sinclair/typebox\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.27.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinclair/typebox/-/typebox-0.27.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+Fj43pSMwJs4KRrH/938Uf+uAELIgVBmQzg/q1YG10djyfA3TnrU8N8XzqCh/okZdszqBQTZf96idMfE5lnwTA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@sinonjs/commons\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinonjs/commons/-/commons-3.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-K3mCHKQ9sVh8o1C9cxkwxaOmXoAMlDxC1mYyHrjqOWEcBjYr76t96zL2zlj5dUGZ3HSw240X1qgH3Mjf1yJWpQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@sinonjs/fake-timers\": {\n      \"version\": \"10.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinonjs/fake-timers/-/fake-timers-10.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-V4BG07kuYSUkTCSBHG8G8TNhM+F19jXFWnQtzj+we8DrkpSBCee9Z3Ms8yiGer/dlmhe35/Xdgyo3/0rQKg7YA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/babel__core\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.20.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__core/-/babel__core-7.20.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qoQprZvz5wQFJwMDqeseRXWv3rqMvhgpbXFfVyWhbx9X47POIA6i/+dXefEmZKoAgOaTdaIgNSMqMIU61yRyzA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.20.7\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.20.7\",\n        \"@types/babel__generator\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/babel__template\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/babel__traverse\": \"*\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@types/babel__generator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__generator/-/babel__generator-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ufFd2Xi92OAVPYsy+P4n7/U7e68fex0+Ee8gSG9KX7eo084CWiQ4sdxktvdl0bOPupXtVJPY19zk6EwWqUQ8lg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/babel__template\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.4.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__template/-/babel__template-7.4.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-h/NUaSyG5EyxBIp8YRxo4RMe2/qQgvyowRwVMzhYhBCONbW8PUsg4lkFMrhgZhUe5z3L3MiLDuvyJ/CaPa2A8A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.1.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@types/babel__traverse\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.20.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__traverse/-/babel__traverse-7.20.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-dkO5fhS7+/oos4ciWxyEyjWe48zmG6wbCheo/G2ZnHx4fs3EU6YC6UM8rk56gAjNJ9P3MTH2jo5jb92/K6wbng==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/graceful-fs\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/graceful-fs/-/graceful-fs-4.1.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-olP3sd1qOEe5dXTSaFvQG+02VdRXcdytWLAZsAq1PecU8uqQAhkrnbli7DagjtXKW/Bl7YJbUsa8MPcuc8LHEQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-lib-coverage/-/istanbul-lib-coverage-2.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2QF/t/auWm0lsy8XtKVPG19v3sSOQlJe/YHZgfjb/KBBHOGSV+J2q/S671rcq9uTBrLAXmZpqJiaQbMT+zNU1w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@types/istanbul-lib-report\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-lib-report/-/istanbul-lib-report-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NQn7AHQnk/RSLOxrBbGyJM/aVQ+pjj5HCgasFxc0K/KhoATfQ/47AyUl15I2yBUpihjmas+a+VJBOqecrFH+uA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/istanbul-reports\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-reports/-/istanbul-reports-3.0.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pk2B1NWalF9toCRu6gjBzR69syFjP4Od8WRAX+0mmf9lAjCRicLOWc+ZrxZHx/0XRjotgkF9t6iaMJ+aXcOdZQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/node\": {\n      \"version\": \"22.14.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/node/-/node-22.14.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-u0HuPQwe/dHrItgHHpmw3N2fYCR6x4ivMNbPHRkBVP4CvN+kiRrKHWk3i8tXiO/joPwXLMYvF9TTF0eqgHIuOw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/stack-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/stack-utils/-/stack-utils-2.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9aEbYZ3TbYMznPdcdr3SmIrLXwC/AKZXQeCf9Pgao5CKb8CyHuEX5jzWPTkvregvhRJHcpRO6BFoGW9ycaOkYw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@types/yargs\": {\n      \"version\": \"17.0.33\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/yargs/-/yargs-17.0.33.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WpxBCKWPLr4xSsHgz511rFJAM+wS28w2zEO1QDNY5zM/S8ok70NNfztH0xwhqKyaK0OHCbN98LDAZuy1ctxDkA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/yargs-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"21.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/yargs-parser/-/yargs-parser-21.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-I4q9QU9MQv4oEOz4tAHJtNz1cwuLxn2F3xcc2iV5WdqLPpUnj30aUuxt1mAxYTG+oe8CZMV/+6rU4S4gRDzqtQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"ansi-escapes\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-escapes/-/ansi-escapes-4.3.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gKXj5ALrKWQLsYG9jlTRmR/xKluxHV+Z9QEwNIgCfM1/uwPMCuzVVnh5mwTd+OuBZcwSIMbqssNWRm1lE51QaQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"ansi-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-regex/-/ansi-regex-5.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-quJQXlTSUGL2LH9SUXo8VwsY4soanhgo6LNSm84E1LBcE8s3O0wpdiRzyR9z/ZZJMlMWv37qOOb9pdJlMUEKFQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"ansi-styles\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-styles/-/ansi-styles-4.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zbB9rCJAT1rbjiVDb2hqKFHNYLxgtk8NURxZ3IZwD3F6NtxbXZQCnnSi1Lkx+IDohdPlFp222wVALIheZJQSEg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"anymatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/anymatch/-/anymatch-3.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KMReFUr0B4t+D+OBkjR3KYqvocp2XaSzO55UcB6mgQMd3KbcE+mWTyvVV7D/zsdEbNnV6acZUutkiHQXvTr1Rw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"normalize-path\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"picomatch\": \"^2.0.4\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"argparse\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/argparse/-/argparse-1.0.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-o5Roy6tNG4SL/FOkCAN6RzjiakZS25RLYFrcMttJqbdd8BWrnA+fGz57iN5Pb06pvBGvl5gQ0B48dJlslXvoTg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"babel-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-jest/-/babel-jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BrvGY3xZSwEcCzKvKsCi2GgHqDqsYkOP4/by5xCgIwGXQxIEh+8ew3gmrE1y7XRR6LHZIj6yLYnUi/mm2KXKBg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@types/babel__core\": \"^7.1.14\",\n        \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": \"^6.1.1\",\n        \"babel-preset-jest\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-plugin-istanbul/-/babel-plugin-istanbul-6.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Y1IQok9821cC9onCx5otgFfRm7Lm+I+wwxOx738M/WLPZ9Q42m4IG5W0FNX8WLL2gYMZo3JkuXIH2DOpWM+qwA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-plugin-utils\": \"^7.0.0\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": \"^5.0.4\",\n        \"test-exclude\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": {\n          \"version\": \"5.2.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-instrument/-/istanbul-lib-instrument-5.2.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-pzqtp31nLv/XFOzXGuvhCb8qhjmTVo5vjVk19XE4CRlSWz0KoeJ3bw9XsA7nOp9YBf4qHjwBxkDzKcME/J29Yg==\",\n          \"dev\": true,\n          \"requires\": {\n            \"@babel/core\": \"^7.12.3\",\n            \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.14.7\",\n            \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n            \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.2.0\",\n            \"semver\": \"^6.3.0\"\n          }\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"babel-plugin-jest-hoist\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-plugin-jest-hoist/-/babel-plugin-jest-hoist-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ESAc/RJvGTFEzRwOTT4+lNDk/GNHMkKbNzsvT0qKRfDyyYTskxB5rnU2njIDYVxXCBHHEI1c0YwHob3WaYujOg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@types/babel__core\": \"^7.1.14\",\n        \"@types/babel__traverse\": \"^7.0.6\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-preset-current-node-syntax/-/babel-preset-current-node-syntax-1.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ldYss8SbBlWva1bs28q78Ju5Zq1F+8BrqBZZ0VFhLBvhh6lCpC2o3gDJi/5DRLs9FgYZCnmPYIVFU4lRXCkyUw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators\": \"^7.8.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties\": \"^7.12.13\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block\": \"^7.14.5\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes\": \"^7.24.7\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object\": \"^7.14.5\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await\": \"^7.14.5\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"babel-preset-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-preset-jest/-/babel-preset-jest-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0B3bhxR6snWXJZtR/RliHTDPRgn1sNHOR0yVtq/IiQFyuOVjFS+wuio/R4gSNkyYmKmJB4wGZv2NZanmKmTnNA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"babel-plugin-jest-hoist\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"balanced-match\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/balanced-match/-/balanced-match-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3oSeUO0TMV67hN1AmbXsK4yaqU7tjiHlbxRDZOpH0KW9+CeX4bRAaX0Anxt0tx2MrpRpWwQaPwIlISEJhYU5Pw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"brace-expansion\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.11\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/brace-expansion/-/brace-expansion-1.1.11.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iCuPHDFgrHX7H2vEI/5xpz07zSHB00TpugqhmYtVmMO6518mCuRMoOYFldEBl0g187ufozdaHgWKcYFb61qGiA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"balanced-match\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"concat-map\": \"0.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"braces\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/braces/-/braces-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-yQbXgO/OSZVD2IsiLlro+7Hf6Q18EJrKSEsdoMzKePKXct3gvD8oLcOQdIzGupr5Fj+EDe8gO/lxc1BzfMpxvA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"browserslist\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.24.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/browserslist/-/browserslist-4.24.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KDi1Ny1gSePi1vm0q4oxSF8b4DR44GF4BbmS2YdhPLOEqd8pDviZOGH/GsmRwoWJ2+5Lr085X7naowMwKHDG1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"caniuse-lite\": \"^1.0.30001688\",\n        \"electron-to-chromium\": \"^1.5.73\",\n        \"node-releases\": \"^2.0.19\",\n        \"update-browserslist-db\": \"^1.1.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"bser\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/bser/-/bser-2.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gQxTNE/GAfIIrmHLUE3oJyp5FO6HRBfhjnw4/wMmA63ZGDJnWBmgY/lyQBpnDUkGmAhbSe39tx2d/iTOAfglwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"buffer-from\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/buffer-from/-/buffer-from-1.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-E+XQCRwSbaaiChtv6k6Dwgc+bx+Bs6vuKJHHl5kox/BaKbhiXzqQOwK4cO22yElGp2OCmjwVhT3HmxgyPGnJfQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"callsites\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/callsites/-/callsites-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-P8BjAsXvZS+VIDUI11hHCQEv74YT67YUi5JJFNWIqL235sBmjX4+qx9Muvls5ivyNENctx46xQLQ3aTuE7ssaQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"camelcase\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/camelcase/-/camelcase-5.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-L28STB170nwWS63UjtlEOE3dldQApaJXZkOI1uMFfzf3rRuPegHaHesyee+YxQ+W6SvRDQV6UrdOdRiR153wJg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"caniuse-lite\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.30001715\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/caniuse-lite/-/caniuse-lite-1.0.30001715.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7ptkFGMm2OAOgvZpwgA4yjQ5SQbrNVGdRjzH0pBdy1Fasvcr+KAeECmbCAECzTuDuoX0FCY8KzUxjf9+9kfZEw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"chalk\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/chalk/-/chalk-4.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-oKnbhFyRIXpUuez8iBMmyEa4nbj4IOQyuhc/wy9kY7/WVPcwIO9VA668Pu8RkO7+0G76SLROeyw9CpQ061i4mA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^7.1.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"char-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/char-regex/-/char-regex-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kWWXztvZ5SBQV+eRgKFeh8q5sLuZY2+8WUIzlxWVTg+oGwY14qylx1KbKzHd8P6ZYkAg0xyIDU9JMHhyJMZ1jw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"ci-info\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.9.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ci-info/-/ci-info-3.9.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NIxF55hv4nSqQswkAeiOi1r83xy8JldOFDTWiug55KBu9Jnblncd2U6ViHmYgHf01TPZS77NJBhBMKdWj9HQMQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"cjs-module-lexer\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cjs-module-lexer/-/cjs-module-lexer-1.4.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9z8TZaGM1pfswYeXrUpzPrkx8UnWYdhJclsiYMm6x/w5+nN+8Tf/LnAgfLGQCm59qAOxU8WwHEq2vNwF6i4j+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"cliui\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cliui/-/cliui-8.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BSeNnyus75C4//NQ9gQt1/csTXyo/8Sb+afLAkzAptFuMsod9HFokGNudZpi/oQV73hnVK+sR+5PVRMd+Dr7YQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.2.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.1\",\n        \"wrap-ansi\": \"^7.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"co\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.6.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/co/-/co-4.6.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-QVb0dM5HvG+uaxitm8wONl7jltx8dqhfU33DcqtOZcLSVIKSDDLDi7+0LbAKiyI8hD9u42m2YxXSkMGWThaecQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"collect-v8-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/collect-v8-coverage/-/collect-v8-coverage-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lHl4d5/ONEbLlJvaJNtsF/Lz+WvB07u2ycqTYbdrq7UypDXailES4valYb2eWiJFxZlVmpGekfqoxQhzyFdT4Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"color-convert\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/color-convert/-/color-convert-2.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RRECPsj7iu/xb5oKYcsFHSppFNnsj/52OVTRKb4zP5onXwVF3zVmmToNcOfGC+CRDpfK/U584fMg38ZHCaElKQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"color-name\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/color-name/-/color-name-1.1.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-dOy+3AuW3a2wNbZHIuMZpTcgjGuLU/uBL/ubcZF9OXbDo8ff4O8yVp5Bf0efS8uEoYo5q4Fx7dY9OgQGXgAsQA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"concat-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/concat-map/-/concat-map-0.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/Srv4dswyQNBfohGpz9o6Yb3Gz3SrUDqBH5rTuhGR7ahtlbYKnVxw2bCFMRljaA7EXHaXZ8wsHdodFvbkhKmqg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"convert-source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/convert-source-map/-/convert-source-map-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Kvp459HrV2FEJ1CAsi1Ku+MY3kasH19TFykTz2xWmMeq6bk2NU3XXvfJ+Q61m0xktWwt+1HSYf3JZsTms3aRJg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"create-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/create-jest/-/create-jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Adz2bdH0Vq3F53KEMJOoftQFutWCukm6J24wbPWRO4k1kMY7gS7ds/uoJkNuV8wDCtWWnuwGcJwpWcih+zEW1Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"prompts\": \"^2.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"cross-spawn\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cross-spawn/-/cross-spawn-7.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-uV2QOWP2nWzsy2aMp8aRibhi9dlzF5Hgh5SHaB9OiTGEyDTiJJyx0uy51QXdyWbtAHNua4XJzUKca3OzKUd3vA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"path-key\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"shebang-command\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"which\": \"^2.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"debug\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/debug/-/debug-4.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6WTZ/IxCY/T6BALoZHaE4ctp9xm+Z5kY/pzYaCHRFeyVhojxlrm+46y68HA6hr0TcwEssoxNiDEUJQjfPZ/RYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"dedent\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/dedent/-/dedent-1.5.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NHQtfOOW68WD8lgypbLA5oT+Bt0xXJhiYvoR6SmmNXZfpzOGXwdKWmcwG8N7PwVVWV3eF/68nmD9BaJSsTBhyQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {}\n    },\n    \"deepmerge\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/deepmerge/-/deepmerge-4.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3sUqbMEc77XqpdNO7FRyRog+eW3ph+GYCbj+rK+uYyRMuwsVy0rMiVtPn+QJlKFvWP/1PYpapqYn0Me2knFn+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"detect-newline\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/detect-newline/-/detect-newline-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TLz+x/vEXm/Y7P7wn1EJFNLxYpUD4TgMosxY6fAVJUnJMbupHBOncxyWUG9OpTaH9EBD7uFI5LfEgmMOc54DsA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"diff-sequences\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/diff-sequences/-/diff-sequences-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-EjePK1srD3P08o2j4f0ExnylqRs5B9tJjcp9t1krH2qRi8CCdsYfwe9JgSLurFBWwq4uOlipzfk5fHNvwFKr8Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"electron-to-chromium\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.140\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/electron-to-chromium/-/electron-to-chromium-1.5.140.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-o82Rj+ONp4Ip7Cl1r7lrqx/pXhbp/lh9DpKcMNscFJdh8ebyRofnc7Sh01B4jx403RI0oqTBvlZ7OBIZLMr2+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"emittery\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.13.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/emittery/-/emittery-0.13.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DeWwawk6r5yR9jFgnDKYt4sLS0LmHJJi3ZOnb5/JdbYwj3nW+FxQnHIjhBKz8YLC7oRNPVM9NQ47I3CVx34eqQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"emoji-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/emoji-regex/-/emoji-regex-8.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MSjYzcWNOA0ewAHpz0MxpYFvwg6yjy1NG3xteoqz644VCo/RPgnr1/GGt+ic3iJTzQ8Eu3TdM14SawnVUmGE6A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"error-ex\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.3.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/error-ex/-/error-ex-1.3.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7dFHNmqeFSEt2ZBsCriorKnn3Z2pj+fd9kmI6QoWw4//DL+icEBfc0U7qJCisqrTsKTjw4fNFy2pW9OqStD84g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"escalade\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/escalade/-/escalade-3.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WUj2qlxaQtO4g6Pq5c29GTcWGDyd8itL8zTlipgECz3JesAiiOKotd8JU6otB3PACgG6xkJUyVhboMS+bje/jA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"escape-string-regexp\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/escape-string-regexp/-/escape-string-regexp-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UpzcLCXolUWcNu5HtVMHYdXJjArjsF9C0aNnquZYY4uW/Vu0miy5YoWvbV345HauVvcAUnpRuhMMcqTcGOY2+w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"esprima\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/esprima/-/esprima-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eGuFFw7Upda+g4p+QHvnW0RyTX/SVeJBDM/gCtMARO0cLuT2HcEKnTPvhjV6aGeqrCB/sbNop0Kszm0jsaWU4A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"execa\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/execa/-/execa-5.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-8uSpZZocAZRBAPIEINJj3Lo9HyGitllczc27Eh5YYojjMFMn8yHMDMaUHE2Jqfq05D/wucwI4JGURyXt1vchyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"cross-spawn\": \"^7.0.3\",\n        \"get-stream\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"human-signals\": \"^2.1.0\",\n        \"is-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"merge-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"npm-run-path\": \"^4.0.1\",\n        \"onetime\": \"^5.1.2\",\n        \"signal-exit\": \"^3.0.3\",\n        \"strip-final-newline\": \"^2.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"exit\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/exit/-/exit-0.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Zk/eNKV2zbjpKzrsQ+n1G6poVbErQxJ0LBOJXaKZ1EViLzH+hrLu9cdXI4zw9dBQJslwBEpbQ2P1oS7nDxs6jQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"expect\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/expect/-/expect-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2Zks0hf1VLFYI1kbh0I5jP3KHHyCHpkfyHBzsSXRFgl/Bg9mWYfMW8oD+PdMPlEwy5HNsR9JutYy6pMeOh61nw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/expect-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"fast-json-stable-stringify\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fast-json-stable-stringify/-/fast-json-stable-stringify-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lhd/wF+Lk98HZoTCtlVraHtfh5XYijIjalXck7saUtuanSDyLMxnHhSXEDJqHxD7msR8D0uCmqlkwjCV8xvwHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"fb-watchman\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fb-watchman/-/fb-watchman-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-p5161BqbuCaSnB8jIbzQHOlpgsPmK5rJVDfDKO91Axs5NC1uu3HRQm6wt9cd9/+GtQQIO53JdGXXoyDpTAsgYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"fill-range\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fill-range/-/fill-range-7.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-YsGpe3WHLK8ZYi4tWDg2Jy3ebRz2rXowDxnld4bkQB00cc/1Zw9AWnC0i9ztDJitivtQvaI9KaLyKrc+hBW0yg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"find-up\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/find-up/-/find-up-4.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-PpOwAdQ/YlXQ2vj8a3h8IipDuYRi3wceVQQGYWxNINccq40Anw7BlsEXCMbt1Zt+OLA6Fq9suIpIWD0OsnISlw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"locate-path\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"path-exists\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"fs.realpath\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fs.realpath/-/fs.realpath-1.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OO0pH2lK6a0hZnAdau5ItzHPI6pUlvI7jMVnxUQRtw4owF2wk8lOSabtGDCTP4Ggrg2MbGnWO9X8K1t4+fGMDw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"fsevents\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fsevents/-/fsevents-2.3.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-5xoDfX+fL7faATnagmWPpbFtwh/R77WmMMqqHGS65C3vvB0YHrgF+B1YmZ3441tMj5n63k0212XNoJwzlhffQw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"optional\": true\n    },\n    \"function-bind\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/function-bind/-/function-bind-1.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7XHNxH7qX9xG5mIwxkhumTox/MIRNcOgDrxWsMt2pAr23WHp6MrRlN7FBSFpCpr+oVO0F744iUgR82nJMfG2SA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"gensync\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0-beta.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/gensync/-/gensync-1.0.0-beta.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3hN7NaskYvMDLQY55gnW3NQ+mesEAepTqlg+VEbj7zzqEMBVNhzcGYYeqFo/TlYz6eQiFcp1HcsCZO+nGgS8zg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"get-caller-file\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-caller-file/-/get-caller-file-2.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DyFP3BM/3YHTQOCUL/w0OZHR0lpKeGrxotcHWcqNEdnltqFwXVfhEBQ94eIo34AfQpo0rGki4cyIiftY06h2Fg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"get-package-type\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-package-type/-/get-package-type-0.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pjzuKtY64GYfWizNAJ0fr9VqttZkNiK2iS430LtIHzjBEr6bX8Am2zm4sW4Ro5wjWW5cAlRL1qAMTcXbjNAO2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"get-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-stream/-/get-stream-6.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ts6Wi+2j3jQjqi70w5AlN8DFnkSwC+MqmxEzdEALB2qXZYV3X/b1CTfgPLGJNMeAWxdPfU8FO1ms3NUfaHCPYg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"glob\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/glob/-/glob-7.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-nFR0zLpU2YCaRxwoCJvL6UvCH2JFyFVIvwTLsIf21AuHlMskA1hhTdk+LlYJtOlYt9v6dvszD2BGRqBL+iQK9Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"fs.realpath\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"inflight\": \"^1.0.4\",\n        \"inherits\": \"2\",\n        \"minimatch\": \"^3.1.1\",\n        \"once\": \"^1.3.0\",\n        \"path-is-absolute\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"globals\": {\n      \"version\": \"11.12.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/globals/-/globals-11.12.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WOBp/EEGUiIsJSp7wcv/y6MO+lV9UoncWqxuFfm8eBwzWNgyfBd6Gz+IeKQ9jCmyhoH99g15M3T+QaVHFjizVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"graceful-fs\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.11\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/graceful-fs/-/graceful-fs-4.2.11.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RbJ5/jmFcNNCcDV5o9eTnBLJ/HszWV0P73bc+Ff4nS/rJj+YaS6IGyiOL0VoBYX+l1Wrl3k63h/KrH+nhJ0XvQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"has-flag\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/has-flag/-/has-flag-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-EykJT/Q1KjTWctppgIAgfSO0tKVuZUjhgMr17kqTumMl6Afv3EISleU7qZUzoXDFTAHTDC4NOoG/ZxU3EvlMPQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"hasown\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/hasown/-/hasown-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0hJU9SCPvmMzIBdZFqNPXWa6dqh7WdH0cII9y+CyS8rG3nL48Bclra9HmKhVVUHyPWNH5Y7xDwAB7bfgSjkUMQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"html-escaper\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/html-escaper/-/html-escaper-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-H2iMtd0I4Mt5eYiapRdIDjp+XzelXQ0tFE4JS7YFwFevXXMmOp9myNrUvCg0D6ws8iqkRPBfKHgbwig1SmlLfg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"human-signals\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/human-signals/-/human-signals-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-B4FFZ6q/T2jhhksgkbEW3HBvWIfDW85snkQgawt07S7J5QXTk6BkNV+0yAeZrM5QpMAdYlocGoljn0sJ/WQkFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"import-local\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/import-local/-/import-local-3.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2SPlun1JUPWoM6t3F0dw0FkCF/jWY8kttcY4f599GLTSjh2OCuuhdTkJQsEcZzBqbXZGKMK2OqW1oZsjtf/gQA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"imurmurhash\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/imurmurhash/-/imurmurhash-0.1.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JmXMZ6wuvDmLiHEml9ykzqO6lwFbof0GG4IkcGaENdCRDDmMVnny7s5HsIgHCbaq0w2MyPhDqkhTUgS2LU2PHA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"inflight\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/inflight/-/inflight-1.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-k92I/b08q4wvFscXCLvqfsHCrjrF7yiXsQuIVvVE7N82W3+aqpzuUdBbfhWcy/FZR3/4IgflMgKLOsvPDrGCJA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"inherits\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/inherits/-/inherits-2.0.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-k/vGaX4/Yla3WzyMCvTQOXYeIHvqOKtnqBduzTHpzpQZzAskKMhZ2K+EnBiSM9zGSoIFeMpXKxa4dYeZIQqewQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-arrayish\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-arrayish/-/is-arrayish-0.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zz06S8t0ozoDXMG+ube26zeCTNXcKIPJZJi8hBrF4idCLms4CG9QtK7qBl1boi5ODzFpjswb5JPmHCbMpjaYzg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-core-module\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.16.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-core-module/-/is-core-module-2.16.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UfoeMA6fIJ8wTYFEUjelnaGI67v6+N7qXJEvQuIGa99l4xsCruSYOVSQ0uPANn4dAzm8lkYPaKLrrijLq7x23w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"is-fullwidth-code-point\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-fullwidth-code-point/-/is-fullwidth-code-point-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zymm5+u+sCsSWyD9qNaejV3DFvhCKclKdizYaJUuHA83RLjb7nSuGnddCHGv0hk+KY7BMAlsWeK4Ueg6EV6XQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-generator-fn\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-generator-fn/-/is-generator-fn-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-cTIB4yPYL/Grw0EaSzASzg6bBy9gqCofvWN8okThAYIxKJZC+udlRAmGbM0XLeniEJSs8uEgHPGuHSe1XsOLSQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-number\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-number/-/is-number-7.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-41Cifkg6e8TylSpdtTpeLVMqvSBEVzTttHvERD741+pnZ8ANv0004MRL43QKPDlK9cGvNp6NZWZUBlbGXYxxng==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-stream/-/is-stream-2.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hFoiJiTl63nn+kstHGBtewWSKnQLpyb155KHheA1l39uvtO9nWIop1p3udqPcUd/xbF1VLMO4n7OI6p7RbngDg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"isexe\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/isexe/-/isexe-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RHxMLp9lnKHGHRng9QFhRCMbYAcVpn69smSGcq3f36xjgVVWThj4qqLbTLlq7Ssj8B+fIQ1EuCEGI2lKsyQeIw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-coverage/-/istanbul-lib-coverage-3.2.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-O8dpsF+r0WV/8MNRKfnmrtCWhuKjxrq2w+jpzBL5UZKTi2LeVWnWOmWRxFlesJONmc+wLAGvKQZEOanko0LFTg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-instrument/-/istanbul-lib-instrument-6.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Vtgk7L/R2JHyyGW07spoFlB8/lpjiOLTjMdms6AFMraYt3BaJauod/NGrfnVG/y4Ix1JEuMRPDPEj2ua+zz1/Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.23.9\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.23.9\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.3\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^7.5.4\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"semver\": {\n          \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"istanbul-lib-report\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-report/-/istanbul-lib-report-3.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GCfE1mtsHGOELCU8e/Z7YWzpmybrx/+dSTfLrvY8qRmaY6zXTKWn6WQIjaAFw069icm6GVMNkgu0NzI4iPZUNw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"make-dir\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^7.1.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"istanbul-lib-source-maps\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-source-maps/-/istanbul-lib-source-maps-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-n3s8EwkdFIJCG3BPKBYvskgXGoy88ARzvegkitk60NxRdwltLOTaH7CUiMRXvwYorl0Q712iEjcWB+fK/MrWVw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"debug\": \"^4.1.1\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"source-map\": \"^0.6.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"istanbul-reports\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-reports/-/istanbul-reports-3.1.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BewmUXImeuRk2YY0PVbxgKAysvhRPUQE0h5QRM++nVWyubKGV0l8qQ5op8+B2DOmwSe63Jivj0BjkPQVf8fP5g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"html-escaper\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-report\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest/-/jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NIy3oAFp9shda19hy4HK0HRTWKtPJmGdnvywu01nOqNC2vZg+Z+fvJDxpMQA88eb2I9EcafcdjYgsDthnYTvGw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/core\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"import-local\": \"^3.0.2\",\n        \"jest-cli\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-changed-files\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-changed-files/-/jest-changed-files-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fEArFiwf1BpQ+4bXSprcDc3/x4HSzL4al2tozwVpDFpsxALjLYdyiIK4e5Vz66GQJIbXJ82+35PtysofptNX2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"execa\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-circus\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-circus/-/jest-circus-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3E1nCMgipcTkCocFwM90XXQab9bS+GMsjdpmPrlelaxwD93Ad8iVEjX/vvHPdLPnFf+L40u+5+iutRdA1N9myw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"co\": \"^4.6.0\",\n        \"dedent\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"is-generator-fn\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"jest-each\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"pure-rand\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"stack-utils\": \"^2.0.3\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-cli\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-cli/-/jest-cli-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OVVobw2IubN/GSYsxETi+gOe7Ka59EFMR/twOU3Jb2GnKKeMGJB5SGUUrEz3SFVmJASUdZUzy83sLNNQ2gZslg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/core\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"create-jest\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"import-local\": \"^3.0.2\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"yargs\": \"^17.3.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-config\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-config/-/jest-config-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-uXbpfeQ7R6TZBqI3/TxCU4q4ttk3u0PJeC+E0zbfSoSjq6bJ7buBPxzQPL0ifrkY4DNu4JUdk0ImlBUYi840eQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@jest/test-sequencer\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-jest\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"deepmerge\": \"^4.2.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-circus\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-environment-node\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runner\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"parse-json\": \"^5.2.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-json-comments\": \"^3.1.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-diff\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-diff/-/jest-diff-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LMIgiIrhigmPrs03JHpxUh2yISK3vLFPkAodPeo0+BuF7wA2FoQbkEg1u8gBYBThncu7e1oEDUfIXVuTqLRUjw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"diff-sequences\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-docblock\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-docblock/-/jest-docblock-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-q617Auw3A612guyaFgsbFeYpNP5t2aoUNLwBUbc/0kD1R4t9ixDbyFTHd1nok4epoVFpr7PmeWHrhvuV3XaJ4g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"jest-each\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-each/-/jest-each-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gns+Er14+ZrEoC5fhOfYCY1LOHHr0TI+rQUHZS8Ttw2l7gl+80eHc/gFf2Ktkw0+SIACDTeWvpFcv3B04VembQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-environment-node\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-environment-node/-/jest-environment-node-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DOSwCRqXirTOyheM+4d5YZOrWcdu0LNZ87ewUoywbcb2XR4wKgqiG8vNeYwhjFMbEkfju7wx2GYH0P2gevGvFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-get-type\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-get-type/-/jest-get-type-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zrteXnqYxfQh7l5FHyL38jL39di8H8rHoecLH3JNxH3BwOrBsNeabdap5e0I23lD4HHI8W5VFBZqG4Eaq5LNcw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"jest-haste-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-haste-map/-/jest-haste-map-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fP8u2pyfqx0K1rGn1R9pyE0/KTn+G7PxktWidOBTqFPLYX0b9ksaMFkhK5vrS3DVun09pckLdlx90QthlW7AmA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/graceful-fs\": \"^4.1.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"anymatch\": \"^3.0.3\",\n        \"fb-watchman\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"fsevents\": \"^2.3.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"walker\": \"^1.0.8\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-leak-detector\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-leak-detector/-/jest-leak-detector-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kYA8IJcSYtST2BY9I+SMC32nDpBT3J2NvWJx8+JCuCdl/CR1I4EKUJROiP8XtCcxqgTTBGJNdbB1A8XRKbTetw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-matcher-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-matcher-utils/-/jest-matcher-utils-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-sBkD+Xi9DtcChsI3L3u0+N0opgPYnCRPtGcQYrgXmR+hmt/fYfWAL0xRXYU8eWOdfuLgBe0YCW3AFtnRLagq/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-diff\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-message-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-message-util/-/jest-message-util-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GBEV4GRADeP+qtB2+6u61stea8mGcOT4mCtrYISZwfu9/ISHFJ/5zOMXYbpBE9RsS5+Gb63DW4FgmnKJ79Kf6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.12.13\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/stack-utils\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"stack-utils\": \"^2.0.3\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-mock\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-mock/-/jest-mock-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ITOMZn+UkYS4ZFh83xYAOzWStloNzJFO2s8DWrE4lhtGD+AorgnbkiKERe4wQVBydIGPx059g6riW5Btp6Llnw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-pnp-resolver\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-pnp-resolver/-/jest-pnp-resolver-1.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+3NpwQEnRoIBtx4fyhblQDPgJI0H1IEIkX7ShLUjPGA7TtUTvI1oiKi3SR4oBR0hQhQR80l4WAe5RrXBwWMA8w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {}\n    },\n    \"jest-regex-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-regex-util/-/jest-regex-util-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KJJBsRCyyLNWCNBOvZyRDnAIfUiRJ8v+hOBQYGn8gDyF3UegwiP4gwRR3/SDa42g1YbVycTidUF3rKjyLFDWbg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"jest-resolve\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-resolve/-/jest-resolve-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-IOVhZSrg+UvVAshDSDtHyFCCBUl/Q3AAJv8iZ6ZjnZ74xzvwuzLXid9IIIPgTnY62SJjfuupMKZsZQRsCvxEgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-pnp-resolver\": \"^1.2.2\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"resolve\": \"^1.20.0\",\n        \"resolve.exports\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-resolve-dependencies\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-resolve-dependencies/-/jest-resolve-dependencies-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-un0zD/6qxJ+S0et7WxeI3H5XSe9lTBBR7bOHCHXkKR6luG5mwDDlIzVQ0V5cZCuoTgEdcdwzTghYkTWfubi+nA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-runner\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-runner/-/jest-runner-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fsc4N6cPCAahybGBfTRcq5wFR6fpLznMg47sY5aDpsoejOcVYFb07AHuSnR0liMcPTgBsA3ZJL6kFOjPdoNipQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"emittery\": \"^0.13.1\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-docblock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-environment-node\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-leak-detector\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-watcher\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"source-map-support\": \"0.5.13\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-runtime\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-runtime/-/jest-runtime-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gUnLjgwdGqW7B4LvOIkbKs9WGbn+QLqRQQ9juC6HndeDiezIwhDP+mhMwHWCEcfQ5RUXa6OPnFF8BJh5xegwwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/globals\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/source-map\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"cjs-module-lexer\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-bom\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-snapshot\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-snapshot/-/jest-snapshot-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Rm0BMWtxBcioHr1/OX5YCP8Uov4riHvKPknOGs804Zg9JGZgmIBkbtlxJC/7Z4msKYVbIJtfU+tKb8xlYNfdkw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@jest/expect-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-diff\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"natural-compare\": \"^1.4.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^7.5.3\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"semver\": {\n          \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-util/-/jest-util-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-z6EbKajIpqGKU56y5KBUgy1dt1ihhQJgWzUlZHArA/+X2ad7Cb5iF+AK1EWVL/Bo7Rz9uurpqw6SiBCefUbCGA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"picomatch\": \"^2.2.3\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-validate\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-validate/-/jest-validate-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ZB7wHqaRGVw/9hST/OuFUReG7M8vKeq0/J2egIGLdvjHCmYqGARhzXmtgi+gVeZ5uXFF219aOc3Ls2yLg27tkw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"camelcase\": \"^6.2.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"leven\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"camelcase\": {\n          \"version\": \"6.3.0\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/camelcase/-/camelcase-6.3.0.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-Gmy6FhYlCY7uOElZUSbxo2UCDH8owEk996gkbrpsgGtrJLM3J7jGxl9Ic7Qwwj4ivOE5AWZWRMecDdF7hqGjFA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-watcher\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-watcher/-/jest-watcher-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-49Fg7WXkU3Vl2h6LbLtMQ/HyB6rXSIX7SqvBLQmssRBGN9I0PNvPmAmCWSOY6SOvrjhI/F7/bGAv9RtnsPA03g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"ansi-escapes\": \"^4.2.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"emittery\": \"^0.13.1\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"string-length\": \"^4.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-worker\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-worker/-/jest-worker-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eIz2msL/EzL9UFTFFx7jBTkeZfku0yUAyZZZmJ93H2TYEiroIx2PQjEXcwYtYl8zXCxb+PAmA2hLIt/6ZEkPHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"merge-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^8.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"supports-color\": {\n          \"version\": \"8.1.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-color/-/supports-color-8.1.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-MpUEN2OodtUzxvKQl72cUF7RQ5EiHsGvSsVG0ia9c5RbWGL2CI4C7EpPS8UTBIplnlzZiNuV56w+FuNxy3ty2Q==\",\n          \"dev\": true,\n          \"requires\": \n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"js-tokens\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/js-tokens/-/js-tokens-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RdJUflcE3cUzKiMqQgsCu06FPu9UdIJO0beYbPhHN4k6apgJtifcoCtT9bcxOpYBtpD2kCM6Sbzg4CausW/PKQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"js-yaml\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.14.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/js-yaml/-/js-yaml-3.14.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-okMH7OXXJ7YrN9Ok3/SXrnu4iX9yOk+25nqX4imS2npuvTYDmo/QEZoqwZkYaIDk3jVvBOTOIEgEhaLOynBS9g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"jsesc\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jsesc/-/jsesc-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/sM3dO2FOzXjKQhJuo0Q173wf2KOo8t4I8vHy6lF9poUp7bKT0/NHE8fPX23PwfhnykfqnC2xRxOnVw5XuGIaA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"json-parse-even-better-errors\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/json-parse-even-better-errors/-/json-parse-even-better-errors-2.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xyFwyhro/JEof6Ghe2iz2NcXoj2sloNsWr/XsERDK/oiPCfaNhl5ONfp+jQdAZRQQ0IJWNzH9zIZF7li91kh2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"json5\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/json5/-/json5-2.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XmOWe7eyHYH14cLdVPoyg+GOH3rYX++KpzrylJwSW98t3Nk+U8XOl8FWKOgwtzdb8lXGf6zYwDUzeHMWfxasyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"kleur\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/kleur/-/kleur-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eTIzlVOSUR+JxdDFepEYcBMtZ9Qqdef+rnzWdRZuMbOywu5tO2w2N7rqjoANZ5k9vywhL6Br1VRjUIgTQx4E8w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"leven\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/leven/-/leven-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qsda+H8jTaUaN/x5vzW2rzc+8Rw4TAQ/4KjB46IwK5VH+IlVeeeje/EoZRpiXvIqjFgK84QffqPztGI3VBLG1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"lines-and-columns\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/lines-and-columns/-/lines-and-columns-1.2.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7ylylesZQ/PV29jhEDl3Ufjo6ZX7gCqJr5F7PKrqc93v7fzSymt1BpwEU8nAUXs8qzzvqhbjhK5QZg6Mt/HkBg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"locate-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/locate-path/-/locate-path-5.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-t7hw9pI+WvuwNJXwk5zVHpyhIqzg2qTlklJOf0mVxGSbe3Fp2VieZcduNYjaLDoy6p9uGpQEGWG87WpMKlNq8g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"lru-cache\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/lru-cache/-/lru-cache-5.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KpNARQA3Iwv+jTA0utUVVbrh+Jlrr1Fv0e56GGzAFOXN7dk/FviaDW8LHmK52DlcH4WP2n6gI8vN1aesBFgo9w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"make-dir\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/make-dir/-/make-dir-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hXdUTZYIVOt1Ex//jAQi+wTZZpUpwBj/0QsOzqegb3rGMMeJiSEu5xLHnYfBrRV4RH2+OCSOO95Is/7x1WJ4bw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": ,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"semver\": {\n          \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"makeerror\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.12\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/makeerror/-/makeerror-1.0.12.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JmqCvUhmt43madlpFzG4BQzG2Z3m6tvQDNKdClZnO3VbIudJYmxsT0FNJMeiB2+JTSlTQTSbU8QdesVmwJcmLg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"merge-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/merge-stream/-/merge-stream-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-abv/qOcuPfk3URPfDzmZU1LKmuw8kT+0nIHvKrKgFrwifol/doWcdA4ZqsWQ8ENrFKkd67Mfpo/LovbIUsbt3w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"micromatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/micromatch/-/micromatch-4.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-PXwfBhYu0hBCPw8Dn0E+WDYb7af3dSLVWKi3HGv84IdF4TyFoC0ysxFd0Goxw7nSv4T/PzEJQxsYsEiFCKo2BA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"mimic-fn\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/mimic-fn/-/mimic-fn-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OqbOk5oEQeAZ8WXWydlu9HJjz9WVdEIvamMCcXmuqUYjTknH/sqsWvhQ3vgwKFRR1HpjvNBKQ37nbJgYzGqGcg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"minimatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/minimatch/-/minimatch-3.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-J7p63hRiAjw1NDEww1W7i37+ByIrOWO5XQQAzZ3VOcL0PNybwpfmV/N05zFAzwQ9USyEcX6t3UO+K5aqBQOIHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"ms\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ms/-/ms-2.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6FlzubTLZG3J2a/NVCAleEhjzq5oxgHyaCU9yYXvcLsvoVaHJq/s5xXI6/XXP6tz7R9xAOtHnSO/tXtF3WRTlA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"natural-compare\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/natural-compare/-/natural-compare-1.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OWND8ei3VtNC9h7V60qff3SVobHr996CTwgxubgyQYEpg290h9J0buyECNNJexkFm5sOajh5G116RYA1c8ZMSw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node-int64\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/node-int64/-/node-int64-0.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-O5lz91xSOeoXP6DulyHfllpq+Eg00MWitZIbtPfoSEvqIHdl5gfcY6hYzDWnj0qD5tz52PI08u9qUvSVeUBeHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node-releases\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.19\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/node-releases/-/node-releases-2.0.19.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xxOWJsBKtzAq7DY0J+DTzuz58K8e7sJbdgwkbMWQe8UYB6ekmsQ45q0M/tJDsGaZmbC+l7n57UV8Hl5tHxO9uw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"normalize-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/normalize-path/-/normalize-path-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6eZs5Ls3WtCisHWp9S2GUy8dqkpGi4BVSz3GaqiE6ezub0512ESztXUwUB6C6IKbQkY2Pnb/mD4WYojCRwcwLA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"npm-run-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/npm-run-path/-/npm-run-path-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-S48WzZW777zhNIrn7gxOlISNAqi9ZC/uQFnRdbeIHhZhCA6UqpkOT8T1G7BvfdgP4Er8gF4sUbaS0i7QvIfCWw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"once\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/once/-/once-1.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lNaJgI+2Q5URQBkccEKHTQOPaXdUxnZZElQTZY0MFUAuaEqe1E+Nyvgdz/aIyNi6Z9MzO5dv1H8n58/GELp3+w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"onetime\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/onetime/-/onetime-5.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kbpaSSGJTWdAY5KPVeMOKXSrPtr8C8C7wodJbcsd51jRnmD+GZu8Y0VoU6Dm5Z4vWr0Ig/1NKuWRKf7j5aaYSg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"p-limit\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-limit/-/p-limit-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TYOanM3wGwNGsZN2cVTYPArw454xnXj5qmWF1bEoAc4+cU/ol7GVh7odevjp1FNHduHc3KZMcFduxU5Xc6uJRQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"p-locate\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-locate/-/p-locate-4.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R79ZZ/0wAxKGu3oYMlz8jy/kbhsNrS7SKZ7PxEHBgJ5+F2mtFW2fK2cOtBh1cHYkQsbzFV7I+EoRKe6Yt0oK7A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": ,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"p-limit\": {\n          \"version\": \"2.3.0\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-limit/-/p-limit-2.3.0.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-//88mFWSJx8lxCzwdAABTJL2MyWB12+eIY7MDL2SqLmAkeKU9qxRvWuSyTjm3FUmpBEMuFfckAIqEaVGUDxb6w==\",\n          \"dev\": true,\n          \"requires\": \n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"p-try\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-try/-/p-try-2.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R4nPAVTAU0B9D35/Gk3uJf/7XYbQcyohSKdvAxIRSNghFl4e71hVoGnBNQz9cWaXxO2I10KTC+3jMdvvoKw6dQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"parse-json\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/parse-json/-/parse-json-5.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ayCKvm/phCGxOkYRSCM82iDwct8/EonSEgCSxWxD7ve6jHggsFl4fZVQBPRNgQoKiuV/odhFrGzQXZwbifC8Rg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.0.0\",\n        \"error-ex\": \"^1.3.1\",\n        \"json-parse-even-better-errors\": \"^2.3.0\",\n        \"lines-and-columns\": \"^1.1.6\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"path-exists\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-exists/-/path-exists-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ak9Qy5Q7jYb2Wwcey5Fpvg2KoAc/ZIhLSLOSBmRmygPsGwkVVt0fZa0qrtMz+m6tJTAHfZQ8FnmB4MG4LWy7/w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"path-is-absolute\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-is-absolute/-/path-is-absolute-1.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-AVbw3UJ2e9bq64vSaS9Am0fje1Pa8pbGqTTsmXfaIiMpnr5DlDhfJOuLj9Sf95ZPVDAUerDfEk88MPmPe7UCQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"path-key\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-key/-/path-key-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ojmeN0qd+y0jszEtoY48r0Peq5dwMEkIlCOu6Q5f41lfkswXuKtYrhgoTpLnyIcHm24Uhqx+5Tqm2InSwLhE6Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"path-parse\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-parse/-/path-parse-1.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LDJzPVEEEPR+y48z93A0Ed0yXb8pAByGWo/k5YYdYgpY2/2EsOsksJrq7lOHxryrVOn1ejG6oAp8ahvOIQD8sw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"picocolors\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/picocolors/-/picocolors-1.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xceH2snhtb5M9liqDsmEw56le376mTZkEX/jEb/RxNFyegNul7eNslCXP9FDj/Lcu0X8KEyMceP2ntpaHrDEVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"picomatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/picomatch/-/picomatch-2.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JU3teHTNjmE2VCGFzuY8EXzCDVwEqB2a8fsIvwaStHhAWJEeVd1o1QD80CU6+ZdEXXSLbSsuLwJjkCBWqRQUVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"pirates\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pirates/-/pirates-4.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TfySrs/5nm8fQJDcBDuUng3VOUKsd7S+zqvbOTiGXHfxX4wK31ard+hoNuvkicM/2YFzlpDgABOevKSsB4G/FA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"pkg-dir\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pkg-dir/-/pkg-dir-4.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-HRDzbaKjC+AOWVXxAU/x54COGeIv9eb+6CkDSQoNTt4XyWoIJvuPsXizxu/Fr23EiekbtZwmh1IcIG/l/a10GQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"pretty-format\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pretty-format/-/pretty-format-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Pdlw/oPxN+aXdmM9R00JVC9WVFoCLTKJvDVLgmJ+qAffBMxsV85l/Lu7sNx4zSzPyoL2euImuEwHhOXdEgNFZQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/schemas\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"react-is\": \"^18.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": {\n          \"version\": \"5.2.0\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-styles/-/ansi-styles-5.2.0.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-Cxwpt2SfTzTtXcfOlzGEee8O+c+MmUgGrNiBcXnuWxuFJHe6a5Hz7qwhwe5OgaSYI0IJvkLqWX1ASG+cJOkEiA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"prompts\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.4.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/prompts/-/prompts-2.4.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NxNv/kLguCA7p3jE8oL2aEBsrJWgAakBpgmgK6lpPWV+WuOmY6r2/zbAVnP+T8bQlA0nzHXSJSJW0Hq7ylaD2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"pure-rand\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pure-rand/-/pure-rand-6.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bVWawvoZoBYpp6yIoQtQXHZjmz35RSVHnUOTefl8Vcjr8snTPY1wnpSPMWekcFwbxI6gtmT7rSYPFvz71ldiOA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"react-is\": {\n      \"version\": \"18.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/react-is/-/react-is-18.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/LLMVyas0ljjAtoYiPqYiL8VWXzUUdThrmU5+n20DZv+a+ClRoevUzw5JxU+Ieh5/c87ytoTBV9G1FiKfNJdmg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"require-directory\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/require-directory/-/require-directory-2.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fGxEI7+wsG9xrvdjsrlmL22OMTTiHRwAMroiEeMgq8gzoLC/PQr7RsRDSTLUg/bZAZtF+TVIkHc6/4RIKrui+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"resolve\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.22.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve/-/resolve-1.22.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NPRy+/ncIMeDlTAsuqwKIiferiawhefFJtkNSW0qZJEqMEb+qBt/77B/jGeeek+F0uOeN05CDa6HXbbIgtVX4w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"is-core-module\": \"^2.16.0\",\n        \"path-parse\": \"^1.0.7\",\n        \"supports-preserve-symlinks-flag\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"resolve-cwd\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve-cwd/-/resolve-cwd-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OrZaX2Mb+rJCpH/6CpSqt9xFVpN++x01XnN2ie9g6P5/3xelLAkXWVADpdz1IHD/KFfEXyE6V0U01OQ3UO2rEg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"resolve-from\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve-from/-/resolve-from-5.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qYg9KP24dD5qka9J47d0aVky0N+b4fTU89LN9iDnjB5waksiC49rvMB0PrUJQGoTmH50XPiqOvAjDfaijGxYZw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"resolve.exports\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve.exports/-/resolve.exports-2.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OcXjMsGdhL4XnbShKpAcSqPMzQoYkYyhbEaeSko47MjRP9NfEQMhZkXL1DoFlt9LWQn4YttrdnV6X2OiyzBi+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-6.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BR7VvDCVHO+q2xBEWskxS6DJE1qRnb7DxzUrogb71CWoSficBxYsiAGd+Kl0mmq/MprG9yArRkyrQxTO6XjMzA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"shebang-command\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/shebang-command/-/shebang-command-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kHxr2zZpYtdmrN1qDjrrX/Z1rR1kG8Dx+gkpK1G4eXmvXswmcE1hTWBWYUzlraYw1/yZp6YuDY77YtvbN0dmDA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"shebang-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/shebang-regex/-/shebang-regex-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7++dFhtcx3353uBaq8DDR4NuxBetBzC7ZQOhmTQInHEd6bSrXdiEyzCvG07Z44UYdLShWUyXt5M/yhz8ekcb1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"signal-exit\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/signal-exit/-/signal-exit-3.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wnD2ZE+l+SPC/uoS0vXeE9L1+0wuaMqKlfz9AMUo38JsyLSBWSFcHR1Rri62LZc12vLr1gb3jl7iwQhgwpAbGQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"sisteransi\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/sisteransi/-/sisteransi-1.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bLGGlR1QxBcynn2d5YmDX4MGjlZvy2MRBDRNHLJ8VI6l6+9FUiyTFNJ0IveOSP0bcXgVDPRcfGqA0pjaqUpfVg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"slash\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/slash/-/slash-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-g9Q1haeby36OSStwb4ntCGGGaKsaVSjQ68fBxoQcutl5fS1vuY18H3wSt3jFyFtrkx+Kz0V1G85A4MyAdDMi2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.6.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/source-map/-/source-map-0.6.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UjgapumWlbMhkBgzT7Ykc5YXUT46F0iKu8SGXq0bcwP5dz/h0Plj6enJqjz1Zbq2l5WaqYnrVbwWOWMyF3F47g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"source-map-support\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.5.13\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/source-map-support/-/source-map-support-0.5.13.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-SHSKFHadjVA5oR4PPqhtAVdcBWwRYVd6g6cAXnIbRiIwc2EhPrTuKUBdSLvlEKyIP3GCf89fltvcZiP9MMFA1w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"buffer-from\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"source-map\": \"^0.6.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"sprintf-js\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/sprintf-js/-/sprintf-js-1.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-D9cPgkvLlV3t3IzL0D0YLvGA9Ahk4PcvVwUbN0dSGr1aP0Nrt4AEnTUbuGvquEC0mA64Gqt1fzirlRs5ibXx8g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"stack-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/stack-utils/-/stack-utils-2.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XlkWvfIm6RmsWtNJx+uqtKLS8eqFbxUg0ZzLXqY0caEy9l7hruX8IpiDnjsLavoBgqCCR71TqWO8MaXYheJ3RQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"string-length\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/string-length/-/string-length-4.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+l6rNN5fYHNhZZy41RXsYptCjA2Igmq4EG7kZAYFQI1E1VTXarr6ZPXBg6eq7Y6eK4FEhY6AJlyuFIb/v/S0VQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"char-regex\": \"^1.0.2\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"string-width\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/string-width/-/string-width-4.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wKyQRQpjJ0sIp62ErSZdGsjMJWsap5oRNihHhu6G7JVO/9jIB6UyevL+tXuOqrng8j/cxKTWyWUwvSTriiZz/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"emoji-regex\": \"^8.0.0\",\n        \"is-fullwidth-code-point\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"strip-ansi\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-ansi/-/strip-ansi-6.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Y38VPSHcqkFrCpFnQ9vuSXmquuv5oXOKpGeT6aGrr3o3Gc9AlVa6JBfUSOCnbxGGZF+/0ooI7KrPuUSztUdU5A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"strip-bom\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-bom/-/strip-bom-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3xurFv5tEgii33Zi8Jtp55wEIILR9eh34FAW00PZf+JnSsTmV/ioewSgQl97JHvgjoRGwPShsWm+IdrxB35d0w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"strip-final-newline\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-final-newline/-/strip-final-newline-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BrpvfNAE3dcvq7ll3xVumzjKjZQ5tI1sEUIKr3Uoks0XUl45St3FlatVqef9prk4jRDzhW6WZg+3bk93y6pLjA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"strip-json-comments\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-json-comments/-/strip-json-comments-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6fPc+R4ihwqP6N/aIv2f1gMH8lOVtWQHoqC4yK6oSDVVocumAsfCqjkXnqiYMhmMwS/mEHLp7Vehlt3ql6lEig==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"supports-color\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-color/-/supports-color-7.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qpCAvRl9stuOHveKsn7HncJRvv501qIacKzQlO/+Lwxc9+0q2wLyv4Dfvt80/DPn2pqOBsJdDiogXGR9+OvwRw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"supports-preserve-symlinks-flag\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag/-/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag-1.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ot0WnXS9fgdkgIcePe6RHNk1WA8+muPa6cSjeR3V8K27q9BB1rTE3R1p7Hv0z1ZyAc8s6Vvv8DIyWf681MAt0w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"test-exclude\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/test-exclude/-/test-exclude-6.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-cAGWPIyOHU6zlmg88jwm7VRyXnMN7iV68OGAbYDk/Mh/xC/pzVPlQtY6ngoIH/5/tciuhGfvESU8GrHrcxD56w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.4\",\n        \"minimatch\": \"^3.0.4\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"tmpl\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/tmpl/-/tmpl-1.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3f0uOEAQwIqGuWW2MVzYg8fV/QNnc/IpuJNG837rLuczAaLVHslWHZQj4IGiEl5Hs3kkbhwL9Ab7Hrsmuj+Smw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"to-regex-range\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/to-regex-range/-/to-regex-range-5.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-65P7iz6X5yEr1cwcgvQxbbIw7Uk3gOy5dIdtZ4rDveLqhrdJP+Li/Hx6tyK0NEb+2GCyneCMJiGqrADCSNk8sQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"type-detect\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/type-detect/-/type-detect-4.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0fr/mIH1dlO+x7TlcMy+bIDqKPsw/70tVyeHW787goQjhmqaZe10uwLujubK9q9Lg6Fiho1KUKDYz0Z7k7g5/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"type-fest\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.21.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/type-fest/-/type-fest-0.21.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-t0rzBq87m3fVcduHDUFhKmyyX+9eo6WQjZvf51Ea/M0Q7+T374Jp1aUiyUl0GKxp8M/OETVHSDvmkyPgvX+X2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"undici-types\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.21.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/undici-types/-/undici-types-6.21.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iwDZqg0QAGrg9Rav5H4n0M64c3mkR59cJ6wQp+7C4nI0gsmExaedaYLNO44eT4AtBBwjbTiGPMlt2Md0T9H9JQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"update-browserslist-db\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/update-browserslist-db/-/update-browserslist-db-1.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UxhIZQ+QInVdunkDAaiazvvT/+fXL5Osr0JZlJulepYu6Jd7qJtDZjlur0emRlT71EN3ScPoE7gvsuIKKNavKw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"v8-to-istanbul\": {\n      \"version\": \"9.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/v8-to-istanbul/-/v8-to-istanbul-9.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kiGUalWN+rgBJ/1OHZsBtU4rXZOfj/7rKQxULKlIzwzQSvMJUUNgPwJEEh7gU6xEVxC0ahoOBvN2YI8GH6FNgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.12\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.1\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"walker\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/walker/-/walker-1.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ts/8E8l5b7kY0vlWLewOkDXMmPdLcVV4GmOQLyxuSswIJsweeFZtAsMF7k1Nszz+TYBQrlYRmzOnr398y1JemQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"which\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/which/-/which-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BLI3Tl1TW3Pvl70l3yq3Y64i+awpwXqsGBYWkkqMtnbXgrMD+yj7rhW0kuEDxzJaYXGjEW5ogapKNMEKNMjibA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"wrap-ansi\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/wrap-ansi/-/wrap-ansi-7.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-YVGIj2kamLSTxw6NsZjoBxfSwsn0ycdesmc4p+Q21c5zPuZ1pl+NfxVdxPtdHvmNVOQ6XSYG4AUtyt/Fi7D16Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"wrappy\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/wrappy/-/wrappy-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-l4Sp/DRseor9wL6EvV2+TuQn63dMkPjZ/sp9XkghTEbV9KlPS1xUsZ3u7/IQO4wxtcFB4bgpQPRcR3QCvezPcQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"write-file-atomic\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/write-file-atomic/-/write-file-atomic-4.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7KxauUdBmSdWnmpaGFg+ppNjKF8uNLry8LyzjauQDOVONfFLNKrKvQOxZ/VuTIcS/gge/YNahf5RIIQWTSarlg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"imurmurhash\": \"^0.1.4\",\n        \"signal-exit\": \"^3.0.7\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"y18n\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/y18n/-/y18n-5.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0pfFzegeDWJHJIAmTLRP2DwHjdF5s7jo9tuztdQxAhINCdvS+3nGINqPd00AphqJR/0LhANUS6/+7SCb98YOfA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"yallist\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yallist/-/yallist-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-a4UGQaWPH59mOXUYnAG2ewncQS4i4F43Tv3JoAM+s2VDAmS9NsK8GpDMLrCHPksFT7h3K6TOoUNn2pb7RoXx4g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"yargs\": {\n      \"version\": \"17.7.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yargs/-/yargs-17.7.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7dSzzRQ++CKnNI/krKnYRV7JKKPUXMEh61soaHKg9mrWEhzFWhFnxPxGl+69cD1Ou63C13NUPCnmIcrvqCuM6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"cliui\": \"^8.0.1\",\n        \"escalade\": \"^3.1.1\",\n        \"get-caller-file\": \"^2.0.5\",\n        \"require-directory\": \"^2.1.1\",\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.2.3\",\n        \"y18n\": \"^5.0.5\",\n        \"yargs-parser\": \"^21.1.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"yargs-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"21.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yargs-parser/-/yargs-parser-21.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tVpsJW7DdjecAiFpbIB1e3qxIQsE6NoPc5/eTdrbbIC4h0LVsWhnoa3g+m2HclBIujHzsxZ4VJVA+GUuc2/LBw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"yocto-queue\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yocto-queue/-/yocto-queue-0.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-rVksvsnNCdJ/ohGc6xgPwyN8eheCxsiLM8mxuE/t/mOVqJewPuO1miLpTHQiRgTKCLexL4MeAFVagts7HmNZ2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    }\n  }\n}\n","file":"package-lock.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() \n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"H\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"He\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hel\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hell\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello \")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello W\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello Wo\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello Wor\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello Worl\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello World\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello World\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  printl(\"Hello World\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  println(\"Hello World\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  l\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  le\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x =\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x = \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x = 5\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x = 5\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x = 5\n  i\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x = 5\n  in\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x = 5\n  int\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x = 5\n  int \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x = 5\n  int x\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x = 5\n  int x \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x = 5\n  int x =\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x = 5\n  int x = \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x = 5\n  int x \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x = 5\n  int x\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x = 5\n  int \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x = 5\n  int\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x = 5\n  in\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x = 5\n  i\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let x = 5\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let  = 5\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let i = 5\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let in = 5\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let int = 5\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let in= 5\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let i= 5\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let = 5\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let n= 5\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let nu= 5\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let num= 5\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let num= 5\n\n    \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let num= 5\n\n  l  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let num= 5\n\n  le  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let num= 5\n\n  let  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let num= 5\n\n  let   \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let num= 5\n\n  let s  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let num= 5\n\n  let w  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let num= 5\n\n  let wo  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let num= 5\n\n  let wor  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let num= 5\n\n  let word  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let num= 5\n\n  let word   \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let num= 5\n\n  let word =  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let num= 5\n\n  let word =   \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let num= 5\n\n  let wor =   \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let num= 5\n\n  let wor =    \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  t  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  ty  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typ  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof()  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof();  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  println(\"Hello World\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof();\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof(v);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof(va);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof(var);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof(vari);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof(varia);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof(variab);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof(variabl);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof(variable);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof(variable );\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  r\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  re\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  ret\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  retu\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  retur\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  return\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  return \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  return ()\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  return\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  return()\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  return(\"\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  return(\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  return(\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  return()\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  return(+)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  return(+\"\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"7:00:13 PM [info] Activating VS Code Recorder\n7:00:15 PM [info] Recording started\n","file":"extension-output-MattiaConsiglio.vs-code-recorder-#1-VS Code Recorder","language":"Log"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  println(\"Hello World\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  printl(\"Hello World\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  print(\"Hello World\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  println(\"Hello World\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"class Player {\n  // Create a Player class with properties:\n  // - health\n  // - weapon\n  // - speed\n  // - name\n  // - damage\n}\n\nfunction createPlayer(name, health, weapon, speed, damage) \n\nmodule.exports = ;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex7-player-class.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function simulateBattle(player1, player2) {\n  /* take two player objects and simulate them attacking each other\n   return an object with the updated health of both players after one round\n  example:  */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = simulateBattle;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex8-battle-simulation.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function createLyrics(songData) {\n  // Use template literals to create lyrics from the songData object\n  // The songData object will have properties like artist, title, verse, chorus\n  // Return the formatted lyrics string\n}\n\nmodule.exports = createLyrics;\n","file":"exercises/hard/ex5-template-lyrics.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof(variable);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  println(\"Hello World\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"7:00:13 PM [info] Activating VS Code Recorder\n7:00:15 PM [info] Recording started\n","file":"extension-output-MattiaConsiglio.vs-code-recorder-#1-VS Code Recorder","language":"Log"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"lockfileVersion\": 2,\n  \"requires\": true,\n  \"packages\": {\n    \"\": {\n      \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"license\": \"ISC\",\n      \"devDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@ampproject/remapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@ampproject/remapping/-/remapping-2.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-30iZtAPgz+LTIYoeivqYo853f02jBYSd5uGnGpkFV0M3xOt9aN73erkgYAmZU43x4VfqcnLxW9Kpg3R5LC4YYw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": \"^0.3.5\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.24\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/code-frame\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/code-frame/-/code-frame-7.26.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RJlIHRueQgwWitWgF8OdFYGZX328Ax5BCemNGlqHfplnRT9ESi8JkFlvaVYbS+UubVY6dpv87Fs2u5M29iNFVQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"js-tokens\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"picocolors\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/compat-data\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/compat-data/-/compat-data-7.26.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-oH5UPLMWR3L2wEFLnFJ1TZXqHufiTKAiLfqw5zkhS4dKXLJ10yVztfil/twG8EDTA4F/tvVNw9nOl4ZMslB8rQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/core\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/core/-/core-7.26.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-vMqyb7XCDMPvJFFOaT9kxtiRh42GwlZEg1/uIgtZshS5a/8OaduUfCi7kynKgc3Tw/6Uo2D+db9qBttghhmxwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@ampproject/remapping\": \"^2.2.0\",\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/helper-compilation-targets\": \"^7.26.5\",\n        \"@babel/helper-module-transforms\": \"^7.26.0\",\n        \"@babel/helpers\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.26.9\",\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"debug\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"gensync\": \"^1.0.0-beta.2\",\n        \"json5\": \"^2.2.3\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": {\n        \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n        \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/babel\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/generator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/generator/-/generator-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-VybsKvpiN1gU1sdMZIp7FcqphVVKEwcuj02x73uvcHE0PTihx1nlBcowYWhDwjpoAXRv43+gDzyggGnn1XZhVw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": \"^0.3.5\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.25\",\n        \"jsesc\": \"^3.0.2\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-compilation-targets\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-compilation-targets/-/helper-compilation-targets-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LVk7fbXml0H2xH34dFzKQ7TDZ2G4/rVTOrq9V+icbbadjbVxxeFeDsNHv2SrZeWoA+6ZiTyWYWtScEIW07EAcA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/compat-data\": \"^7.26.8\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-option\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"browserslist\": \"^4.24.0\",\n        \"lru-cache\": \"^5.1.1\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-module-imports\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-module-imports/-/helper-module-imports-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tnUA4RsrmflIM6W6RFTLFSXITtl0wKjgpnLgXyowocVPrbYrLUXSBXDgTs8BlbmIzIdlBySRQjINYs2BAkiLtw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-module-transforms\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-module-transforms/-/helper-module-transforms-7.26.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xO+xu6B5K2czEnQye6BHA7DolFFmS3LB7stHZFaOLb1pAwO1HWLS8fXA+eh0A2yIvltPVmx3eNNDBJA2SLHXFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-module-imports\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-plugin-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-plugin-utils/-/helper-plugin-utils-7.26.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RS+jZcRdZdRFzMyr+wcsaqOmld1/EqTghfaBGQQd/WnRdzdlvSZ//kF7U8VQTxf1ynZ4cjUcYgjVGx13ewNPMg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-string-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-string-parser/-/helper-string-parser-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-4A/SCr/2KLd5jrtOMFzaKjVtAei3+2r/NChoBNoZ3EyP/+GlhoaEGoWOZUmFmoITP7zOJyHIMm+DYRd8o3PvHA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-validator-identifier/-/helper-validator-identifier-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Ed61U6XJc3CVRfkERJWDz4dJwKe7iLmmJsbOGu9wSloNSFttHV0I8g6UAgb7qnK5ly5bGLPd4oXZlxCdANBOWQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-validator-option\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-validator-option/-/helper-validator-option-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-e/zv1co8pp55dNdEcCynfj9X7nyUKUXoUEwfXqaZt0omVOmDe9oOTdKStH4GmAw6zxMFs50ZayuMfHDKlO7Tfw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helpers\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helpers/-/helpers-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-U5eyP/CTFPuNE3qk+WZMxFkp/4zUzdceQlfzf7DdGdhp+Fezd7HD+i8Y24ZuTMKX3wQBld449jijbGq6OdGNQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/parser/-/parser-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iaepho73/2Pz7w2eMS0Q5f83+0RKI7i4xmiYeBmDzfRVbQtTOG7Ts0S4HzJVsTMGI9keU8rNfuZr8DKfSt7Yyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators/-/plugin-syntax-async-generators-7.8.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tycmZxkGfZaxhMRbXlPXuVFpdWlXpir2W4AMhSJgRKzk/eDlIXOhb2LHWoLpDF7TEHylV5zNhykX6KAgHJmTNw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint/-/plugin-syntax-bigint-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wnTnFlG+YxQm3vDxpGE57Pj0srRU4sHE/mDkt1qv2YJJSeUAec2ma4WLUnUPeKjyrfntVwe/N6dCXpU+zL3Npg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.12.13\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties/-/plugin-syntax-class-properties-7.12.13.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fm4idjKla0YahUNgFNLCB0qySdsoPiZP3iQE3rky0mBUtMZ23yDJ9SJdg6dXTSDnulOVqiF3Hgr9nbXvXTQZYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block/-/plugin-syntax-class-static-block-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-b+YyPmr6ldyNnM6sqYeMWE+bgJcJpO6yS4QD7ymxgH34GBPNDM/THBh8iunyvKIZztiwLH4CJZ0RxTk9emgpjw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes/-/plugin-syntax-import-attributes-7.26.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-e2dttdsJ1ZTpi3B9UYGLw41hifAubg19AtCu/2I/F1QNVclOBr1dYpTdmdyZ84Xiz43BS/tCUkMAZNLv12Pi+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta/-/plugin-syntax-import-meta-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Yqfm+XDx0+Prh3VSeEQCPU81yC+JWZ2pDPFSS4ZdpfZhp4MkFMaDC1UqseovEKwSUpnIL7+vK+Clp7bfh0iD7g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings/-/plugin-syntax-json-strings-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lY6kdGpWHvjoe2vk4WrAapEuBR69EMxZl+RoGRhrFGNYVK8mOPAW8VfbT/ZgrFbXlDNiiaxQnAtgVCZ6jv30EA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx/-/plugin-syntax-jsx-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ld6oezHQMZsZfp6pWtbjaNDF2tiiCYYDqQszHt5VV437lewP9aSi2Of99CK0D0XB21k7FLgnLcmQKyKzynfeAA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators/-/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-d8waShlpFDinQ5MtvGU9xDAOzKH47+FFoney2baFIoMr952hKOLp1HR7VszoZvOsV/4+RRszNY7D17ba0te0ig==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator/-/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-aSff4zPII1u2QD7y+F8oDsz19ew4IGEJg9SVW+bqwpwtfFleiQDMdzA/R+UlWDzfnHFCxxleFT0PMIrR36XLNQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator/-/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9H6YdfkcK/uOnY/K7/aA2xpzaAgkQn37yzWUMRK7OaPOqOpGS1+n0H5hxT9AUw9EsSjPW8SVyMJwYRtWs3X3ug==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread/-/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XoqMijGZb9y3y2XskN+P1wUGiVwWZ5JmoDRwx5+3GmEplNyVM2s2Dg8ILFQm8rWM48orGy5YpI5Bl8U1y7ydlA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding/-/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6VPD0Pc1lpTqw0aKoeRTMiB+kWhAoT24PA+ksWSBrFtl5SIRVpZlwN3NNPQjehA2E/91FV3RjLWoVTglWcSV3Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining/-/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KoK9ErH1MBlCPxV0VANkXW2/dw4vlbGDrFgz8bmUsBGYkFRcbRwMh6cIJubdPrkxRwuGdtCk0v/wPTKbQgBjkg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object/-/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0wVnp9dxJ72ZUJDV27ZfbSj6iHLoytYZmh3rFcxNnvsJF3ktkzLDZPy/mA17HGsaQT3/DQsWYX1f1QGWkCoVUg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await/-/plugin-syntax-top-level-await-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hx++upLv5U1rgYfwe1xBQUhRmU41NEvpUvrp8jkrSCdvGSnM5/qdRMtylJ6PG5OFkBaHkbTAKTnd3/YyESRHFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript/-/plugin-syntax-typescript-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hjMgRy5hb8uJJjUcdWunWVcoi9bGpJp8p5Ol1229PoN6aytsLwNMgmdftO23wnCLMfVmTwZDWMPNq/D1SY60JQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/template\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/template/-/template-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2ncevenBqXI6qRMukPlXwHKHchC7RyMuu4xv5JBXRfOGVcTy1mXCD12qrp7Jsoxll1EV3+9sE4GugBVRjT2jFA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/traverse\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/traverse/-/traverse-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-19lYZFzYVQkkHkl4Cy4WrAVcqBkgvV2YM2TU3xG6DIwO7O3ecbDPfW3yM3bjAGcqcQHi+CCtjMR3dIEHxsd6bA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"debug\": \"^4.3.1\",\n        \"globals\": \"^11.1.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/types\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/types/-/types-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-H45s8fVLYjbhFH62dIJ3WtmJ6RSPt/3DRO0ZcT2SUiYiQyz3BLVb9ADEnLl91m74aQPS3AzzeajZHYOalWe3bg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-string-parser\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@bcoe/v8-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@bcoe/v8-coverage/-/v8-coverage-0.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0hYQ8SB4Db5zvZB4axdMHGwEaQjkZzFjQiN9LVYvIFB2nSUHW9tYpxWriPrWDASIxiaXax83REcLxuSdnGPZtw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config/-/load-nyc-config-1.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-VjeHSlIzpv/NyD3N0YuHfXOPDIixcA1q2ZV98wsMqcYlPmv2n3Yb2lYP9XMElnaFVXg5A7YLTeLu6V84uQDjmQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"camelcase\": \"^5.3.1\",\n        \"find-up\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"get-package-type\": \"^0.1.0\",\n        \"js-yaml\": \"^3.13.1\",\n        \"resolve-from\": \"^5.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@istanbuljs/schema\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@istanbuljs/schema/-/schema-0.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ZXRY4jNvVgSVQ8DL3LTcakaAtXwTVUxE81hslsyD2AtoXW/wVob10HkOJ1X/pAlcI7D+2YoZKg5do8G/w6RYgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/console\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/console/-/console-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-5Ni4CU7XHQi32IJ398EEP4RrB8eV09sXP2ROqD4bksHrnTree52PsxvX8tpL8LvTZ3pFzXyPbNQReSN41CAhOg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/core\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/core/-/core-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-n7aeXWKMnGtDA48y8TLWJPJmLmmZ642Ceo78cYWEpiD7FzDgmNDV/GCVRorPABdXLJZ/9wzzgZAlHjXjxDHGsg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/reporters\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"ansi-escapes\": \"^4.2.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-changed-files\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-resolve-dependencies\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runner\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-watcher\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/environment\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/environment/-/environment-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-aQIfHDq33ExsN4jP1NWGXhxgQ/wixs60gDiKO+XVMd8Mn0NWPWgc34ZQDTb2jKaUWQ7MuwoitXAsN2XVXNMpAw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/expect\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/expect/-/expect-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-8uMeAMycttpva3P1lBHB8VciS9V0XAr3GymPpipdyQXbBcuhkLQOSe8E/p92RyAdToS6ZD1tFkX+CkhoECE0dQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/expect-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/expect-utils/-/expect-utils-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GlsNBWiFQFCVi9QVSx7f5AgMeLxe9YCCs5PuP2O2LdjDAA8Jh9eX7lA1Jq/xdXw3Wb3hyvlFNfZIfcRetSzYcA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/fake-timers\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/fake-timers/-/fake-timers-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-q4DH1Ha4TTFPdxLsqDXK1d3+ioSL7yL5oCMJZgDYm6i+6CygW5E5xVr/D1HdsGxjt1ZWSfUAs9OxSB/BNelWrQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@sinonjs/fake-timers\": \"^10.0.2\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/globals\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/globals/-/globals-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-mpiz3dutLbkW2MNFubUGUEVLkTGiqW6yLVTA+JbP6fI6J5iL9Y0Nlg8k95pcF8ctKwCS7WVxteBs29hhfAotzQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/reporters\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/reporters/-/reporters-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DApq0KJbJOEzAFYjHADNNxAE3KbhxQB1y5Kplb5Waqw6zVbuWatSnMjE5gs8FUgEPmNsnZA3NCWl9NG0ia04Pg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@bcoe/v8-coverage\": \"^0.2.3\",\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-report\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-source-maps\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-reports\": \"^3.1.3\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"string-length\": \"^4.0.1\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"v8-to-istanbul\": \"^9.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/schemas\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/schemas/-/schemas-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-mo5j5X+jIZmJQveBKeS/clAueipV7KgiX1vMgCxam1RNYiqE1w62n0/tJJnHtjW8ZHcQco5gY85jA3mi0L+nSA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/source-map/-/source-map-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MHjT95QuipcPrpLM+8JMSzFx6eHp5Bm+4XeFDJlwsvVBjmKNiIAvasGK2fxz2WbGRlnvqehFbh07MMa7n3YJnw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"callsites\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/test-result\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/test-result/-/test-result-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Fdx+tv6x1zlkJPcWXmMDAG2HBnaR9XPSd5aDWQVsfrZmLVT3lU1cwyxLgRmXR9yrq4NBoEm9BMsfgFzTQAbJYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/test-sequencer\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/test-sequencer/-/test-sequencer-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GQwJ5WZVrKnOJuiYiAF52UNUJXgTZx1NHjFSEB0qEMmSZKAkdMoIzw/Cj6x6NF4AvV23AUqDpFzQkN/eYCYTxw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/transform\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/transform/-/transform-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ok/BTPFzFKVMwO5eOHRrvnBVHdRy9IrsrW1GpMaQ9MCnilNLXQKmAX8s1YXDFaai9xJpac2ySzV0YeRRECr2Vw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": \"^6.1.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"fast-json-stable-stringify\": \"^2.1.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pirates\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"write-file-atomic\": \"^4.0.2\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/types\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/types/-/types-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-u3UPsIilWKOM3F9CXtrG8LEJmNxwoCQC/XVj4IKYXvvpx7QIi/Kg1LI5uDmDpKlac62NUtX7eLjRh+jVZcLOzw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/schemas\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-reports\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/yargs\": \"^17.0.8\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.3.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/gen-mapping/-/gen-mapping-0.3.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-imAbBGkb+ebQyxKgzv5Hu2nmROxoDOXHh80evxdoXNOrvAnVx7zimzc1Oo5h9RlfV4vPXaE2iM5pOFbvOCClWA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/set-array\": \"^1.2.1\",\n        \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": \"^1.4.10\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.24\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/resolve-uri\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/resolve-uri/-/resolve-uri-3.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bRISgCIjP20/tbWSPWMEi54QVPRZExkuD9lJL+UIxUKtwVJA8wW1Trb1jMs1RFXo1CBTNZ/5hpC9QvmKWdopKw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/set-array\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/set-array/-/set-array-1.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R8gLRTZeyp03ymzP/6Lil/28tGeGEzhx1q2k703KGWRAI1VdvPIXdG70VJc2pAMw3NA6JKL5hhFu1sJX0Mnn/A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec/-/sourcemap-codec-1.5.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gv3ZRaISU3fjPAgNsriBRqGWQL6quFx04YMPW/zD8XMLsU32mhCCbfbO6KZFLjvYpCZ8zyDEgqsgf+PwPaM7GQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.3.25\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/trace-mapping/-/trace-mapping-0.3.25.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-vNk6aEwybGtawWmy/PzwnGDOjCkLWSD2wqvjGGAgOAwCGWySYXfYoxt00IJkTF+8Lb57DwOb3Aa0o9CApepiYQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/resolve-uri\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": \"^1.4.14\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@sinclair/typebox\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.27.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinclair/typebox/-/typebox-0.27.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+Fj43pSMwJs4KRrH/938Uf+uAELIgVBmQzg/q1YG10djyfA3TnrU8N8XzqCh/okZdszqBQTZf96idMfE5lnwTA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@sinonjs/commons\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinonjs/commons/-/commons-3.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-K3mCHKQ9sVh8o1C9cxkwxaOmXoAMlDxC1mYyHrjqOWEcBjYr76t96zL2zlj5dUGZ3HSw240X1qgH3Mjf1yJWpQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@sinonjs/fake-timers\": {\n      \"version\": \"10.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinonjs/fake-timers/-/fake-timers-10.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-V4BG07kuYSUkTCSBHG8G8TNhM+F19jXFWnQtzj+we8DrkpSBCee9Z3Ms8yiGer/dlmhe35/Xdgyo3/0rQKg7YA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/babel__core\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.20.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__core/-/babel__core-7.20.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qoQprZvz5wQFJwMDqeseRXWv3rqMvhgpbXFfVyWhbx9X47POIA6i/+dXefEmZKoAgOaTdaIgNSMqMIU61yRyzA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.20.7\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.20.7\",\n        \"@types/babel__generator\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/babel__template\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/babel__traverse\": \"*\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/babel__generator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__generator/-/babel__generator-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ufFd2Xi92OAVPYsy+P4n7/U7e68fex0+Ee8gSG9KX7eo084CWiQ4sdxktvdl0bOPupXtVJPY19zk6EwWqUQ8lg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/babel__template\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.4.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__template/-/babel__template-7.4.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-h/NUaSyG5EyxBIp8YRxo4RMe2/qQgvyowRwVMzhYhBCONbW8PUsg4lkFMrhgZhUe5z3L3MiLDuvyJ/CaPa2A8A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.1.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/babel__traverse\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.20.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__traverse/-/babel__traverse-7.20.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-dkO5fhS7+/oos4ciWxyEyjWe48zmG6wbCheo/G2ZnHx4fs3EU6YC6UM8rk56gAjNJ9P3MTH2jo5jb92/K6wbng==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/graceful-fs\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/graceful-fs/-/graceful-fs-4.1.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-olP3sd1qOEe5dXTSaFvQG+02VdRXcdytWLAZsAq1PecU8uqQAhkrnbli7DagjtXKW/Bl7YJbUsa8MPcuc8LHEQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-lib-coverage/-/istanbul-lib-coverage-2.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2QF/t/auWm0lsy8XtKVPG19v3sSOQlJe/YHZgfjb/KBBHOGSV+J2q/S671rcq9uTBrLAXmZpqJiaQbMT+zNU1w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/istanbul-lib-report\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-lib-report/-/istanbul-lib-report-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NQn7AHQnk/RSLOxrBbGyJM/aVQ+pjj5HCgasFxc0K/KhoATfQ/47AyUl15I2yBUpihjmas+a+VJBOqecrFH+uA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/istanbul-reports\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-reports/-/istanbul-reports-3.0.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pk2B1NWalF9toCRu6gjBzR69syFjP4Od8WRAX+0mmf9lAjCRicLOWc+ZrxZHx/0XRjotgkF9t6iaMJ+aXcOdZQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/node\": {\n      \"version\": \"22.14.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/node/-/node-22.14.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-u0HuPQwe/dHrItgHHpmw3N2fYCR6x4ivMNbPHRkBVP4CvN+kiRrKHWk3i8tXiO/joPwXLMYvF9TTF0eqgHIuOw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/stack-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/stack-utils/-/stack-utils-2.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9aEbYZ3TbYMznPdcdr3SmIrLXwC/AKZXQeCf9Pgao5CKb8CyHuEX5jzWPTkvregvhRJHcpRO6BFoGW9ycaOkYw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/yargs\": {\n      \"version\": \"17.0.33\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/yargs/-/yargs-17.0.33.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WpxBCKWPLr4xSsHgz511rFJAM+wS28w2zEO1QDNY5zM/S8ok70NNfztH0xwhqKyaK0OHCbN98LDAZuy1ctxDkA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/yargs-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"21.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/yargs-parser/-/yargs-parser-21.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-I4q9QU9MQv4oEOz4tAHJtNz1cwuLxn2F3xcc2iV5WdqLPpUnj30aUuxt1mAxYTG+oe8CZMV/+6rU4S4gRDzqtQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/ansi-escapes\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-escapes/-/ansi-escapes-4.3.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gKXj5ALrKWQLsYG9jlTRmR/xKluxHV+Z9QEwNIgCfM1/uwPMCuzVVnh5mwTd+OuBZcwSIMbqssNWRm1lE51QaQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/ansi-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-regex/-/ansi-regex-5.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-quJQXlTSUGL2LH9SUXo8VwsY4soanhgo6LNSm84E1LBcE8s3O0wpdiRzyR9z/ZZJMlMWv37qOOb9pdJlMUEKFQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/ansi-styles\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-styles/-/ansi-styles-4.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zbB9rCJAT1rbjiVDb2hqKFHNYLxgtk8NURxZ3IZwD3F6NtxbXZQCnnSi1Lkx+IDohdPlFp222wVALIheZJQSEg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/anymatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/anymatch/-/anymatch-3.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KMReFUr0B4t+D+OBkjR3KYqvocp2XaSzO55UcB6mgQMd3KbcE+mWTyvVV7D/zsdEbNnV6acZUutkiHQXvTr1Rw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"normalize-path\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"picomatch\": \"^2.0.4\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/argparse\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/argparse/-/argparse-1.0.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-o5Roy6tNG4SL/FOkCAN6RzjiakZS25RLYFrcMttJqbdd8BWrnA+fGz57iN5Pb06pvBGvl5gQ0B48dJlslXvoTg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-jest/-/babel-jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BrvGY3xZSwEcCzKvKsCi2GgHqDqsYkOP4/by5xCgIwGXQxIEh+8ew3gmrE1y7XRR6LHZIj6yLYnUi/mm2KXKBg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@types/babel__core\": \"^7.1.14\",\n        \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": \"^6.1.1\",\n        \"babel-preset-jest\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-plugin-istanbul\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-plugin-istanbul/-/babel-plugin-istanbul-6.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Y1IQok9821cC9onCx5otgFfRm7Lm+I+wwxOx738M/WLPZ9Q42m4IG5W0FNX8WLL2gYMZo3JkuXIH2DOpWM+qwA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-plugin-utils\": \"^7.0.0\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": \"^5.0.4\",\n        \"test-exclude\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-plugin-istanbul/node_modules/istanbul-lib-instrument\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-instrument/-/istanbul-lib-instrument-5.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pzqtp31nLv/XFOzXGuvhCb8qhjmTVo5vjVk19XE4CRlSWz0KoeJ3bw9XsA7nOp9YBf4qHjwBxkDzKcME/J29Yg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.12.3\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.14.7\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-plugin-jest-hoist\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-plugin-jest-hoist/-/babel-plugin-jest-hoist-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ESAc/RJvGTFEzRwOTT4+lNDk/GNHMkKbNzsvT0qKRfDyyYTskxB5rnU2njIDYVxXCBHHEI1c0YwHob3WaYujOg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@types/babel__core\": \"^7.1.14\",\n        \"@types/babel__traverse\": \"^7.0.6\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-preset-current-node-syntax/-/babel-preset-current-node-syntax-1.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ldYss8SbBlWva1bs28q78Ju5Zq1F+8BrqBZZ0VFhLBvhh6lCpC2o3gDJi/5DRLs9FgYZCnmPYIVFU4lRXCkyUw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators\": \"^7.8.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties\": \"^7.12.13\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block\": \"^7.14.5\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes\": \"^7.24.7\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object\": \"^7.14.5\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await\": \"^7.14.5\"\n      },\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-preset-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-preset-jest/-/babel-preset-jest-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0B3bhxR6snWXJZtR/RliHTDPRgn1sNHOR0yVtq/IiQFyuOVjFS+wuio/R4gSNkyYmKmJB4wGZv2NZanmKmTnNA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"babel-plugin-jest-hoist\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/balanced-match\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/balanced-match/-/balanced-match-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3oSeUO0TMV67hN1AmbXsK4yaqU7tjiHlbxRDZOpH0KW9+CeX4bRAaX0Anxt0tx2MrpRpWwQaPwIlISEJhYU5Pw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/brace-expansion\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.11\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/brace-expansion/-/brace-expansion-1.1.11.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iCuPHDFgrHX7H2vEI/5xpz07zSHB00TpugqhmYtVmMO6518mCuRMoOYFldEBl0g187ufozdaHgWKcYFb61qGiA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"balanced-match\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"concat-map\": \"0.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/braces\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/braces/-/braces-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-yQbXgO/OSZVD2IsiLlro+7Hf6Q18EJrKSEsdoMzKePKXct3gvD8oLcOQdIzGupr5Fj+EDe8gO/lxc1BzfMpxvA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/browserslist\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.24.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/browserslist/-/browserslist-4.24.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KDi1Ny1gSePi1vm0q4oxSF8b4DR44GF4BbmS2YdhPLOEqd8pDviZOGH/GsmRwoWJ2+5Lr085X7naowMwKHDG1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n          \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"tidelift\",\n          \"url\": \"https://tidelift.com/funding/github/npm/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"github\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/ai\"\n        }\n      ],\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"caniuse-lite\": \"^1.0.30001688\",\n        \"electron-to-chromium\": \"^1.5.73\",\n        \"node-releases\": \"^2.0.19\",\n        \"update-browserslist-db\": \"^1.1.1\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": {\n        \"node\": \"^6 || ^7 || ^8 || ^9 || ^10 || ^11 || ^12 || >=13.7\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/bser\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/bser/-/bser-2.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gQxTNE/GAfIIrmHLUE3oJyp5FO6HRBfhjnw4/wMmA63ZGDJnWBmgY/lyQBpnDUkGmAhbSe39tx2d/iTOAfglwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/buffer-from\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/buffer-from/-/buffer-from-1.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-E+XQCRwSbaaiChtv6k6Dwgc+bx+Bs6vuKJHHl5kox/BaKbhiXzqQOwK4cO22yElGp2OCmjwVhT3HmxgyPGnJfQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/callsites\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/callsites/-/callsites-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-P8BjAsXvZS+VIDUI11hHCQEv74YT67YUi5JJFNWIqL235sBmjX4+qx9Muvls5ivyNENctx46xQLQ3aTuE7ssaQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/camelcase\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/camelcase/-/camelcase-5.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-L28STB170nwWS63UjtlEOE3dldQApaJXZkOI1uMFfzf3rRuPegHaHesyee+YxQ+W6SvRDQV6UrdOdRiR153wJg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/caniuse-lite\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.30001715\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/caniuse-lite/-/caniuse-lite-1.0.30001715.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7ptkFGMm2OAOgvZpwgA4yjQ5SQbrNVGdRjzH0pBdy1Fasvcr+KAeECmbCAECzTuDuoX0FCY8KzUxjf9+9kfZEw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n          \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"tidelift\",\n          \"url\": \"https://tidelift.com/funding/github/npm/caniuse-lite\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"github\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/ai\"\n        }\n      ]\n    },\n    \"node_modules/chalk\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/chalk/-/chalk-4.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-oKnbhFyRIXpUuez8iBMmyEa4nbj4IOQyuhc/wy9kY7/WVPcwIO9VA668Pu8RkO7+0G76SLROeyw9CpQ061i4mA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^7.1.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/char-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/char-regex/-/char-regex-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kWWXztvZ5SBQV+eRgKFeh8q5sLuZY2+8WUIzlxWVTg+oGwY14qylx1KbKzHd8P6ZYkAg0xyIDU9JMHhyJMZ1jw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/ci-info\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.9.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ci-info/-/ci-info-3.9.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NIxF55hv4nSqQswkAeiOi1r83xy8JldOFDTWiug55KBu9Jnblncd2U6ViHmYgHf01TPZS77NJBhBMKdWj9HQMQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"github\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/sibiraj-s\"\n        }\n      ],\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/cjs-module-lexer\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cjs-module-lexer/-/cjs-module-lexer-1.4.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9z8TZaGM1pfswYeXrUpzPrkx8UnWYdhJclsiYMm6x/w5+nN+8Tf/LnAgfLGQCm59qAOxU8WwHEq2vNwF6i4j+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/cliui\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cliui/-/cliui-8.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BSeNnyus75C4//NQ9gQt1/csTXyo/8Sb+afLAkzAptFuMsod9HFokGNudZpi/oQV73hnVK+sR+5PVRMd+Dr7YQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.2.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.1\",\n        \"wrap-ansi\": \"^7.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/co\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.6.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/co/-/co-4.6.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-QVb0dM5HvG+uaxitm8wONl7jltx8dqhfU33DcqtOZcLSVIKSDDLDi7+0LbAKiyI8hD9u42m2YxXSkMGWThaecQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/collect-v8-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/collect-v8-coverage/-/collect-v8-coverage-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lHl4d5/ONEbLlJvaJNtsF/Lz+WvB07u2ycqTYbdrq7UypDXailES4valYb2eWiJFxZlVmpGekfqoxQhzyFdT4Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/color-convert\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/color-convert/-/color-convert-2.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RRECPsj7iu/xb5oKYcsFHSppFNnsj/52OVTRKb4zP5onXwVF3zVmmToNcOfGC+CRDpfK/U584fMg38ZHCaElKQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/color-name\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/color-name/-/color-name-1.1.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-dOy+3AuW3a2wNbZHIuMZpTcgjGuLU/uBL/ubcZF9OXbDo8ff4O8yVp5Bf0efS8uEoYo5q4Fx7dY9OgQGXgAsQA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/concat-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/concat-map/-/concat-map-0.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/Srv4dswyQNBfohGpz9o6Yb3Gz3SrUDqBH5rTuhGR7ahtlbYKnVxw2bCFMRljaA7EXHaXZ8wsHdodFvbkhKmqg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/convert-source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/convert-source-map/-/convert-source-map-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Kvp459HrV2FEJ1CAsi1Ku+MY3kasH19TFykTz2xWmMeq6bk2NU3XXvfJ+Q61m0xktWwt+1HSYf3JZsTms3aRJg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/create-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/create-jest/-/create-jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Adz2bdH0Vq3F53KEMJOoftQFutWCukm6J24wbPWRO4k1kMY7gS7ds/uoJkNuV8wDCtWWnuwGcJwpWcih+zEW1Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"prompts\": \"^2.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/cross-spawn\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cross-spawn/-/cross-spawn-7.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-uV2QOWP2nWzsy2aMp8aRibhi9dlzF5Hgh5SHaB9OiTGEyDTiJJyx0uy51QXdyWbtAHNua4XJzUKca3OzKUd3vA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"path-key\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"shebang-command\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"which\": \"^2.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/debug\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/debug/-/debug-4.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6WTZ/IxCY/T6BALoZHaE4ctp9xm+Z5kY/pzYaCHRFeyVhojxlrm+46y68HA6hr0TcwEssoxNiDEUJQjfPZ/RYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/dedent\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/dedent/-/dedent-1.5.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NHQtfOOW68WD8lgypbLA5oT+Bt0xXJhiYvoR6SmmNXZfpzOGXwdKWmcwG8N7PwVVWV3eF/68nmD9BaJSsTBhyQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/deepmerge\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/deepmerge/-/deepmerge-4.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3sUqbMEc77XqpdNO7FRyRog+eW3ph+GYCbj+rK+uYyRMuwsVy0rMiVtPn+QJlKFvWP/1PYpapqYn0Me2knFn+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/detect-newline\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/detect-newline/-/detect-newline-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TLz+x/vEXm/Y7P7wn1EJFNLxYpUD4TgMosxY6fAVJUnJMbupHBOncxyWUG9OpTaH9EBD7uFI5LfEgmMOc54DsA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/diff-sequences\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/diff-sequences/-/diff-sequences-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-EjePK1srD3P08o2j4f0ExnylqRs5B9tJjcp9t1krH2qRi8CCdsYfwe9JgSLurFBWwq4uOlipzfk5fHNvwFKr8Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/electron-to-chromium\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.140\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/electron-to-chromium/-/electron-to-chromium-1.5.140.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-o82Rj+ONp4Ip7Cl1r7lrqx/pXhbp/lh9DpKcMNscFJdh8ebyRofnc7Sh01B4jx403RI0oqTBvlZ7OBIZLMr2+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/emittery\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.13.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/emittery/-/emittery-0.13.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DeWwawk6r5yR9jFgnDKYt4sLS0LmHJJi3ZOnb5/JdbYwj3nW+FxQnHIjhBKz8YLC7oRNPVM9NQ47I3CVx34eqQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": {\n        \"url\": \"https://github.com/sindresorhus/emittery?sponsor=1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/emoji-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/emoji-regex/-/emoji-regex-8.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MSjYzcWNOA0ewAHpz0MxpYFvwg6yjy1NG3xteoqz644VCo/RPgnr1/GGt+ic3iJTzQ8Eu3TdM14SawnVUmGE6A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/error-ex\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.3.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/error-ex/-/error-ex-1.3.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7dFHNmqeFSEt2ZBsCriorKnn3Z2pj+fd9kmI6QoWw4//DL+icEBfc0U7qJCisqrTsKTjw4fNFy2pW9OqStD84g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/escalade\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/escalade/-/escalade-3.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WUj2qlxaQtO4g6Pq5c29GTcWGDyd8itL8zTlipgECz3JesAiiOKotd8JU6otB3PACgG6xkJUyVhboMS+bje/jA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/escape-string-regexp\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/escape-string-regexp/-/escape-string-regexp-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UpzcLCXolUWcNu5HtVMHYdXJjArjsF9C0aNnquZYY4uW/Vu0miy5YoWvbV345HauVvcAUnpRuhMMcqTcGOY2+w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/esprima\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/esprima/-/esprima-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eGuFFw7Upda+g4p+QHvnW0RyTX/SVeJBDM/gCtMARO0cLuT2HcEKnTPvhjV6aGeqrCB/sbNop0Kszm0jsaWU4A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": {\n        \"esparse\": \"bin/esparse.js\",\n        \"esvalidate\": \"bin/esvalidate.js\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/execa\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/execa/-/execa-5.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-8uSpZZocAZRBAPIEINJj3Lo9HyGitllczc27Eh5YYojjMFMn8yHMDMaUHE2Jqfq05D/wucwI4JGURyXt1vchyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"cross-spawn\": \"^7.0.3\",\n        \"get-stream\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"human-signals\": \"^2.1.0\",\n        \"is-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"merge-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"npm-run-path\": \"^4.0.1\",\n        \"onetime\": \"^5.1.2\",\n        \"signal-exit\": \"^3.0.3\",\n        \"strip-final-newline\": \"^2.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/exit\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/exit/-/exit-0.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Zk/eNKV2zbjpKzrsQ+n1G6poVbErQxJ0LBOJXaKZ1EViLzH+hrLu9cdXI4zw9dBQJslwBEpbQ2P1oS7nDxs6jQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/expect\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/expect/-/expect-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2Zks0hf1VLFYI1kbh0I5jP3KHHyCHpkfyHBzsSXRFgl/Bg9mWYfMW8oD+PdMPlEwy5HNsR9JutYy6pMeOh61nw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/expect-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/fast-json-stable-stringify\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fast-json-stable-stringify/-/fast-json-stable-stringify-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lhd/wF+Lk98HZoTCtlVraHtfh5XYijIjalXck7saUtuanSDyLMxnHhSXEDJqHxD7msR8D0uCmqlkwjCV8xvwHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/fb-watchman\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fb-watchman/-/fb-watchman-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-p5161BqbuCaSnB8jIbzQHOlpgsPmK5rJVDfDKO91Axs5NC1uu3HRQm6wt9cd9/+GtQQIO53JdGXXoyDpTAsgYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/fill-range\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fill-range/-/fill-range-7.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-YsGpe3WHLK8ZYi4tWDg2Jy3ebRz2rXowDxnld4bkQB00cc/1Zw9AWnC0i9ztDJitivtQvaI9KaLyKrc+hBW0yg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/find-up\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/find-up/-/find-up-4.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-PpOwAdQ/YlXQ2vj8a3h8IipDuYRi3wceVQQGYWxNINccq40Anw7BlsEXCMbt1Zt+OLA6Fq9suIpIWD0OsnISlw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"locate-path\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"path-exists\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/fs.realpath\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fs.realpath/-/fs.realpath-1.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OO0pH2lK6a0hZnAdau5ItzHPI6pUlvI7jMVnxUQRtw4owF2wk8lOSabtGDCTP4Ggrg2MbGnWO9X8K1t4+fGMDw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/fsevents\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fsevents/-/fsevents-2.3.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-5xoDfX+fL7faATnagmWPpbFtwh/R77WmMMqqHGS65C3vvB0YHrgF+B1YmZ3441tMj5n63k0212XNoJwzlhffQw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"hasInstallScript\": true,\n      \"optional\": true,\n      \"os\": [\n        \"darwin\"\n      ],\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/function-bind\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/function-bind/-/function-bind-1.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7XHNxH7qX9xG5mIwxkhumTox/MIRNcOgDrxWsMt2pAr23WHp6MrRlN7FBSFpCpr+oVO0F744iUgR82nJMfG2SA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/gensync\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0-beta.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/gensync/-/gensync-1.0.0-beta.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3hN7NaskYvMDLQY55gnW3NQ+mesEAepTqlg+VEbj7zzqEMBVNhzcGYYeqFo/TlYz6eQiFcp1HcsCZO+nGgS8zg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/get-caller-file\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-caller-file/-/get-caller-file-2.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DyFP3BM/3YHTQOCUL/w0OZHR0lpKeGrxotcHWcqNEdnltqFwXVfhEBQ94eIo34AfQpo0rGki4cyIiftY06h2Fg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/get-package-type\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-package-type/-/get-package-type-0.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pjzuKtY64GYfWizNAJ0fr9VqttZkNiK2iS430LtIHzjBEr6bX8Am2zm4sW4Ro5wjWW5cAlRL1qAMTcXbjNAO2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/get-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-stream/-/get-stream-6.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ts6Wi+2j3jQjqi70w5AlN8DFnkSwC+MqmxEzdEALB2qXZYV3X/b1CTfgPLGJNMeAWxdPfU8FO1ms3NUfaHCPYg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/glob\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/glob/-/glob-7.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-nFR0zLpU2YCaRxwoCJvL6UvCH2JFyFVIvwTLsIf21AuHlMskA1hhTdk+LlYJtOlYt9v6dvszD2BGRqBL+iQK9Q==\",\n      \"deprecated\": \"Glob versions prior to v9 are no longer supported\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"fs.realpath\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"inflight\": \"^1.0.4\",\n        \"inherits\": \"2\",\n        \"minimatch\": \"^3.1.1\",\n        \"once\": \"^1.3.0\",\n        \"path-is-absolute\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/globals\": {\n      \"version\": \"11.12.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/globals/-/globals-11.12.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WOBp/EEGUiIsJSp7wcv/y6MO+lV9UoncWqxuFfm8eBwzWNgyfBd6Gz+IeKQ9jCmyhoH99g15M3T+QaVHFjizVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/graceful-fs\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.11\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/graceful-fs/-/graceful-fs-4.2.11.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RbJ5/jmFcNNCcDV5o9eTnBLJ/HszWV0P73bc+Ff4nS/rJj+YaS6IGyiOL0VoBYX+l1Wrl3k63h/KrH+nhJ0XvQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/has-flag\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/has-flag/-/has-flag-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-EykJT/Q1KjTWctppgIAgfSO0tKVuZUjhgMr17kqTumMl6Afv3EISleU7qZUzoXDFTAHTDC4NOoG/ZxU3EvlMPQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/hasown\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/hasown/-/hasown-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0hJU9SCPvmMzIBdZFqNPXWa6dqh7WdH0cII9y+CyS8rG3nL48Bclra9HmKhVVUHyPWNH5Y7xDwAB7bfgSjkUMQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/html-escaper\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/html-escaper/-/html-escaper-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-H2iMtd0I4Mt5eYiapRdIDjp+XzelXQ0tFE4JS7YFwFevXXMmOp9myNrUvCg0D6ws8iqkRPBfKHgbwig1SmlLfg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/human-signals\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/human-signals/-/human-signals-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-B4FFZ6q/T2jhhksgkbEW3HBvWIfDW85snkQgawt07S7J5QXTk6BkNV+0yAeZrM5QpMAdYlocGoljn0sJ/WQkFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/import-local\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/import-local/-/import-local-3.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2SPlun1JUPWoM6t3F0dw0FkCF/jWY8kttcY4f599GLTSjh2OCuuhdTkJQsEcZzBqbXZGKMK2OqW1oZsjtf/gQA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/imurmurhash\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/imurmurhash/-/imurmurhash-0.1.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JmXMZ6wuvDmLiHEml9ykzqO6lwFbof0GG4IkcGaENdCRDDmMVnny7s5HsIgHCbaq0w2MyPhDqkhTUgS2LU2PHA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/inflight\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/inflight/-/inflight-1.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-k92I/b08q4wvFscXCLvqfsHCrjrF7yiXsQuIVvVE7N82W3+aqpzuUdBbfhWcy/FZR3/4IgflMgKLOsvPDrGCJA==\",\n      \"deprecated\": \"This module is not supported, and leaks memory. Do not use it. Check out lru-cache if you want a good and tested way to coalesce async requests by a key value, which is much more comprehensive and powerful.\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/inherits\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/inherits/-/inherits-2.0.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-k/vGaX4/Yla3WzyMCvTQOXYeIHvqOKtnqBduzTHpzpQZzAskKMhZ2K+EnBiSM9zGSoIFeMpXKxa4dYeZIQqewQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-arrayish\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-arrayish/-/is-arrayish-0.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zz06S8t0ozoDXMG+ube26zeCTNXcKIPJZJi8hBrF4idCLms4CG9QtK7qBl1boi5ODzFpjswb5JPmHCbMpjaYzg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-core-module\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.16.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-core-module/-/is-core-module-2.16.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UfoeMA6fIJ8wTYFEUjelnaGI67v6+N7qXJEvQuIGa99l4xsCruSYOVSQ0uPANn4dAzm8lkYPaKLrrijLq7x23w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-fullwidth-code-point\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-fullwidth-code-point/-/is-fullwidth-code-point-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zymm5+u+sCsSWyD9qNaejV3DFvhCKclKdizYaJUuHA83RLjb7nSuGnddCHGv0hk+KY7BMAlsWeK4Ueg6EV6XQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-generator-fn\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-generator-fn/-/is-generator-fn-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-cTIB4yPYL/Grw0EaSzASzg6bBy9gqCofvWN8okThAYIxKJZC+udlRAmGbM0XLeniEJSs8uEgHPGuHSe1XsOLSQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-number\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-number/-/is-number-7.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-41Cifkg6e8TylSpdtTpeLVMqvSBEVzTttHvERD741+pnZ8ANv0004MRL43QKPDlK9cGvNp6NZWZUBlbGXYxxng==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-stream/-/is-stream-2.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hFoiJiTl63nn+kstHGBtewWSKnQLpyb155KHheA1l39uvtO9nWIop1p3udqPcUd/xbF1VLMO4n7OI6p7RbngDg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/isexe\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/isexe/-/isexe-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RHxMLp9lnKHGHRng9QFhRCMbYAcVpn69smSGcq3f36xjgVVWThj4qqLbTLlq7Ssj8B+fIQ1EuCEGI2lKsyQeIw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-coverage/-/istanbul-lib-coverage-3.2.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-O8dpsF+r0WV/8MNRKfnmrtCWhuKjxrq2w+jpzBL5UZKTi2LeVWnWOmWRxFlesJONmc+wLAGvKQZEOanko0LFTg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-instrument\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-instrument/-/istanbul-lib-instrument-6.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Vtgk7L/R2JHyyGW07spoFlB8/lpjiOLTjMdms6AFMraYt3BaJauod/NGrfnVG/y4Ix1JEuMRPDPEj2ua+zz1/Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.23.9\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.23.9\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.3\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^7.5.4\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-instrument/node_modules/semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-report\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-report/-/istanbul-lib-report-3.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GCfE1mtsHGOELCU8e/Z7YWzpmybrx/+dSTfLrvY8qRmaY6zXTKWn6WQIjaAFw069icm6GVMNkgu0NzI4iPZUNw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"make-dir\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^7.1.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-source-maps\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-source-maps/-/istanbul-lib-source-maps-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-n3s8EwkdFIJCG3BPKBYvskgXGoy88ARzvegkitk60NxRdwltLOTaH7CUiMRXvwYorl0Q712iEjcWB+fK/MrWVw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"debug\": \"^4.1.1\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"source-map\": \"^0.6.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-reports\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-reports/-/istanbul-reports-3.1.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BewmUXImeuRk2YY0PVbxgKAysvhRPUQE0h5QRM++nVWyubKGV0l8qQ5op8+B2DOmwSe63Jivj0BjkPQVf8fP5g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"html-escaper\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-report\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest/-/jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NIy3oAFp9shda19hy4HK0HRTWKtPJmGdnvywu01nOqNC2vZg+Z+fvJDxpMQA88eb2I9EcafcdjYgsDthnYTvGw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/core\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"import-local\": \"^3.0.2\",\n        \"jest-cli\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-changed-files\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-changed-files/-/jest-changed-files-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fEArFiwf1BpQ+4bXSprcDc3/x4HSzL4al2tozwVpDFpsxALjLYdyiIK4e5Vz66GQJIbXJ82+35PtysofptNX2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"execa\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-circus\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-circus/-/jest-circus-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3E1nCMgipcTkCocFwM90XXQab9bS+GMsjdpmPrlelaxwD93Ad8iVEjX/vvHPdLPnFf+L40u+5+iutRdA1N9myw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"co\": \"^4.6.0\",\n        \"dedent\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"is-generator-fn\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"jest-each\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"pure-rand\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"stack-utils\": \"^2.0.3\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-cli\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-cli/-/jest-cli-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OVVobw2IubN/GSYsxETi+gOe7Ka59EFMR/twOU3Jb2GnKKeMGJB5SGUUrEz3SFVmJASUdZUzy83sLNNQ2gZslg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/core\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"create-jest\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"import-local\": \"^3.0.2\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"yargs\": \"^17.3.1\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-config\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-config/-/jest-config-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-uXbpfeQ7R6TZBqI3/TxCU4q4ttk3u0PJeC+E0zbfSoSjq6bJ7buBPxzQPL0ifrkY4DNu4JUdk0ImlBUYi840eQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@jest/test-sequencer\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-jest\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"deepmerge\": \"^4.2.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-circus\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-environment-node\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runner\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"parse-json\": \"^5.2.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-json-comments\": \"^3.1.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": ,\n        \"ts-node\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-diff\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-diff/-/jest-diff-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LMIgiIrhigmPrs03JHpxUh2yISK3vLFPkAodPeo0+BuF7wA2FoQbkEg1u8gBYBThncu7e1oEDUfIXVuTqLRUjw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"diff-sequences\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-docblock\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-docblock/-/jest-docblock-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-q617Auw3A612guyaFgsbFeYpNP5t2aoUNLwBUbc/0kD1R4t9ixDbyFTHd1nok4epoVFpr7PmeWHrhvuV3XaJ4g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-each\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-each/-/jest-each-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gns+Er14+ZrEoC5fhOfYCY1LOHHr0TI+rQUHZS8Ttw2l7gl+80eHc/gFf2Ktkw0+SIACDTeWvpFcv3B04VembQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-environment-node\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-environment-node/-/jest-environment-node-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DOSwCRqXirTOyheM+4d5YZOrWcdu0LNZ87ewUoywbcb2XR4wKgqiG8vNeYwhjFMbEkfju7wx2GYH0P2gevGvFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-get-type\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-get-type/-/jest-get-type-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zrteXnqYxfQh7l5FHyL38jL39di8H8rHoecLH3JNxH3BwOrBsNeabdap5e0I23lD4HHI8W5VFBZqG4Eaq5LNcw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-haste-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-haste-map/-/jest-haste-map-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fP8u2pyfqx0K1rGn1R9pyE0/KTn+G7PxktWidOBTqFPLYX0b9ksaMFkhK5vrS3DVun09pckLdlx90QthlW7AmA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/graceful-fs\": \"^4.1.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"anymatch\": \"^3.0.3\",\n        \"fb-watchman\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"walker\": \"^1.0.8\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"optionalDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-leak-detector\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-leak-detector/-/jest-leak-detector-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kYA8IJcSYtST2BY9I+SMC32nDpBT3J2NvWJx8+JCuCdl/CR1I4EKUJROiP8XtCcxqgTTBGJNdbB1A8XRKbTetw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-matcher-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-matcher-utils/-/jest-matcher-utils-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-sBkD+Xi9DtcChsI3L3u0+N0opgPYnCRPtGcQYrgXmR+hmt/fYfWAL0xRXYU8eWOdfuLgBe0YCW3AFtnRLagq/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-diff\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-message-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-message-util/-/jest-message-util-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GBEV4GRADeP+qtB2+6u61stea8mGcOT4mCtrYISZwfu9/ISHFJ/5zOMXYbpBE9RsS5+Gb63DW4FgmnKJ79Kf6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.12.13\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/stack-utils\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"stack-utils\": \"^2.0.3\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-mock\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-mock/-/jest-mock-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ITOMZn+UkYS4ZFh83xYAOzWStloNzJFO2s8DWrE4lhtGD+AorgnbkiKERe4wQVBydIGPx059g6riW5Btp6Llnw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-pnp-resolver\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-pnp-resolver/-/jest-pnp-resolver-1.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+3NpwQEnRoIBtx4fyhblQDPgJI0H1IEIkX7ShLUjPGA7TtUTvI1oiKi3SR4oBR0hQhQR80l4WAe5RrXBwWMA8w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-regex-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-regex-util/-/jest-regex-util-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KJJBsRCyyLNWCNBOvZyRDnAIfUiRJ8v+hOBQYGn8gDyF3UegwiP4gwRR3/SDa42g1YbVycTidUF3rKjyLFDWbg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-resolve\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-resolve/-/jest-resolve-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-IOVhZSrg+UvVAshDSDtHyFCCBUl/Q3AAJv8iZ6ZjnZ74xzvwuzLXid9IIIPgTnY62SJjfuupMKZsZQRsCvxEgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-pnp-resolver\": \"^1.2.2\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"resolve\": \"^1.20.0\",\n        \"resolve.exports\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-resolve-dependencies\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-resolve-dependencies/-/jest-resolve-dependencies-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-un0zD/6qxJ+S0et7WxeI3H5XSe9lTBBR7bOHCHXkKR6luG5mwDDlIzVQ0V5cZCuoTgEdcdwzTghYkTWfubi+nA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-runner\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-runner/-/jest-runner-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fsc4N6cPCAahybGBfTRcq5wFR6fpLznMg47sY5aDpsoejOcVYFb07AHuSnR0liMcPTgBsA3ZJL6kFOjPdoNipQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"emittery\": \"^0.13.1\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-docblock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-environment-node\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-leak-detector\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-watcher\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"source-map-support\": \"0.5.13\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-runtime\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-runtime/-/jest-runtime-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gUnLjgwdGqW7B4LvOIkbKs9WGbn+QLqRQQ9juC6HndeDiezIwhDP+mhMwHWCEcfQ5RUXa6OPnFF8BJh5xegwwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/globals\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/source-map\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"cjs-module-lexer\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-bom\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-snapshot\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-snapshot/-/jest-snapshot-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Rm0BMWtxBcioHr1/OX5YCP8Uov4riHvKPknOGs804Zg9JGZgmIBkbtlxJC/7Z4msKYVbIJtfU+tKb8xlYNfdkw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@jest/expect-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-diff\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"natural-compare\": \"^1.4.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^7.5.3\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-snapshot/node_modules/semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-util/-/jest-util-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-z6EbKajIpqGKU56y5KBUgy1dt1ihhQJgWzUlZHArA/+X2ad7Cb5iF+AK1EWVL/Bo7Rz9uurpqw6SiBCefUbCGA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"picomatch\": \"^2.2.3\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-validate\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-validate/-/jest-validate-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ZB7wHqaRGVw/9hST/OuFUReG7M8vKeq0/J2egIGLdvjHCmYqGARhzXmtgi+gVeZ5uXFF219aOc3Ls2yLg27tkw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"camelcase\": \"^6.2.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"leven\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-validate/node_modules/camelcase\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/camelcase/-/camelcase-6.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Gmy6FhYlCY7uOElZUSbxo2UCDH8owEk996gkbrpsgGtrJLM3J7jGxl9Ic7Qwwj4ivOE5AWZWRMecDdF7hqGjFA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-watcher\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-watcher/-/jest-watcher-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-49Fg7WXkU3Vl2h6LbLtMQ/HyB6rXSIX7SqvBLQmssRBGN9I0PNvPmAmCWSOY6SOvrjhI/F7/bGAv9RtnsPA03g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"ansi-escapes\": \"^4.2.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"emittery\": \"^0.13.1\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"string-length\": \"^4.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-worker\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-worker/-/jest-worker-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eIz2msL/EzL9UFTFFx7jBTkeZfku0yUAyZZZmJ93H2TYEiroIx2PQjEXcwYtYl8zXCxb+PAmA2hLIt/6ZEkPHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"merge-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^8.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-worker/node_modules/supports-color\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-color/-/supports-color-8.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MpUEN2OodtUzxvKQl72cUF7RQ5EiHsGvSsVG0ia9c5RbWGL2CI4C7EpPS8UTBIplnlzZiNuV56w+FuNxy3ty2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/js-tokens\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/js-tokens/-/js-tokens-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RdJUflcE3cUzKiMqQgsCu06FPu9UdIJO0beYbPhHN4k6apgJtifcoCtT9bcxOpYBtpD2kCM6Sbzg4CausW/PKQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/js-yaml\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.14.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/js-yaml/-/js-yaml-3.14.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-okMH7OXXJ7YrN9Ok3/SXrnu4iX9yOk+25nqX4imS2npuvTYDmo/QEZoqwZkYaIDk3jVvBOTOIEgEhaLOynBS9g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jsesc\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jsesc/-/jsesc-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/sM3dO2FOzXjKQhJuo0Q173wf2KOo8t4I8vHy6lF9poUp7bKT0/NHE8fPX23PwfhnykfqnC2xRxOnVw5XuGIaA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/json-parse-even-better-errors\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/json-parse-even-better-errors/-/json-parse-even-better-errors-2.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xyFwyhro/JEof6Ghe2iz2NcXoj2sloNsWr/XsERDK/oiPCfaNhl5ONfp+jQdAZRQQ0IJWNzH9zIZF7li91kh2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/json5\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/json5/-/json5-2.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XmOWe7eyHYH14cLdVPoyg+GOH3rYX++KpzrylJwSW98t3Nk+U8XOl8FWKOgwtzdb8lXGf6zYwDUzeHMWfxasyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/kleur\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/kleur/-/kleur-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eTIzlVOSUR+JxdDFepEYcBMtZ9Qqdef+rnzWdRZuMbOywu5tO2w2N7rqjoANZ5k9vywhL6Br1VRjUIgTQx4E8w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/leven\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/leven/-/leven-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qsda+H8jTaUaN/x5vzW2rzc+8Rw4TAQ/4KjB46IwK5VH+IlVeeeje/EoZRpiXvIqjFgK84QffqPztGI3VBLG1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/lines-and-columns\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/lines-and-columns/-/lines-and-columns-1.2.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7ylylesZQ/PV29jhEDl3Ufjo6ZX7gCqJr5F7PKrqc93v7fzSymt1BpwEU8nAUXs8qzzvqhbjhK5QZg6Mt/HkBg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/locate-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/locate-path/-/locate-path-5.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-t7hw9pI+WvuwNJXwk5zVHpyhIqzg2qTlklJOf0mVxGSbe3Fp2VieZcduNYjaLDoy6p9uGpQEGWG87WpMKlNq8g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/lru-cache\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/lru-cache/-/lru-cache-5.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KpNARQA3Iwv+jTA0utUVVbrh+Jlrr1Fv0e56GGzAFOXN7dk/FviaDW8LHmK52DlcH4WP2n6gI8vN1aesBFgo9w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/make-dir\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/make-dir/-/make-dir-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hXdUTZYIVOt1Ex//jAQi+wTZZpUpwBj/0QsOzqegb3rGMMeJiSEu5xLHnYfBrRV4RH2+OCSOO95Is/7x1WJ4bw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/make-dir/node_modules/semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/makeerror\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.12\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/makeerror/-/makeerror-1.0.12.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JmqCvUhmt43madlpFzG4BQzG2Z3m6tvQDNKdClZnO3VbIudJYmxsT0FNJMeiB2+JTSlTQTSbU8QdesVmwJcmLg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/merge-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/merge-stream/-/merge-stream-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-abv/qOcuPfk3URPfDzmZU1LKmuw8kT+0nIHvKrKgFrwifol/doWcdA4ZqsWQ8ENrFKkd67Mfpo/LovbIUsbt3w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/micromatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/micromatch/-/micromatch-4.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-PXwfBhYu0hBCPw8Dn0E+WDYb7af3dSLVWKi3HGv84IdF4TyFoC0ysxFd0Goxw7nSv4T/PzEJQxsYsEiFCKo2BA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/mimic-fn\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/mimic-fn/-/mimic-fn-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OqbOk5oEQeAZ8WXWydlu9HJjz9WVdEIvamMCcXmuqUYjTknH/sqsWvhQ3vgwKFRR1HpjvNBKQ37nbJgYzGqGcg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/minimatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/minimatch/-/minimatch-3.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-J7p63hRiAjw1NDEww1W7i37+ByIrOWO5XQQAzZ3VOcL0PNybwpfmV/N05zFAzwQ9USyEcX6t3UO+K5aqBQOIHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/ms\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ms/-/ms-2.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6FlzubTLZG3J2a/NVCAleEhjzq5oxgHyaCU9yYXvcLsvoVaHJq/s5xXI6/XXP6tz7R9xAOtHnSO/tXtF3WRTlA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/natural-compare\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/natural-compare/-/natural-compare-1.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OWND8ei3VtNC9h7V60qff3SVobHr996CTwgxubgyQYEpg290h9J0buyECNNJexkFm5sOajh5G116RYA1c8ZMSw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/node-int64\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/node-int64/-/node-int64-0.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-O5lz91xSOeoXP6DulyHfllpq+Eg00MWitZIbtPfoSEvqIHdl5gfcY6hYzDWnj0qD5tz52PI08u9qUvSVeUBeHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/node-releases\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.19\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/node-releases/-/node-releases-2.0.19.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xxOWJsBKtzAq7DY0J+DTzuz58K8e7sJbdgwkbMWQe8UYB6ekmsQ45q0M/tJDsGaZmbC+l7n57UV8Hl5tHxO9uw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/normalize-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/normalize-path/-/normalize-path-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6eZs5Ls3WtCisHWp9S2GUy8dqkpGi4BVSz3GaqiE6ezub0512ESztXUwUB6C6IKbQkY2Pnb/mD4WYojCRwcwLA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/npm-run-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/npm-run-path/-/npm-run-path-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-S48WzZW777zhNIrn7gxOlISNAqi9ZC/uQFnRdbeIHhZhCA6UqpkOT8T1G7BvfdgP4Er8gF4sUbaS0i7QvIfCWw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/once\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/once/-/once-1.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lNaJgI+2Q5URQBkccEKHTQOPaXdUxnZZElQTZY0MFUAuaEqe1E+Nyvgdz/aIyNi6Z9MzO5dv1H8n58/GELp3+w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/onetime\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/onetime/-/onetime-5.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kbpaSSGJTWdAY5KPVeMOKXSrPtr8C8C7wodJbcsd51jRnmD+GZu8Y0VoU6Dm5Z4vWr0Ig/1NKuWRKf7j5aaYSg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/p-limit\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-limit/-/p-limit-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TYOanM3wGwNGsZN2cVTYPArw454xnXj5qmWF1bEoAc4+cU/ol7GVh7odevjp1FNHduHc3KZMcFduxU5Xc6uJRQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/p-locate\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-locate/-/p-locate-4.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R79ZZ/0wAxKGu3oYMlz8jy/kbhsNrS7SKZ7PxEHBgJ5+F2mtFW2fK2cOtBh1cHYkQsbzFV7I+EoRKe6Yt0oK7A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/p-locate/node_modules/p-limit\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-limit/-/p-limit-2.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-//88mFWSJx8lxCzwdAABTJL2MyWB12+eIY7MDL2SqLmAkeKU9qxRvWuSyTjm3FUmpBEMuFfckAIqEaVGUDxb6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/p-try\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-try/-/p-try-2.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R4nPAVTAU0B9D35/Gk3uJf/7XYbQcyohSKdvAxIRSNghFl4e71hVoGnBNQz9cWaXxO2I10KTC+3jMdvvoKw6dQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/parse-json\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/parse-json/-/parse-json-5.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ayCKvm/phCGxOkYRSCM82iDwct8/EonSEgCSxWxD7ve6jHggsFl4fZVQBPRNgQoKiuV/odhFrGzQXZwbifC8Rg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.0.0\",\n        \"error-ex\": \"^1.3.1\",\n        \"json-parse-even-better-errors\": \"^2.3.0\",\n        \"lines-and-columns\": \"^1.1.6\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/path-exists\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-exists/-/path-exists-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ak9Qy5Q7jYb2Wwcey5Fpvg2KoAc/ZIhLSLOSBmRmygPsGwkVVt0fZa0qrtMz+m6tJTAHfZQ8FnmB4MG4LWy7/w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/path-is-absolute\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-is-absolute/-/path-is-absolute-1.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-AVbw3UJ2e9bq64vSaS9Am0fje1Pa8pbGqTTsmXfaIiMpnr5DlDhfJOuLj9Sf95ZPVDAUerDfEk88MPmPe7UCQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/path-key\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-key/-/path-key-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ojmeN0qd+y0jszEtoY48r0Peq5dwMEkIlCOu6Q5f41lfkswXuKtYrhgoTpLnyIcHm24Uhqx+5Tqm2InSwLhE6Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/path-parse\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-parse/-/path-parse-1.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LDJzPVEEEPR+y48z93A0Ed0yXb8pAByGWo/k5YYdYgpY2/2EsOsksJrq7lOHxryrVOn1ejG6oAp8ahvOIQD8sw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/picocolors\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/picocolors/-/picocolors-1.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xceH2snhtb5M9liqDsmEw56le376mTZkEX/jEb/RxNFyegNul7eNslCXP9FDj/Lcu0X8KEyMceP2ntpaHrDEVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/picomatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/picomatch/-/picomatch-2.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JU3teHTNjmE2VCGFzuY8EXzCDVwEqB2a8fsIvwaStHhAWJEeVd1o1QD80CU6+ZdEXXSLbSsuLwJjkCBWqRQUVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pirates\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pirates/-/pirates-4.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TfySrs/5nm8fQJDcBDuUng3VOUKsd7S+zqvbOTiGXHfxX4wK31ard+hoNuvkicM/2YFzlpDgABOevKSsB4G/FA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pkg-dir\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pkg-dir/-/pkg-dir-4.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-HRDzbaKjC+AOWVXxAU/x54COGeIv9eb+6CkDSQoNTt4XyWoIJvuPsXizxu/Fr23EiekbtZwmh1IcIG/l/a10GQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pretty-format\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pretty-format/-/pretty-format-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Pdlw/oPxN+aXdmM9R00JVC9WVFoCLTKJvDVLgmJ+qAffBMxsV85l/Lu7sNx4zSzPyoL2euImuEwHhOXdEgNFZQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/schemas\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"react-is\": \"^18.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pretty-format/node_modules/ansi-styles\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-styles/-/ansi-styles-5.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Cxwpt2SfTzTtXcfOlzGEee8O+c+MmUgGrNiBcXnuWxuFJHe6a5Hz7qwhwe5OgaSYI0IJvkLqWX1ASG+cJOkEiA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/prompts\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.4.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/prompts/-/prompts-2.4.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NxNv/kLguCA7p3jE8oL2aEBsrJWgAakBpgmgK6lpPWV+WuOmY6r2/zbAVnP+T8bQlA0nzHXSJSJW0Hq7ylaD2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pure-rand\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pure-rand/-/pure-rand-6.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bVWawvoZoBYpp6yIoQtQXHZjmz35RSVHnUOTefl8Vcjr8snTPY1wnpSPMWekcFwbxI6gtmT7rSYPFvz71ldiOA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"individual\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/dubzzz\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n          \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/fast-check\"\n        }\n      ]\n    },\n    \"node_modules/react-is\": {\n      \"version\": \"18.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/react-is/-/react-is-18.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/LLMVyas0ljjAtoYiPqYiL8VWXzUUdThrmU5+n20DZv+a+ClRoevUzw5JxU+Ieh5/c87ytoTBV9G1FiKfNJdmg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/require-directory\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/require-directory/-/require-directory-2.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fGxEI7+wsG9xrvdjsrlmL22OMTTiHRwAMroiEeMgq8gzoLC/PQr7RsRDSTLUg/bZAZtF+TVIkHc6/4RIKrui+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/resolve\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.22.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve/-/resolve-1.22.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NPRy+/ncIMeDlTAsuqwKIiferiawhefFJtkNSW0qZJEqMEb+qBt/77B/jGeeek+F0uOeN05CDa6HXbbIgtVX4w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"is-core-module\": \"^2.16.0\",\n        \"path-parse\": \"^1.0.7\",\n        \"supports-preserve-symlinks-flag\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/resolve-cwd\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve-cwd/-/resolve-cwd-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OrZaX2Mb+rJCpH/6CpSqt9xFVpN++x01XnN2ie9g6P5/3xelLAkXWVADpdz1IHD/KFfEXyE6V0U01OQ3UO2rEg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/resolve-from\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve-from/-/resolve-from-5.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qYg9KP24dD5qka9J47d0aVky0N+b4fTU89LN9iDnjB5waksiC49rvMB0PrUJQGoTmH50XPiqOvAjDfaijGxYZw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/resolve.exports\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve.exports/-/resolve.exports-2.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OcXjMsGdhL4XnbShKpAcSqPMzQoYkYyhbEaeSko47MjRP9NfEQMhZkXL1DoFlt9LWQn4YttrdnV6X2OiyzBi+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-6.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BR7VvDCVHO+q2xBEWskxS6DJE1qRnb7DxzUrogb71CWoSficBxYsiAGd+Kl0mmq/MprG9yArRkyrQxTO6XjMzA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/shebang-command\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/shebang-command/-/shebang-command-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kHxr2zZpYtdmrN1qDjrrX/Z1rR1kG8Dx+gkpK1G4eXmvXswmcE1hTWBWYUzlraYw1/yZp6YuDY77YtvbN0dmDA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/shebang-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/shebang-regex/-/shebang-regex-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7++dFhtcx3353uBaq8DDR4NuxBetBzC7ZQOhmTQInHEd6bSrXdiEyzCvG07Z44UYdLShWUyXt5M/yhz8ekcb1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/signal-exit\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/signal-exit/-/signal-exit-3.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wnD2ZE+l+SPC/uoS0vXeE9L1+0wuaMqKlfz9AMUo38JsyLSBWSFcHR1Rri62LZc12vLr1gb3jl7iwQhgwpAbGQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/sisteransi\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/sisteransi/-/sisteransi-1.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bLGGlR1QxBcynn2d5YmDX4MGjlZvy2MRBDRNHLJ8VI6l6+9FUiyTFNJ0IveOSP0bcXgVDPRcfGqA0pjaqUpfVg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/slash\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/slash/-/slash-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-g9Q1haeby36OSStwb4ntCGGGaKsaVSjQ68fBxoQcutl5fS1vuY18H3wSt3jFyFtrkx+Kz0V1G85A4MyAdDMi2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.6.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/source-map/-/source-map-0.6.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UjgapumWlbMhkBgzT7Ykc5YXUT46F0iKu8SGXq0bcwP5dz/h0Plj6enJqjz1Zbq2l5WaqYnrVbwWOWMyF3F47g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/source-map-support\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.5.13\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/source-map-support/-/source-map-support-0.5.13.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-SHSKFHadjVA5oR4PPqhtAVdcBWwRYVd6g6cAXnIbRiIwc2EhPrTuKUBdSLvlEKyIP3GCf89fltvcZiP9MMFA1w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"buffer-from\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"source-map\": \"^0.6.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/sprintf-js\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/sprintf-js/-/sprintf-js-1.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-D9cPgkvLlV3t3IzL0D0YLvGA9Ahk4PcvVwUbN0dSGr1aP0Nrt4AEnTUbuGvquEC0mA64Gqt1fzirlRs5ibXx8g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/stack-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/stack-utils/-/stack-utils-2.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XlkWvfIm6RmsWtNJx+uqtKLS8eqFbxUg0ZzLXqY0caEy9l7hruX8IpiDnjsLavoBgqCCR71TqWO8MaXYheJ3RQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/string-length\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/string-length/-/string-length-4.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+l6rNN5fYHNhZZy41RXsYptCjA2Igmq4EG7kZAYFQI1E1VTXarr6ZPXBg6eq7Y6eK4FEhY6AJlyuFIb/v/S0VQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"char-regex\": \"^1.0.2\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/string-width\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/string-width/-/string-width-4.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wKyQRQpjJ0sIp62ErSZdGsjMJWsap5oRNihHhu6G7JVO/9jIB6UyevL+tXuOqrng8j/cxKTWyWUwvSTriiZz/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"emoji-regex\": \"^8.0.0\",\n        \"is-fullwidth-code-point\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/strip-ansi\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-ansi/-/strip-ansi-6.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Y38VPSHcqkFrCpFnQ9vuSXmquuv5oXOKpGeT6aGrr3o3Gc9AlVa6JBfUSOCnbxGGZF+/0ooI7KrPuUSztUdU5A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/strip-bom\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-bom/-/strip-bom-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3xurFv5tEgii33Zi8Jtp55wEIILR9eh34FAW00PZf+JnSsTmV/ioewSgQl97JHvgjoRGwPShsWm+IdrxB35d0w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/strip-final-newline\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-final-newline/-/strip-final-newline-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BrpvfNAE3dcvq7ll3xVumzjKjZQ5tI1sEUIKr3Uoks0XUl45St3FlatVqef9prk4jRDzhW6WZg+3bk93y6pLjA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/strip-json-comments\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-json-comments/-/strip-json-comments-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6fPc+R4ihwqP6N/aIv2f1gMH8lOVtWQHoqC4yK6oSDVVocumAsfCqjkXnqiYMhmMwS/mEHLp7Vehlt3ql6lEig==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/supports-color\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-color/-/supports-color-7.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qpCAvRl9stuOHveKsn7HncJRvv501qIacKzQlO/+Lwxc9+0q2wLyv4Dfvt80/DPn2pqOBsJdDiogXGR9+OvwRw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag/-/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag-1.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ot0WnXS9fgdkgIcePe6RHNk1WA8+muPa6cSjeR3V8K27q9BB1rTE3R1p7Hv0z1ZyAc8s6Vvv8DIyWf681MAt0w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/test-exclude\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/test-exclude/-/test-exclude-6.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-cAGWPIyOHU6zlmg88jwm7VRyXnMN7iV68OGAbYDk/Mh/xC/pzVPlQtY6ngoIH/5/tciuhGfvESU8GrHrcxD56w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.4\",\n        \"minimatch\": \"^3.0.4\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/tmpl\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/tmpl/-/tmpl-1.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3f0uOEAQwIqGuWW2MVzYg8fV/QNnc/IpuJNG837rLuczAaLVHslWHZQj4IGiEl5Hs3kkbhwL9Ab7Hrsmuj+Smw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/to-regex-range\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/to-regex-range/-/to-regex-range-5.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-65P7iz6X5yEr1cwcgvQxbbIw7Uk3gOy5dIdtZ4rDveLqhrdJP+Li/Hx6tyK0NEb+2GCyneCMJiGqrADCSNk8sQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/type-detect\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/type-detect/-/type-detect-4.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0fr/mIH1dlO+x7TlcMy+bIDqKPsw/70tVyeHW787goQjhmqaZe10uwLujubK9q9Lg6Fiho1KUKDYz0Z7k7g5/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/type-fest\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.21.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/type-fest/-/type-fest-0.21.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-t0rzBq87m3fVcduHDUFhKmyyX+9eo6WQjZvf51Ea/M0Q7+T374Jp1aUiyUl0GKxp8M/OETVHSDvmkyPgvX+X2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/undici-types\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.21.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/undici-types/-/undici-types-6.21.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iwDZqg0QAGrg9Rav5H4n0M64c3mkR59cJ6wQp+7C4nI0gsmExaedaYLNO44eT4AtBBwjbTiGPMlt2Md0T9H9JQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/update-browserslist-db\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/update-browserslist-db/-/update-browserslist-db-1.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UxhIZQ+QInVdunkDAaiazvvT/+fXL5Osr0JZlJulepYu6Jd7qJtDZjlur0emRlT71EN3ScPoE7gvsuIKKNavKw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n          \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"tidelift\",\n          \"url\": \"https://tidelift.com/funding/github/npm/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"github\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/ai\"\n        }\n      ],\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/v8-to-istanbul\": {\n      \"version\": \"9.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/v8-to-istanbul/-/v8-to-istanbul-9.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kiGUalWN+rgBJ/1OHZsBtU4rXZOfj/7rKQxULKlIzwzQSvMJUUNgPwJEEh7gU6xEVxC0ahoOBvN2YI8GH6FNgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.12\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.1\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/walker\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/walker/-/walker-1.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ts/8E8l5b7kY0vlWLewOkDXMmPdLcVV4GmOQLyxuSswIJsweeFZtAsMF7k1Nszz+TYBQrlYRmzOnr398y1JemQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/which\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/which/-/which-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BLI3Tl1TW3Pvl70l3yq3Y64i+awpwXqsGBYWkkqMtnbXgrMD+yj7rhW0kuEDxzJaYXGjEW5ogapKNMEKNMjibA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/wrap-ansi\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/wrap-ansi/-/wrap-ansi-7.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-YVGIj2kamLSTxw6NsZjoBxfSwsn0ycdesmc4p+Q21c5zPuZ1pl+NfxVdxPtdHvmNVOQ6XSYG4AUtyt/Fi7D16Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/wrappy\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/wrappy/-/wrappy-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-l4Sp/DRseor9wL6EvV2+TuQn63dMkPjZ/sp9XkghTEbV9KlPS1xUsZ3u7/IQO4wxtcFB4bgpQPRcR3QCvezPcQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/write-file-atomic\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/write-file-atomic/-/write-file-atomic-4.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7KxauUdBmSdWnmpaGFg+ppNjKF8uNLry8LyzjauQDOVONfFLNKrKvQOxZ/VuTIcS/gge/YNahf5RIIQWTSarlg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"imurmurhash\": \"^0.1.4\",\n        \"signal-exit\": \"^3.0.7\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/y18n\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/y18n/-/y18n-5.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0pfFzegeDWJHJIAmTLRP2DwHjdF5s7jo9tuztdQxAhINCdvS+3nGINqPd00AphqJR/0LhANUS6/+7SCb98YOfA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/yallist\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yallist/-/yallist-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-a4UGQaWPH59mOXUYnAG2ewncQS4i4F43Tv3JoAM+s2VDAmS9NsK8GpDMLrCHPksFT7h3K6TOoUNn2pb7RoXx4g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/yargs\": {\n      \"version\": \"17.7.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yargs/-/yargs-17.7.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7dSzzRQ++CKnNI/krKnYRV7JKKPUXMEh61soaHKg9mrWEhzFWhFnxPxGl+69cD1Ou63C13NUPCnmIcrvqCuM6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"cliui\": \"^8.0.1\",\n        \"escalade\": \"^3.1.1\",\n        \"get-caller-file\": \"^2.0.5\",\n        \"require-directory\": \"^2.1.1\",\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.2.3\",\n        \"y18n\": \"^5.0.5\",\n        \"yargs-parser\": \"^21.1.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/yargs-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"21.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yargs-parser/-/yargs-parser-21.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tVpsJW7DdjecAiFpbIB1e3qxIQsE6NoPc5/eTdrbbIC4h0LVsWhnoa3g+m2HclBIujHzsxZ4VJVA+GUuc2/LBw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/yocto-queue\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yocto-queue/-/yocto-queue-0.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-rVksvsnNCdJ/ohGc6xgPwyN8eheCxsiLM8mxuE/t/mOVqJewPuO1miLpTHQiRgTKCLexL4MeAFVagts7HmNZ2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    }\n  },\n  \"dependencies\": {\n    \"@ampproject/remapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@ampproject/remapping/-/remapping-2.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-30iZtAPgz+LTIYoeivqYo853f02jBYSd5uGnGpkFV0M3xOt9aN73erkgYAmZU43x4VfqcnLxW9Kpg3R5LC4YYw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": \"^0.3.5\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.24\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/code-frame\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/code-frame/-/code-frame-7.26.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RJlIHRueQgwWitWgF8OdFYGZX328Ax5BCemNGlqHfplnRT9ESi8JkFlvaVYbS+UubVY6dpv87Fs2u5M29iNFVQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"js-tokens\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"picocolors\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/compat-data\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/compat-data/-/compat-data-7.26.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-oH5UPLMWR3L2wEFLnFJ1TZXqHufiTKAiLfqw5zkhS4dKXLJ10yVztfil/twG8EDTA4F/tvVNw9nOl4ZMslB8rQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/core\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/core/-/core-7.26.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-vMqyb7XCDMPvJFFOaT9kxtiRh42GwlZEg1/uIgtZshS5a/8OaduUfCi7kynKgc3Tw/6Uo2D+db9qBttghhmxwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@ampproject/remapping\": \"^2.2.0\",\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/helper-compilation-targets\": \"^7.26.5\",\n        \"@babel/helper-module-transforms\": \"^7.26.0\",\n        \"@babel/helpers\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.26.9\",\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"debug\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"gensync\": \"^1.0.0-beta.2\",\n        \"json5\": \"^2.2.3\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/generator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/generator/-/generator-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-VybsKvpiN1gU1sdMZIp7FcqphVVKEwcuj02x73uvcHE0PTihx1nlBcowYWhDwjpoAXRv43+gDzyggGnn1XZhVw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": \"^0.3.5\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.25\",\n        \"jsesc\": \"^3.0.2\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-compilation-targets\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-compilation-targets/-/helper-compilation-targets-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LVk7fbXml0H2xH34dFzKQ7TDZ2G4/rVTOrq9V+icbbadjbVxxeFeDsNHv2SrZeWoA+6ZiTyWYWtScEIW07EAcA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/compat-data\": \"^7.26.8\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-option\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"browserslist\": \"^4.24.0\",\n        \"lru-cache\": \"^5.1.1\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-module-imports\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-module-imports/-/helper-module-imports-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tnUA4RsrmflIM6W6RFTLFSXITtl0wKjgpnLgXyowocVPrbYrLUXSBXDgTs8BlbmIzIdlBySRQjINYs2BAkiLtw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-module-transforms\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-module-transforms/-/helper-module-transforms-7.26.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xO+xu6B5K2czEnQye6BHA7DolFFmS3LB7stHZFaOLb1pAwO1HWLS8fXA+eh0A2yIvltPVmx3eNNDBJA2SLHXFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-module-imports\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-plugin-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-plugin-utils/-/helper-plugin-utils-7.26.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RS+jZcRdZdRFzMyr+wcsaqOmld1/EqTghfaBGQQd/WnRdzdlvSZ//kF7U8VQTxf1ynZ4cjUcYgjVGx13ewNPMg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-string-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-string-parser/-/helper-string-parser-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-4A/SCr/2KLd5jrtOMFzaKjVtAei3+2r/NChoBNoZ3EyP/+GlhoaEGoWOZUmFmoITP7zOJyHIMm+DYRd8o3PvHA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-validator-identifier/-/helper-validator-identifier-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Ed61U6XJc3CVRfkERJWDz4dJwKe7iLmmJsbOGu9wSloNSFttHV0I8g6UAgb7qnK5ly5bGLPd4oXZlxCdANBOWQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-validator-option\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-validator-option/-/helper-validator-option-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-e/zv1co8pp55dNdEcCynfj9X7nyUKUXoUEwfXqaZt0omVOmDe9oOTdKStH4GmAw6zxMFs50ZayuMfHDKlO7Tfw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/helpers\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helpers/-/helpers-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-U5eyP/CTFPuNE3qk+WZMxFkp/4zUzdceQlfzf7DdGdhp+Fezd7HD+i8Y24ZuTMKX3wQBld449jijbGq6OdGNQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/parser/-/parser-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iaepho73/2Pz7w2eMS0Q5f83+0RKI7i4xmiYeBmDzfRVbQtTOG7Ts0S4HzJVsTMGI9keU8rNfuZr8DKfSt7Yyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators/-/plugin-syntax-async-generators-7.8.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tycmZxkGfZaxhMRbXlPXuVFpdWlXpir2W4AMhSJgRKzk/eDlIXOhb2LHWoLpDF7TEHylV5zNhykX6KAgHJmTNw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint/-/plugin-syntax-bigint-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wnTnFlG+YxQm3vDxpGE57Pj0srRU4sHE/mDkt1qv2YJJSeUAec2ma4WLUnUPeKjyrfntVwe/N6dCXpU+zL3Npg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.12.13\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties/-/plugin-syntax-class-properties-7.12.13.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fm4idjKla0YahUNgFNLCB0qySdsoPiZP3iQE3rky0mBUtMZ23yDJ9SJdg6dXTSDnulOVqiF3Hgr9nbXvXTQZYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block/-/plugin-syntax-class-static-block-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-b+YyPmr6ldyNnM6sqYeMWE+bgJcJpO6yS4QD7ymxgH34GBPNDM/THBh8iunyvKIZztiwLH4CJZ0RxTk9emgpjw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes/-/plugin-syntax-import-attributes-7.26.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-e2dttdsJ1ZTpi3B9UYGLw41hifAubg19AtCu/2I/F1QNVclOBr1dYpTdmdyZ84Xiz43BS/tCUkMAZNLv12Pi+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta/-/plugin-syntax-import-meta-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Yqfm+XDx0+Prh3VSeEQCPU81yC+JWZ2pDPFSS4ZdpfZhp4MkFMaDC1UqseovEKwSUpnIL7+vK+Clp7bfh0iD7g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings/-/plugin-syntax-json-strings-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lY6kdGpWHvjoe2vk4WrAapEuBR69EMxZl+RoGRhrFGNYVK8mOPAW8VfbT/ZgrFbXlDNiiaxQnAtgVCZ6jv30EA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx/-/plugin-syntax-jsx-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ld6oezHQMZsZfp6pWtbjaNDF2tiiCYYDqQszHt5VV437lewP9aSi2Of99CK0D0XB21k7FLgnLcmQKyKzynfeAA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators/-/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-d8waShlpFDinQ5MtvGU9xDAOzKH47+FFoney2baFIoMr952hKOLp1HR7VszoZvOsV/4+RRszNY7D17ba0te0ig==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator/-/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-aSff4zPII1u2QD7y+F8oDsz19ew4IGEJg9SVW+bqwpwtfFleiQDMdzA/R+UlWDzfnHFCxxleFT0PMIrR36XLNQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator/-/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9H6YdfkcK/uOnY/K7/aA2xpzaAgkQn37yzWUMRK7OaPOqOpGS1+n0H5hxT9AUw9EsSjPW8SVyMJwYRtWs3X3ug==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread/-/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XoqMijGZb9y3y2XskN+P1wUGiVwWZ5JmoDRwx5+3GmEplNyVM2s2Dg8ILFQm8rWM48orGy5YpI5Bl8U1y7ydlA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding/-/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6VPD0Pc1lpTqw0aKoeRTMiB+kWhAoT24PA+ksWSBrFtl5SIRVpZlwN3NNPQjehA2E/91FV3RjLWoVTglWcSV3Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining/-/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KoK9ErH1MBlCPxV0VANkXW2/dw4vlbGDrFgz8bmUsBGYkFRcbRwMh6cIJubdPrkxRwuGdtCk0v/wPTKbQgBjkg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object/-/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0wVnp9dxJ72ZUJDV27ZfbSj6iHLoytYZmh3rFcxNnvsJF3ktkzLDZPy/mA17HGsaQT3/DQsWYX1f1QGWkCoVUg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await/-/plugin-syntax-top-level-await-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hx++upLv5U1rgYfwe1xBQUhRmU41NEvpUvrp8jkrSCdvGSnM5/qdRMtylJ6PG5OFkBaHkbTAKTnd3/YyESRHFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript/-/plugin-syntax-typescript-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hjMgRy5hb8uJJjUcdWunWVcoi9bGpJp8p5Ol1229PoN6aytsLwNMgmdftO23wnCLMfVmTwZDWMPNq/D1SY60JQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/template\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/template/-/template-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2ncevenBqXI6qRMukPlXwHKHchC7RyMuu4xv5JBXRfOGVcTy1mXCD12qrp7Jsoxll1EV3+9sE4GugBVRjT2jFA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/traverse\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/traverse/-/traverse-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-19lYZFzYVQkkHkl4Cy4WrAVcqBkgvV2YM2TU3xG6DIwO7O3ecbDPfW3yM3bjAGcqcQHi+CCtjMR3dIEHxsd6bA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"debug\": \"^4.3.1\",\n        \"globals\": \"^11.1.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/types\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/types/-/types-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-H45s8fVLYjbhFH62dIJ3WtmJ6RSPt/3DRO0ZcT2SUiYiQyz3BLVb9ADEnLl91m74aQPS3AzzeajZHYOalWe3bg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-string-parser\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@bcoe/v8-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@bcoe/v8-coverage/-/v8-coverage-0.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0hYQ8SB4Db5zvZB4axdMHGwEaQjkZzFjQiN9LVYvIFB2nSUHW9tYpxWriPrWDASIxiaXax83REcLxuSdnGPZtw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config/-/load-nyc-config-1.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-VjeHSlIzpv/NyD3N0YuHfXOPDIixcA1q2ZV98wsMqcYlPmv2n3Yb2lYP9XMElnaFVXg5A7YLTeLu6V84uQDjmQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"camelcase\": \"^5.3.1\",\n        \"find-up\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"get-package-type\": \"^0.1.0\",\n        \"js-yaml\": \"^3.13.1\",\n        \"resolve-from\": \"^5.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@istanbuljs/schema\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@istanbuljs/schema/-/schema-0.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ZXRY4jNvVgSVQ8DL3LTcakaAtXwTVUxE81hslsyD2AtoXW/wVob10HkOJ1X/pAlcI7D+2YoZKg5do8G/w6RYgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@jest/console\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/console/-/console-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-5Ni4CU7XHQi32IJ398EEP4RrB8eV09sXP2ROqD4bksHrnTree52PsxvX8tpL8LvTZ3pFzXyPbNQReSN41CAhOg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/core\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/core/-/core-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-n7aeXWKMnGtDA48y8TLWJPJmLmmZ642Ceo78cYWEpiD7FzDgmNDV/GCVRorPABdXLJZ/9wzzgZAlHjXjxDHGsg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/reporters\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"ansi-escapes\": \"^4.2.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-changed-files\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-resolve-dependencies\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runner\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-watcher\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/environment\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/environment/-/environment-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-aQIfHDq33ExsN4jP1NWGXhxgQ/wixs60gDiKO+XVMd8Mn0NWPWgc34ZQDTb2jKaUWQ7MuwoitXAsN2XVXNMpAw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/expect\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/expect/-/expect-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-8uMeAMycttpva3P1lBHB8VciS9V0XAr3GymPpipdyQXbBcuhkLQOSe8E/p92RyAdToS6ZD1tFkX+CkhoECE0dQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/expect-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/expect-utils/-/expect-utils-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GlsNBWiFQFCVi9QVSx7f5AgMeLxe9YCCs5PuP2O2LdjDAA8Jh9eX7lA1Jq/xdXw3Wb3hyvlFNfZIfcRetSzYcA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@jest/fake-timers\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/fake-timers/-/fake-timers-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-q4DH1Ha4TTFPdxLsqDXK1d3+ioSL7yL5oCMJZgDYm6i+6CygW5E5xVr/D1HdsGxjt1ZWSfUAs9OxSB/BNelWrQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@sinonjs/fake-timers\": \"^10.0.2\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/globals\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/globals/-/globals-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-mpiz3dutLbkW2MNFubUGUEVLkTGiqW6yLVTA+JbP6fI6J5iL9Y0Nlg8k95pcF8ctKwCS7WVxteBs29hhfAotzQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/reporters\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/reporters/-/reporters-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DApq0KJbJOEzAFYjHADNNxAE3KbhxQB1y5Kplb5Waqw6zVbuWatSnMjE5gs8FUgEPmNsnZA3NCWl9NG0ia04Pg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@bcoe/v8-coverage\": \"^0.2.3\",\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-report\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-source-maps\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-reports\": \"^3.1.3\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"string-length\": \"^4.0.1\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"v8-to-istanbul\": \"^9.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/schemas\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/schemas/-/schemas-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-mo5j5X+jIZmJQveBKeS/clAueipV7KgiX1vMgCxam1RNYiqE1w62n0/tJJnHtjW8ZHcQco5gY85jA3mi0L+nSA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@jest/source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/source-map/-/source-map-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MHjT95QuipcPrpLM+8JMSzFx6eHp5Bm+4XeFDJlwsvVBjmKNiIAvasGK2fxz2WbGRlnvqehFbh07MMa7n3YJnw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"callsites\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/test-result\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/test-result/-/test-result-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Fdx+tv6x1zlkJPcWXmMDAG2HBnaR9XPSd5aDWQVsfrZmLVT3lU1cwyxLgRmXR9yrq4NBoEm9BMsfgFzTQAbJYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/test-sequencer\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/test-sequencer/-/test-sequencer-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GQwJ5WZVrKnOJuiYiAF52UNUJXgTZx1NHjFSEB0qEMmSZKAkdMoIzw/Cj6x6NF4AvV23AUqDpFzQkN/eYCYTxw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/transform\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/transform/-/transform-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ok/BTPFzFKVMwO5eOHRrvnBVHdRy9IrsrW1GpMaQ9MCnilNLXQKmAX8s1YXDFaai9xJpac2ySzV0YeRRECr2Vw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": \"^6.1.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"fast-json-stable-stringify\": \"^2.1.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pirates\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"write-file-atomic\": \"^4.0.2\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/types\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/types/-/types-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-u3UPsIilWKOM3F9CXtrG8LEJmNxwoCQC/XVj4IKYXvvpx7QIi/Kg1LI5uDmDpKlac62NUtX7eLjRh+jVZcLOzw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/schemas\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-reports\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/yargs\": \"^17.0.8\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.3.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/gen-mapping/-/gen-mapping-0.3.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-imAbBGkb+ebQyxKgzv5Hu2nmROxoDOXHh80evxdoXNOrvAnVx7zimzc1Oo5h9RlfV4vPXaE2iM5pOFbvOCClWA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/set-array\": \"^1.2.1\",\n        \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": \"^1.4.10\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.24\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/resolve-uri\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/resolve-uri/-/resolve-uri-3.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bRISgCIjP20/tbWSPWMEi54QVPRZExkuD9lJL+UIxUKtwVJA8wW1Trb1jMs1RFXo1CBTNZ/5hpC9QvmKWdopKw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/set-array\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/set-array/-/set-array-1.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R8gLRTZeyp03ymzP/6Lil/28tGeGEzhx1q2k703KGWRAI1VdvPIXdG70VJc2pAMw3NA6JKL5hhFu1sJX0Mnn/A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec/-/sourcemap-codec-1.5.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gv3ZRaISU3fjPAgNsriBRqGWQL6quFx04YMPW/zD8XMLsU32mhCCbfbO6KZFLjvYpCZ8zyDEgqsgf+PwPaM7GQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.3.25\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/trace-mapping/-/trace-mapping-0.3.25.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-vNk6aEwybGtawWmy/PzwnGDOjCkLWSD2wqvjGGAgOAwCGWySYXfYoxt00IJkTF+8Lb57DwOb3Aa0o9CApepiYQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/resolve-uri\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": \"^1.4.14\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@sinclair/typebox\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.27.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinclair/typebox/-/typebox-0.27.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+Fj43pSMwJs4KRrH/938Uf+uAELIgVBmQzg/q1YG10djyfA3TnrU8N8XzqCh/okZdszqBQTZf96idMfE5lnwTA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@sinonjs/commons\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinonjs/commons/-/commons-3.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-K3mCHKQ9sVh8o1C9cxkwxaOmXoAMlDxC1mYyHrjqOWEcBjYr76t96zL2zlj5dUGZ3HSw240X1qgH3Mjf1yJWpQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@sinonjs/fake-timers\": {\n      \"version\": \"10.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinonjs/fake-timers/-/fake-timers-10.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-V4BG07kuYSUkTCSBHG8G8TNhM+F19jXFWnQtzj+we8DrkpSBCee9Z3Ms8yiGer/dlmhe35/Xdgyo3/0rQKg7YA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/babel__core\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.20.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__core/-/babel__core-7.20.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qoQprZvz5wQFJwMDqeseRXWv3rqMvhgpbXFfVyWhbx9X47POIA6i/+dXefEmZKoAgOaTdaIgNSMqMIU61yRyzA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.20.7\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.20.7\",\n        \"@types/babel__generator\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/babel__template\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/babel__traverse\": \"*\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@types/babel__generator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__generator/-/babel__generator-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ufFd2Xi92OAVPYsy+P4n7/U7e68fex0+Ee8gSG9KX7eo084CWiQ4sdxktvdl0bOPupXtVJPY19zk6EwWqUQ8lg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/babel__template\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.4.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__template/-/babel__template-7.4.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-h/NUaSyG5EyxBIp8YRxo4RMe2/qQgvyowRwVMzhYhBCONbW8PUsg4lkFMrhgZhUe5z3L3MiLDuvyJ/CaPa2A8A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.1.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@types/babel__traverse\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.20.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__traverse/-/babel__traverse-7.20.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-dkO5fhS7+/oos4ciWxyEyjWe48zmG6wbCheo/G2ZnHx4fs3EU6YC6UM8rk56gAjNJ9P3MTH2jo5jb92/K6wbng==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/graceful-fs\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/graceful-fs/-/graceful-fs-4.1.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-olP3sd1qOEe5dXTSaFvQG+02VdRXcdytWLAZsAq1PecU8uqQAhkrnbli7DagjtXKW/Bl7YJbUsa8MPcuc8LHEQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-lib-coverage/-/istanbul-lib-coverage-2.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2QF/t/auWm0lsy8XtKVPG19v3sSOQlJe/YHZgfjb/KBBHOGSV+J2q/S671rcq9uTBrLAXmZpqJiaQbMT+zNU1w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@types/istanbul-lib-report\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-lib-report/-/istanbul-lib-report-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NQn7AHQnk/RSLOxrBbGyJM/aVQ+pjj5HCgasFxc0K/KhoATfQ/47AyUl15I2yBUpihjmas+a+VJBOqecrFH+uA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/istanbul-reports\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-reports/-/istanbul-reports-3.0.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pk2B1NWalF9toCRu6gjBzR69syFjP4Od8WRAX+0mmf9lAjCRicLOWc+ZrxZHx/0XRjotgkF9t6iaMJ+aXcOdZQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/node\": {\n      \"version\": \"22.14.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/node/-/node-22.14.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-u0HuPQwe/dHrItgHHpmw3N2fYCR6x4ivMNbPHRkBVP4CvN+kiRrKHWk3i8tXiO/joPwXLMYvF9TTF0eqgHIuOw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/stack-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/stack-utils/-/stack-utils-2.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9aEbYZ3TbYMznPdcdr3SmIrLXwC/AKZXQeCf9Pgao5CKb8CyHuEX5jzWPTkvregvhRJHcpRO6BFoGW9ycaOkYw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@types/yargs\": {\n      \"version\": \"17.0.33\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/yargs/-/yargs-17.0.33.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WpxBCKWPLr4xSsHgz511rFJAM+wS28w2zEO1QDNY5zM/S8ok70NNfztH0xwhqKyaK0OHCbN98LDAZuy1ctxDkA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/yargs-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"21.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/yargs-parser/-/yargs-parser-21.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-I4q9QU9MQv4oEOz4tAHJtNz1cwuLxn2F3xcc2iV5WdqLPpUnj30aUuxt1mAxYTG+oe8CZMV/+6rU4S4gRDzqtQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"ansi-escapes\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-escapes/-/ansi-escapes-4.3.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gKXj5ALrKWQLsYG9jlTRmR/xKluxHV+Z9QEwNIgCfM1/uwPMCuzVVnh5mwTd+OuBZcwSIMbqssNWRm1lE51QaQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"ansi-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-regex/-/ansi-regex-5.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-quJQXlTSUGL2LH9SUXo8VwsY4soanhgo6LNSm84E1LBcE8s3O0wpdiRzyR9z/ZZJMlMWv37qOOb9pdJlMUEKFQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"ansi-styles\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-styles/-/ansi-styles-4.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zbB9rCJAT1rbjiVDb2hqKFHNYLxgtk8NURxZ3IZwD3F6NtxbXZQCnnSi1Lkx+IDohdPlFp222wVALIheZJQSEg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"anymatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/anymatch/-/anymatch-3.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KMReFUr0B4t+D+OBkjR3KYqvocp2XaSzO55UcB6mgQMd3KbcE+mWTyvVV7D/zsdEbNnV6acZUutkiHQXvTr1Rw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"normalize-path\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"picomatch\": \"^2.0.4\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"argparse\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/argparse/-/argparse-1.0.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-o5Roy6tNG4SL/FOkCAN6RzjiakZS25RLYFrcMttJqbdd8BWrnA+fGz57iN5Pb06pvBGvl5gQ0B48dJlslXvoTg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"babel-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-jest/-/babel-jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BrvGY3xZSwEcCzKvKsCi2GgHqDqsYkOP4/by5xCgIwGXQxIEh+8ew3gmrE1y7XRR6LHZIj6yLYnUi/mm2KXKBg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@types/babel__core\": \"^7.1.14\",\n        \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": \"^6.1.1\",\n        \"babel-preset-jest\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-plugin-istanbul/-/babel-plugin-istanbul-6.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Y1IQok9821cC9onCx5otgFfRm7Lm+I+wwxOx738M/WLPZ9Q42m4IG5W0FNX8WLL2gYMZo3JkuXIH2DOpWM+qwA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-plugin-utils\": \"^7.0.0\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": \"^5.0.4\",\n        \"test-exclude\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": {\n          \"version\": \"5.2.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-instrument/-/istanbul-lib-instrument-5.2.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-pzqtp31nLv/XFOzXGuvhCb8qhjmTVo5vjVk19XE4CRlSWz0KoeJ3bw9XsA7nOp9YBf4qHjwBxkDzKcME/J29Yg==\",\n          \"dev\": true,\n          \"requires\": {\n            \"@babel/core\": \"^7.12.3\",\n            \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.14.7\",\n            \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n            \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.2.0\",\n            \"semver\": \"^6.3.0\"\n          }\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"babel-plugin-jest-hoist\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-plugin-jest-hoist/-/babel-plugin-jest-hoist-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ESAc/RJvGTFEzRwOTT4+lNDk/GNHMkKbNzsvT0qKRfDyyYTskxB5rnU2njIDYVxXCBHHEI1c0YwHob3WaYujOg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@types/babel__core\": \"^7.1.14\",\n        \"@types/babel__traverse\": \"^7.0.6\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-preset-current-node-syntax/-/babel-preset-current-node-syntax-1.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ldYss8SbBlWva1bs28q78Ju5Zq1F+8BrqBZZ0VFhLBvhh6lCpC2o3gDJi/5DRLs9FgYZCnmPYIVFU4lRXCkyUw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators\": \"^7.8.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties\": \"^7.12.13\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block\": \"^7.14.5\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes\": \"^7.24.7\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object\": \"^7.14.5\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await\": \"^7.14.5\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"babel-preset-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-preset-jest/-/babel-preset-jest-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0B3bhxR6snWXJZtR/RliHTDPRgn1sNHOR0yVtq/IiQFyuOVjFS+wuio/R4gSNkyYmKmJB4wGZv2NZanmKmTnNA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"babel-plugin-jest-hoist\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"balanced-match\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/balanced-match/-/balanced-match-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3oSeUO0TMV67hN1AmbXsK4yaqU7tjiHlbxRDZOpH0KW9+CeX4bRAaX0Anxt0tx2MrpRpWwQaPwIlISEJhYU5Pw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"brace-expansion\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.11\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/brace-expansion/-/brace-expansion-1.1.11.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iCuPHDFgrHX7H2vEI/5xpz07zSHB00TpugqhmYtVmMO6518mCuRMoOYFldEBl0g187ufozdaHgWKcYFb61qGiA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"balanced-match\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"concat-map\": \"0.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"braces\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/braces/-/braces-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-yQbXgO/OSZVD2IsiLlro+7Hf6Q18EJrKSEsdoMzKePKXct3gvD8oLcOQdIzGupr5Fj+EDe8gO/lxc1BzfMpxvA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"browserslist\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.24.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/browserslist/-/browserslist-4.24.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KDi1Ny1gSePi1vm0q4oxSF8b4DR44GF4BbmS2YdhPLOEqd8pDviZOGH/GsmRwoWJ2+5Lr085X7naowMwKHDG1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"caniuse-lite\": \"^1.0.30001688\",\n        \"electron-to-chromium\": \"^1.5.73\",\n        \"node-releases\": \"^2.0.19\",\n        \"update-browserslist-db\": \"^1.1.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"bser\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/bser/-/bser-2.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gQxTNE/GAfIIrmHLUE3oJyp5FO6HRBfhjnw4/wMmA63ZGDJnWBmgY/lyQBpnDUkGmAhbSe39tx2d/iTOAfglwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"buffer-from\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/buffer-from/-/buffer-from-1.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-E+XQCRwSbaaiChtv6k6Dwgc+bx+Bs6vuKJHHl5kox/BaKbhiXzqQOwK4cO22yElGp2OCmjwVhT3HmxgyPGnJfQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"callsites\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/callsites/-/callsites-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-P8BjAsXvZS+VIDUI11hHCQEv74YT67YUi5JJFNWIqL235sBmjX4+qx9Muvls5ivyNENctx46xQLQ3aTuE7ssaQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"camelcase\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/camelcase/-/camelcase-5.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-L28STB170nwWS63UjtlEOE3dldQApaJXZkOI1uMFfzf3rRuPegHaHesyee+YxQ+W6SvRDQV6UrdOdRiR153wJg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"caniuse-lite\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.30001715\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/caniuse-lite/-/caniuse-lite-1.0.30001715.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7ptkFGMm2OAOgvZpwgA4yjQ5SQbrNVGdRjzH0pBdy1Fasvcr+KAeECmbCAECzTuDuoX0FCY8KzUxjf9+9kfZEw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"chalk\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/chalk/-/chalk-4.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-oKnbhFyRIXpUuez8iBMmyEa4nbj4IOQyuhc/wy9kY7/WVPcwIO9VA668Pu8RkO7+0G76SLROeyw9CpQ061i4mA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^7.1.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"char-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/char-regex/-/char-regex-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kWWXztvZ5SBQV+eRgKFeh8q5sLuZY2+8WUIzlxWVTg+oGwY14qylx1KbKzHd8P6ZYkAg0xyIDU9JMHhyJMZ1jw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"ci-info\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.9.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ci-info/-/ci-info-3.9.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NIxF55hv4nSqQswkAeiOi1r83xy8JldOFDTWiug55KBu9Jnblncd2U6ViHmYgHf01TPZS77NJBhBMKdWj9HQMQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"cjs-module-lexer\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cjs-module-lexer/-/cjs-module-lexer-1.4.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9z8TZaGM1pfswYeXrUpzPrkx8UnWYdhJclsiYMm6x/w5+nN+8Tf/LnAgfLGQCm59qAOxU8WwHEq2vNwF6i4j+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"cliui\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cliui/-/cliui-8.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BSeNnyus75C4//NQ9gQt1/csTXyo/8Sb+afLAkzAptFuMsod9HFokGNudZpi/oQV73hnVK+sR+5PVRMd+Dr7YQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.2.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.1\",\n        \"wrap-ansi\": \"^7.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"co\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.6.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/co/-/co-4.6.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-QVb0dM5HvG+uaxitm8wONl7jltx8dqhfU33DcqtOZcLSVIKSDDLDi7+0LbAKiyI8hD9u42m2YxXSkMGWThaecQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"collect-v8-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/collect-v8-coverage/-/collect-v8-coverage-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lHl4d5/ONEbLlJvaJNtsF/Lz+WvB07u2ycqTYbdrq7UypDXailES4valYb2eWiJFxZlVmpGekfqoxQhzyFdT4Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"color-convert\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/color-convert/-/color-convert-2.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RRECPsj7iu/xb5oKYcsFHSppFNnsj/52OVTRKb4zP5onXwVF3zVmmToNcOfGC+CRDpfK/U584fMg38ZHCaElKQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"color-name\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/color-name/-/color-name-1.1.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-dOy+3AuW3a2wNbZHIuMZpTcgjGuLU/uBL/ubcZF9OXbDo8ff4O8yVp5Bf0efS8uEoYo5q4Fx7dY9OgQGXgAsQA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"concat-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/concat-map/-/concat-map-0.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/Srv4dswyQNBfohGpz9o6Yb3Gz3SrUDqBH5rTuhGR7ahtlbYKnVxw2bCFMRljaA7EXHaXZ8wsHdodFvbkhKmqg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"convert-source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/convert-source-map/-/convert-source-map-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Kvp459HrV2FEJ1CAsi1Ku+MY3kasH19TFykTz2xWmMeq6bk2NU3XXvfJ+Q61m0xktWwt+1HSYf3JZsTms3aRJg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"create-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/create-jest/-/create-jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Adz2bdH0Vq3F53KEMJOoftQFutWCukm6J24wbPWRO4k1kMY7gS7ds/uoJkNuV8wDCtWWnuwGcJwpWcih+zEW1Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"prompts\": \"^2.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"cross-spawn\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cross-spawn/-/cross-spawn-7.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-uV2QOWP2nWzsy2aMp8aRibhi9dlzF5Hgh5SHaB9OiTGEyDTiJJyx0uy51QXdyWbtAHNua4XJzUKca3OzKUd3vA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"path-key\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"shebang-command\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"which\": \"^2.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"debug\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/debug/-/debug-4.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6WTZ/IxCY/T6BALoZHaE4ctp9xm+Z5kY/pzYaCHRFeyVhojxlrm+46y68HA6hr0TcwEssoxNiDEUJQjfPZ/RYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"dedent\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/dedent/-/dedent-1.5.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NHQtfOOW68WD8lgypbLA5oT+Bt0xXJhiYvoR6SmmNXZfpzOGXwdKWmcwG8N7PwVVWV3eF/68nmD9BaJSsTBhyQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {}\n    },\n    \"deepmerge\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/deepmerge/-/deepmerge-4.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3sUqbMEc77XqpdNO7FRyRog+eW3ph+GYCbj+rK+uYyRMuwsVy0rMiVtPn+QJlKFvWP/1PYpapqYn0Me2knFn+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"detect-newline\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/detect-newline/-/detect-newline-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TLz+x/vEXm/Y7P7wn1EJFNLxYpUD4TgMosxY6fAVJUnJMbupHBOncxyWUG9OpTaH9EBD7uFI5LfEgmMOc54DsA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"diff-sequences\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/diff-sequences/-/diff-sequences-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-EjePK1srD3P08o2j4f0ExnylqRs5B9tJjcp9t1krH2qRi8CCdsYfwe9JgSLurFBWwq4uOlipzfk5fHNvwFKr8Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"electron-to-chromium\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.140\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/electron-to-chromium/-/electron-to-chromium-1.5.140.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-o82Rj+ONp4Ip7Cl1r7lrqx/pXhbp/lh9DpKcMNscFJdh8ebyRofnc7Sh01B4jx403RI0oqTBvlZ7OBIZLMr2+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"emittery\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.13.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/emittery/-/emittery-0.13.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DeWwawk6r5yR9jFgnDKYt4sLS0LmHJJi3ZOnb5/JdbYwj3nW+FxQnHIjhBKz8YLC7oRNPVM9NQ47I3CVx34eqQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"emoji-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/emoji-regex/-/emoji-regex-8.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MSjYzcWNOA0ewAHpz0MxpYFvwg6yjy1NG3xteoqz644VCo/RPgnr1/GGt+ic3iJTzQ8Eu3TdM14SawnVUmGE6A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"error-ex\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.3.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/error-ex/-/error-ex-1.3.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7dFHNmqeFSEt2ZBsCriorKnn3Z2pj+fd9kmI6QoWw4//DL+icEBfc0U7qJCisqrTsKTjw4fNFy2pW9OqStD84g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"escalade\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/escalade/-/escalade-3.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WUj2qlxaQtO4g6Pq5c29GTcWGDyd8itL8zTlipgECz3JesAiiOKotd8JU6otB3PACgG6xkJUyVhboMS+bje/jA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"escape-string-regexp\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/escape-string-regexp/-/escape-string-regexp-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UpzcLCXolUWcNu5HtVMHYdXJjArjsF9C0aNnquZYY4uW/Vu0miy5YoWvbV345HauVvcAUnpRuhMMcqTcGOY2+w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"esprima\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/esprima/-/esprima-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eGuFFw7Upda+g4p+QHvnW0RyTX/SVeJBDM/gCtMARO0cLuT2HcEKnTPvhjV6aGeqrCB/sbNop0Kszm0jsaWU4A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"execa\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/execa/-/execa-5.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-8uSpZZocAZRBAPIEINJj3Lo9HyGitllczc27Eh5YYojjMFMn8yHMDMaUHE2Jqfq05D/wucwI4JGURyXt1vchyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"cross-spawn\": \"^7.0.3\",\n        \"get-stream\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"human-signals\": \"^2.1.0\",\n        \"is-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"merge-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"npm-run-path\": \"^4.0.1\",\n        \"onetime\": \"^5.1.2\",\n        \"signal-exit\": \"^3.0.3\",\n        \"strip-final-newline\": \"^2.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"exit\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/exit/-/exit-0.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Zk/eNKV2zbjpKzrsQ+n1G6poVbErQxJ0LBOJXaKZ1EViLzH+hrLu9cdXI4zw9dBQJslwBEpbQ2P1oS7nDxs6jQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"expect\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/expect/-/expect-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2Zks0hf1VLFYI1kbh0I5jP3KHHyCHpkfyHBzsSXRFgl/Bg9mWYfMW8oD+PdMPlEwy5HNsR9JutYy6pMeOh61nw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/expect-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"fast-json-stable-stringify\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fast-json-stable-stringify/-/fast-json-stable-stringify-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lhd/wF+Lk98HZoTCtlVraHtfh5XYijIjalXck7saUtuanSDyLMxnHhSXEDJqHxD7msR8D0uCmqlkwjCV8xvwHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"fb-watchman\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fb-watchman/-/fb-watchman-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-p5161BqbuCaSnB8jIbzQHOlpgsPmK5rJVDfDKO91Axs5NC1uu3HRQm6wt9cd9/+GtQQIO53JdGXXoyDpTAsgYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"fill-range\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fill-range/-/fill-range-7.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-YsGpe3WHLK8ZYi4tWDg2Jy3ebRz2rXowDxnld4bkQB00cc/1Zw9AWnC0i9ztDJitivtQvaI9KaLyKrc+hBW0yg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"find-up\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/find-up/-/find-up-4.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-PpOwAdQ/YlXQ2vj8a3h8IipDuYRi3wceVQQGYWxNINccq40Anw7BlsEXCMbt1Zt+OLA6Fq9suIpIWD0OsnISlw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"locate-path\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"path-exists\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"fs.realpath\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fs.realpath/-/fs.realpath-1.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OO0pH2lK6a0hZnAdau5ItzHPI6pUlvI7jMVnxUQRtw4owF2wk8lOSabtGDCTP4Ggrg2MbGnWO9X8K1t4+fGMDw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"fsevents\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fsevents/-/fsevents-2.3.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-5xoDfX+fL7faATnagmWPpbFtwh/R77WmMMqqHGS65C3vvB0YHrgF+B1YmZ3441tMj5n63k0212XNoJwzlhffQw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"optional\": true\n    },\n    \"function-bind\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/function-bind/-/function-bind-1.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7XHNxH7qX9xG5mIwxkhumTox/MIRNcOgDrxWsMt2pAr23WHp6MrRlN7FBSFpCpr+oVO0F744iUgR82nJMfG2SA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"gensync\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0-beta.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/gensync/-/gensync-1.0.0-beta.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3hN7NaskYvMDLQY55gnW3NQ+mesEAepTqlg+VEbj7zzqEMBVNhzcGYYeqFo/TlYz6eQiFcp1HcsCZO+nGgS8zg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"get-caller-file\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-caller-file/-/get-caller-file-2.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DyFP3BM/3YHTQOCUL/w0OZHR0lpKeGrxotcHWcqNEdnltqFwXVfhEBQ94eIo34AfQpo0rGki4cyIiftY06h2Fg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"get-package-type\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-package-type/-/get-package-type-0.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pjzuKtY64GYfWizNAJ0fr9VqttZkNiK2iS430LtIHzjBEr6bX8Am2zm4sW4Ro5wjWW5cAlRL1qAMTcXbjNAO2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"get-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-stream/-/get-stream-6.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ts6Wi+2j3jQjqi70w5AlN8DFnkSwC+MqmxEzdEALB2qXZYV3X/b1CTfgPLGJNMeAWxdPfU8FO1ms3NUfaHCPYg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"glob\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/glob/-/glob-7.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-nFR0zLpU2YCaRxwoCJvL6UvCH2JFyFVIvwTLsIf21AuHlMskA1hhTdk+LlYJtOlYt9v6dvszD2BGRqBL+iQK9Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"fs.realpath\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"inflight\": \"^1.0.4\",\n        \"inherits\": \"2\",\n        \"minimatch\": \"^3.1.1\",\n        \"once\": \"^1.3.0\",\n        \"path-is-absolute\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"globals\": {\n      \"version\": \"11.12.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/globals/-/globals-11.12.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WOBp/EEGUiIsJSp7wcv/y6MO+lV9UoncWqxuFfm8eBwzWNgyfBd6Gz+IeKQ9jCmyhoH99g15M3T+QaVHFjizVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"graceful-fs\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.11\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/graceful-fs/-/graceful-fs-4.2.11.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RbJ5/jmFcNNCcDV5o9eTnBLJ/HszWV0P73bc+Ff4nS/rJj+YaS6IGyiOL0VoBYX+l1Wrl3k63h/KrH+nhJ0XvQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"has-flag\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/has-flag/-/has-flag-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-EykJT/Q1KjTWctppgIAgfSO0tKVuZUjhgMr17kqTumMl6Afv3EISleU7qZUzoXDFTAHTDC4NOoG/ZxU3EvlMPQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"hasown\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/hasown/-/hasown-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0hJU9SCPvmMzIBdZFqNPXWa6dqh7WdH0cII9y+CyS8rG3nL48Bclra9HmKhVVUHyPWNH5Y7xDwAB7bfgSjkUMQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"html-escaper\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/html-escaper/-/html-escaper-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-H2iMtd0I4Mt5eYiapRdIDjp+XzelXQ0tFE4JS7YFwFevXXMmOp9myNrUvCg0D6ws8iqkRPBfKHgbwig1SmlLfg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"human-signals\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/human-signals/-/human-signals-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-B4FFZ6q/T2jhhksgkbEW3HBvWIfDW85snkQgawt07S7J5QXTk6BkNV+0yAeZrM5QpMAdYlocGoljn0sJ/WQkFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"import-local\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/import-local/-/import-local-3.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2SPlun1JUPWoM6t3F0dw0FkCF/jWY8kttcY4f599GLTSjh2OCuuhdTkJQsEcZzBqbXZGKMK2OqW1oZsjtf/gQA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"imurmurhash\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/imurmurhash/-/imurmurhash-0.1.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JmXMZ6wuvDmLiHEml9ykzqO6lwFbof0GG4IkcGaENdCRDDmMVnny7s5HsIgHCbaq0w2MyPhDqkhTUgS2LU2PHA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"inflight\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/inflight/-/inflight-1.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-k92I/b08q4wvFscXCLvqfsHCrjrF7yiXsQuIVvVE7N82W3+aqpzuUdBbfhWcy/FZR3/4IgflMgKLOsvPDrGCJA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"inherits\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/inherits/-/inherits-2.0.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-k/vGaX4/Yla3WzyMCvTQOXYeIHvqOKtnqBduzTHpzpQZzAskKMhZ2K+EnBiSM9zGSoIFeMpXKxa4dYeZIQqewQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-arrayish\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-arrayish/-/is-arrayish-0.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zz06S8t0ozoDXMG+ube26zeCTNXcKIPJZJi8hBrF4idCLms4CG9QtK7qBl1boi5ODzFpjswb5JPmHCbMpjaYzg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-core-module\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.16.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-core-module/-/is-core-module-2.16.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UfoeMA6fIJ8wTYFEUjelnaGI67v6+N7qXJEvQuIGa99l4xsCruSYOVSQ0uPANn4dAzm8lkYPaKLrrijLq7x23w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"is-fullwidth-code-point\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-fullwidth-code-point/-/is-fullwidth-code-point-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zymm5+u+sCsSWyD9qNaejV3DFvhCKclKdizYaJUuHA83RLjb7nSuGnddCHGv0hk+KY7BMAlsWeK4Ueg6EV6XQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-generator-fn\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-generator-fn/-/is-generator-fn-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-cTIB4yPYL/Grw0EaSzASzg6bBy9gqCofvWN8okThAYIxKJZC+udlRAmGbM0XLeniEJSs8uEgHPGuHSe1XsOLSQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-number\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-number/-/is-number-7.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-41Cifkg6e8TylSpdtTpeLVMqvSBEVzTttHvERD741+pnZ8ANv0004MRL43QKPDlK9cGvNp6NZWZUBlbGXYxxng==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-stream/-/is-stream-2.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hFoiJiTl63nn+kstHGBtewWSKnQLpyb155KHheA1l39uvtO9nWIop1p3udqPcUd/xbF1VLMO4n7OI6p7RbngDg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"isexe\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/isexe/-/isexe-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RHxMLp9lnKHGHRng9QFhRCMbYAcVpn69smSGcq3f36xjgVVWThj4qqLbTLlq7Ssj8B+fIQ1EuCEGI2lKsyQeIw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-coverage/-/istanbul-lib-coverage-3.2.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-O8dpsF+r0WV/8MNRKfnmrtCWhuKjxrq2w+jpzBL5UZKTi2LeVWnWOmWRxFlesJONmc+wLAGvKQZEOanko0LFTg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-instrument/-/istanbul-lib-instrument-6.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Vtgk7L/R2JHyyGW07spoFlB8/lpjiOLTjMdms6AFMraYt3BaJauod/NGrfnVG/y4Ix1JEuMRPDPEj2ua+zz1/Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.23.9\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.23.9\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.3\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^7.5.4\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"semver\": {\n          \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"istanbul-lib-report\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-report/-/istanbul-lib-report-3.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GCfE1mtsHGOELCU8e/Z7YWzpmybrx/+dSTfLrvY8qRmaY6zXTKWn6WQIjaAFw069icm6GVMNkgu0NzI4iPZUNw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"make-dir\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^7.1.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"istanbul-lib-source-maps\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-source-maps/-/istanbul-lib-source-maps-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-n3s8EwkdFIJCG3BPKBYvskgXGoy88ARzvegkitk60NxRdwltLOTaH7CUiMRXvwYorl0Q712iEjcWB+fK/MrWVw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"debug\": \"^4.1.1\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"source-map\": \"^0.6.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"istanbul-reports\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-reports/-/istanbul-reports-3.1.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BewmUXImeuRk2YY0PVbxgKAysvhRPUQE0h5QRM++nVWyubKGV0l8qQ5op8+B2DOmwSe63Jivj0BjkPQVf8fP5g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"html-escaper\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-report\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest/-/jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NIy3oAFp9shda19hy4HK0HRTWKtPJmGdnvywu01nOqNC2vZg+Z+fvJDxpMQA88eb2I9EcafcdjYgsDthnYTvGw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/core\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"import-local\": \"^3.0.2\",\n        \"jest-cli\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-changed-files\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-changed-files/-/jest-changed-files-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fEArFiwf1BpQ+4bXSprcDc3/x4HSzL4al2tozwVpDFpsxALjLYdyiIK4e5Vz66GQJIbXJ82+35PtysofptNX2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"execa\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-circus\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-circus/-/jest-circus-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3E1nCMgipcTkCocFwM90XXQab9bS+GMsjdpmPrlelaxwD93Ad8iVEjX/vvHPdLPnFf+L40u+5+iutRdA1N9myw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"co\": \"^4.6.0\",\n        \"dedent\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"is-generator-fn\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"jest-each\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"pure-rand\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"stack-utils\": \"^2.0.3\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-cli\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-cli/-/jest-cli-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OVVobw2IubN/GSYsxETi+gOe7Ka59EFMR/twOU3Jb2GnKKeMGJB5SGUUrEz3SFVmJASUdZUzy83sLNNQ2gZslg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/core\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"create-jest\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"import-local\": \"^3.0.2\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"yargs\": \"^17.3.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-config\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-config/-/jest-config-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-uXbpfeQ7R6TZBqI3/TxCU4q4ttk3u0PJeC+E0zbfSoSjq6bJ7buBPxzQPL0ifrkY4DNu4JUdk0ImlBUYi840eQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@jest/test-sequencer\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-jest\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"deepmerge\": \"^4.2.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-circus\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-environment-node\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runner\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"parse-json\": \"^5.2.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-json-comments\": \"^3.1.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-diff\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-diff/-/jest-diff-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LMIgiIrhigmPrs03JHpxUh2yISK3vLFPkAodPeo0+BuF7wA2FoQbkEg1u8gBYBThncu7e1oEDUfIXVuTqLRUjw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"diff-sequences\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-docblock\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-docblock/-/jest-docblock-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-q617Auw3A612guyaFgsbFeYpNP5t2aoUNLwBUbc/0kD1R4t9ixDbyFTHd1nok4epoVFpr7PmeWHrhvuV3XaJ4g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"jest-each\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-each/-/jest-each-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gns+Er14+ZrEoC5fhOfYCY1LOHHr0TI+rQUHZS8Ttw2l7gl+80eHc/gFf2Ktkw0+SIACDTeWvpFcv3B04VembQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-environment-node\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-environment-node/-/jest-environment-node-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DOSwCRqXirTOyheM+4d5YZOrWcdu0LNZ87ewUoywbcb2XR4wKgqiG8vNeYwhjFMbEkfju7wx2GYH0P2gevGvFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-get-type\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-get-type/-/jest-get-type-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zrteXnqYxfQh7l5FHyL38jL39di8H8rHoecLH3JNxH3BwOrBsNeabdap5e0I23lD4HHI8W5VFBZqG4Eaq5LNcw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"jest-haste-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-haste-map/-/jest-haste-map-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fP8u2pyfqx0K1rGn1R9pyE0/KTn+G7PxktWidOBTqFPLYX0b9ksaMFkhK5vrS3DVun09pckLdlx90QthlW7AmA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/graceful-fs\": \"^4.1.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"anymatch\": \"^3.0.3\",\n        \"fb-watchman\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"fsevents\": \"^2.3.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"walker\": \"^1.0.8\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-leak-detector\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-leak-detector/-/jest-leak-detector-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kYA8IJcSYtST2BY9I+SMC32nDpBT3J2NvWJx8+JCuCdl/CR1I4EKUJROiP8XtCcxqgTTBGJNdbB1A8XRKbTetw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-matcher-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-matcher-utils/-/jest-matcher-utils-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-sBkD+Xi9DtcChsI3L3u0+N0opgPYnCRPtGcQYrgXmR+hmt/fYfWAL0xRXYU8eWOdfuLgBe0YCW3AFtnRLagq/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-diff\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-message-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-message-util/-/jest-message-util-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GBEV4GRADeP+qtB2+6u61stea8mGcOT4mCtrYISZwfu9/ISHFJ/5zOMXYbpBE9RsS5+Gb63DW4FgmnKJ79Kf6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.12.13\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/stack-utils\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"stack-utils\": \"^2.0.3\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-mock\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-mock/-/jest-mock-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ITOMZn+UkYS4ZFh83xYAOzWStloNzJFO2s8DWrE4lhtGD+AorgnbkiKERe4wQVBydIGPx059g6riW5Btp6Llnw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-pnp-resolver\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-pnp-resolver/-/jest-pnp-resolver-1.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+3NpwQEnRoIBtx4fyhblQDPgJI0H1IEIkX7ShLUjPGA7TtUTvI1oiKi3SR4oBR0hQhQR80l4WAe5RrXBwWMA8w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {}\n    },\n    \"jest-regex-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-regex-util/-/jest-regex-util-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KJJBsRCyyLNWCNBOvZyRDnAIfUiRJ8v+hOBQYGn8gDyF3UegwiP4gwRR3/SDa42g1YbVycTidUF3rKjyLFDWbg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"jest-resolve\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-resolve/-/jest-resolve-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-IOVhZSrg+UvVAshDSDtHyFCCBUl/Q3AAJv8iZ6ZjnZ74xzvwuzLXid9IIIPgTnY62SJjfuupMKZsZQRsCvxEgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-pnp-resolver\": \"^1.2.2\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"resolve\": \"^1.20.0\",\n        \"resolve.exports\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-resolve-dependencies\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-resolve-dependencies/-/jest-resolve-dependencies-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-un0zD/6qxJ+S0et7WxeI3H5XSe9lTBBR7bOHCHXkKR6luG5mwDDlIzVQ0V5cZCuoTgEdcdwzTghYkTWfubi+nA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-runner\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-runner/-/jest-runner-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fsc4N6cPCAahybGBfTRcq5wFR6fpLznMg47sY5aDpsoejOcVYFb07AHuSnR0liMcPTgBsA3ZJL6kFOjPdoNipQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"emittery\": \"^0.13.1\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-docblock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-environment-node\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-leak-detector\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-watcher\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"source-map-support\": \"0.5.13\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-runtime\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-runtime/-/jest-runtime-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gUnLjgwdGqW7B4LvOIkbKs9WGbn+QLqRQQ9juC6HndeDiezIwhDP+mhMwHWCEcfQ5RUXa6OPnFF8BJh5xegwwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/globals\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/source-map\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"cjs-module-lexer\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-bom\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-snapshot\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-snapshot/-/jest-snapshot-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Rm0BMWtxBcioHr1/OX5YCP8Uov4riHvKPknOGs804Zg9JGZgmIBkbtlxJC/7Z4msKYVbIJtfU+tKb8xlYNfdkw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@jest/expect-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-diff\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"natural-compare\": \"^1.4.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^7.5.3\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"semver\": {\n          \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-util/-/jest-util-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-z6EbKajIpqGKU56y5KBUgy1dt1ihhQJgWzUlZHArA/+X2ad7Cb5iF+AK1EWVL/Bo7Rz9uurpqw6SiBCefUbCGA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"picomatch\": \"^2.2.3\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-validate\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-validate/-/jest-validate-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ZB7wHqaRGVw/9hST/OuFUReG7M8vKeq0/J2egIGLdvjHCmYqGARhzXmtgi+gVeZ5uXFF219aOc3Ls2yLg27tkw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"camelcase\": \"^6.2.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"leven\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"camelcase\": {\n          \"version\": \"6.3.0\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/camelcase/-/camelcase-6.3.0.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-Gmy6FhYlCY7uOElZUSbxo2UCDH8owEk996gkbrpsgGtrJLM3J7jGxl9Ic7Qwwj4ivOE5AWZWRMecDdF7hqGjFA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-watcher\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-watcher/-/jest-watcher-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-49Fg7WXkU3Vl2h6LbLtMQ/HyB6rXSIX7SqvBLQmssRBGN9I0PNvPmAmCWSOY6SOvrjhI/F7/bGAv9RtnsPA03g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"ansi-escapes\": \"^4.2.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"emittery\": \"^0.13.1\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"string-length\": \"^4.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-worker\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-worker/-/jest-worker-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eIz2msL/EzL9UFTFFx7jBTkeZfku0yUAyZZZmJ93H2TYEiroIx2PQjEXcwYtYl8zXCxb+PAmA2hLIt/6ZEkPHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"merge-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^8.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"supports-color\": {\n          \"version\": \"8.1.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-color/-/supports-color-8.1.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-MpUEN2OodtUzxvKQl72cUF7RQ5EiHsGvSsVG0ia9c5RbWGL2CI4C7EpPS8UTBIplnlzZiNuV56w+FuNxy3ty2Q==\",\n          \"dev\": true,\n          \"requires\": \n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"js-tokens\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/js-tokens/-/js-tokens-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RdJUflcE3cUzKiMqQgsCu06FPu9UdIJO0beYbPhHN4k6apgJtifcoCtT9bcxOpYBtpD2kCM6Sbzg4CausW/PKQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"js-yaml\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.14.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/js-yaml/-/js-yaml-3.14.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-okMH7OXXJ7YrN9Ok3/SXrnu4iX9yOk+25nqX4imS2npuvTYDmo/QEZoqwZkYaIDk3jVvBOTOIEgEhaLOynBS9g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"jsesc\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jsesc/-/jsesc-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/sM3dO2FOzXjKQhJuo0Q173wf2KOo8t4I8vHy6lF9poUp7bKT0/NHE8fPX23PwfhnykfqnC2xRxOnVw5XuGIaA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"json-parse-even-better-errors\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/json-parse-even-better-errors/-/json-parse-even-better-errors-2.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xyFwyhro/JEof6Ghe2iz2NcXoj2sloNsWr/XsERDK/oiPCfaNhl5ONfp+jQdAZRQQ0IJWNzH9zIZF7li91kh2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"json5\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/json5/-/json5-2.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XmOWe7eyHYH14cLdVPoyg+GOH3rYX++KpzrylJwSW98t3Nk+U8XOl8FWKOgwtzdb8lXGf6zYwDUzeHMWfxasyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"kleur\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/kleur/-/kleur-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eTIzlVOSUR+JxdDFepEYcBMtZ9Qqdef+rnzWdRZuMbOywu5tO2w2N7rqjoANZ5k9vywhL6Br1VRjUIgTQx4E8w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"leven\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/leven/-/leven-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qsda+H8jTaUaN/x5vzW2rzc+8Rw4TAQ/4KjB46IwK5VH+IlVeeeje/EoZRpiXvIqjFgK84QffqPztGI3VBLG1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"lines-and-columns\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/lines-and-columns/-/lines-and-columns-1.2.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7ylylesZQ/PV29jhEDl3Ufjo6ZX7gCqJr5F7PKrqc93v7fzSymt1BpwEU8nAUXs8qzzvqhbjhK5QZg6Mt/HkBg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"locate-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/locate-path/-/locate-path-5.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-t7hw9pI+WvuwNJXwk5zVHpyhIqzg2qTlklJOf0mVxGSbe3Fp2VieZcduNYjaLDoy6p9uGpQEGWG87WpMKlNq8g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"lru-cache\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/lru-cache/-/lru-cache-5.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KpNARQA3Iwv+jTA0utUVVbrh+Jlrr1Fv0e56GGzAFOXN7dk/FviaDW8LHmK52DlcH4WP2n6gI8vN1aesBFgo9w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"make-dir\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/make-dir/-/make-dir-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hXdUTZYIVOt1Ex//jAQi+wTZZpUpwBj/0QsOzqegb3rGMMeJiSEu5xLHnYfBrRV4RH2+OCSOO95Is/7x1WJ4bw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": ,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"semver\": {\n          \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"makeerror\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.12\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/makeerror/-/makeerror-1.0.12.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JmqCvUhmt43madlpFzG4BQzG2Z3m6tvQDNKdClZnO3VbIudJYmxsT0FNJMeiB2+JTSlTQTSbU8QdesVmwJcmLg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"merge-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/merge-stream/-/merge-stream-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-abv/qOcuPfk3URPfDzmZU1LKmuw8kT+0nIHvKrKgFrwifol/doWcdA4ZqsWQ8ENrFKkd67Mfpo/LovbIUsbt3w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"micromatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/micromatch/-/micromatch-4.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-PXwfBhYu0hBCPw8Dn0E+WDYb7af3dSLVWKi3HGv84IdF4TyFoC0ysxFd0Goxw7nSv4T/PzEJQxsYsEiFCKo2BA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"mimic-fn\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/mimic-fn/-/mimic-fn-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OqbOk5oEQeAZ8WXWydlu9HJjz9WVdEIvamMCcXmuqUYjTknH/sqsWvhQ3vgwKFRR1HpjvNBKQ37nbJgYzGqGcg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"minimatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/minimatch/-/minimatch-3.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-J7p63hRiAjw1NDEww1W7i37+ByIrOWO5XQQAzZ3VOcL0PNybwpfmV/N05zFAzwQ9USyEcX6t3UO+K5aqBQOIHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"ms\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ms/-/ms-2.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6FlzubTLZG3J2a/NVCAleEhjzq5oxgHyaCU9yYXvcLsvoVaHJq/s5xXI6/XXP6tz7R9xAOtHnSO/tXtF3WRTlA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"natural-compare\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/natural-compare/-/natural-compare-1.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OWND8ei3VtNC9h7V60qff3SVobHr996CTwgxubgyQYEpg290h9J0buyECNNJexkFm5sOajh5G116RYA1c8ZMSw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node-int64\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/node-int64/-/node-int64-0.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-O5lz91xSOeoXP6DulyHfllpq+Eg00MWitZIbtPfoSEvqIHdl5gfcY6hYzDWnj0qD5tz52PI08u9qUvSVeUBeHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node-releases\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.19\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/node-releases/-/node-releases-2.0.19.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xxOWJsBKtzAq7DY0J+DTzuz58K8e7sJbdgwkbMWQe8UYB6ekmsQ45q0M/tJDsGaZmbC+l7n57UV8Hl5tHxO9uw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"normalize-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/normalize-path/-/normalize-path-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6eZs5Ls3WtCisHWp9S2GUy8dqkpGi4BVSz3GaqiE6ezub0512ESztXUwUB6C6IKbQkY2Pnb/mD4WYojCRwcwLA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"npm-run-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/npm-run-path/-/npm-run-path-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-S48WzZW777zhNIrn7gxOlISNAqi9ZC/uQFnRdbeIHhZhCA6UqpkOT8T1G7BvfdgP4Er8gF4sUbaS0i7QvIfCWw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"once\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/once/-/once-1.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lNaJgI+2Q5URQBkccEKHTQOPaXdUxnZZElQTZY0MFUAuaEqe1E+Nyvgdz/aIyNi6Z9MzO5dv1H8n58/GELp3+w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"onetime\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/onetime/-/onetime-5.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kbpaSSGJTWdAY5KPVeMOKXSrPtr8C8C7wodJbcsd51jRnmD+GZu8Y0VoU6Dm5Z4vWr0Ig/1NKuWRKf7j5aaYSg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"p-limit\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-limit/-/p-limit-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TYOanM3wGwNGsZN2cVTYPArw454xnXj5qmWF1bEoAc4+cU/ol7GVh7odevjp1FNHduHc3KZMcFduxU5Xc6uJRQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"p-locate\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-locate/-/p-locate-4.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R79ZZ/0wAxKGu3oYMlz8jy/kbhsNrS7SKZ7PxEHBgJ5+F2mtFW2fK2cOtBh1cHYkQsbzFV7I+EoRKe6Yt0oK7A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": ,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"p-limit\": {\n          \"version\": \"2.3.0\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-limit/-/p-limit-2.3.0.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-//88mFWSJx8lxCzwdAABTJL2MyWB12+eIY7MDL2SqLmAkeKU9qxRvWuSyTjm3FUmpBEMuFfckAIqEaVGUDxb6w==\",\n          \"dev\": true,\n          \"requires\": \n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"p-try\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-try/-/p-try-2.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R4nPAVTAU0B9D35/Gk3uJf/7XYbQcyohSKdvAxIRSNghFl4e71hVoGnBNQz9cWaXxO2I10KTC+3jMdvvoKw6dQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"parse-json\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/parse-json/-/parse-json-5.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ayCKvm/phCGxOkYRSCM82iDwct8/EonSEgCSxWxD7ve6jHggsFl4fZVQBPRNgQoKiuV/odhFrGzQXZwbifC8Rg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.0.0\",\n        \"error-ex\": \"^1.3.1\",\n        \"json-parse-even-better-errors\": \"^2.3.0\",\n        \"lines-and-columns\": \"^1.1.6\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"path-exists\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-exists/-/path-exists-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ak9Qy5Q7jYb2Wwcey5Fpvg2KoAc/ZIhLSLOSBmRmygPsGwkVVt0fZa0qrtMz+m6tJTAHfZQ8FnmB4MG4LWy7/w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"path-is-absolute\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-is-absolute/-/path-is-absolute-1.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-AVbw3UJ2e9bq64vSaS9Am0fje1Pa8pbGqTTsmXfaIiMpnr5DlDhfJOuLj9Sf95ZPVDAUerDfEk88MPmPe7UCQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"path-key\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-key/-/path-key-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ojmeN0qd+y0jszEtoY48r0Peq5dwMEkIlCOu6Q5f41lfkswXuKtYrhgoTpLnyIcHm24Uhqx+5Tqm2InSwLhE6Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"path-parse\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-parse/-/path-parse-1.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LDJzPVEEEPR+y48z93A0Ed0yXb8pAByGWo/k5YYdYgpY2/2EsOsksJrq7lOHxryrVOn1ejG6oAp8ahvOIQD8sw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"picocolors\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/picocolors/-/picocolors-1.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xceH2snhtb5M9liqDsmEw56le376mTZkEX/jEb/RxNFyegNul7eNslCXP9FDj/Lcu0X8KEyMceP2ntpaHrDEVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"picomatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/picomatch/-/picomatch-2.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JU3teHTNjmE2VCGFzuY8EXzCDVwEqB2a8fsIvwaStHhAWJEeVd1o1QD80CU6+ZdEXXSLbSsuLwJjkCBWqRQUVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"pirates\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pirates/-/pirates-4.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TfySrs/5nm8fQJDcBDuUng3VOUKsd7S+zqvbOTiGXHfxX4wK31ard+hoNuvkicM/2YFzlpDgABOevKSsB4G/FA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"pkg-dir\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pkg-dir/-/pkg-dir-4.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-HRDzbaKjC+AOWVXxAU/x54COGeIv9eb+6CkDSQoNTt4XyWoIJvuPsXizxu/Fr23EiekbtZwmh1IcIG/l/a10GQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"pretty-format\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pretty-format/-/pretty-format-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Pdlw/oPxN+aXdmM9R00JVC9WVFoCLTKJvDVLgmJ+qAffBMxsV85l/Lu7sNx4zSzPyoL2euImuEwHhOXdEgNFZQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/schemas\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"react-is\": \"^18.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": {\n          \"version\": \"5.2.0\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-styles/-/ansi-styles-5.2.0.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-Cxwpt2SfTzTtXcfOlzGEee8O+c+MmUgGrNiBcXnuWxuFJHe6a5Hz7qwhwe5OgaSYI0IJvkLqWX1ASG+cJOkEiA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"prompts\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.4.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/prompts/-/prompts-2.4.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NxNv/kLguCA7p3jE8oL2aEBsrJWgAakBpgmgK6lpPWV+WuOmY6r2/zbAVnP+T8bQlA0nzHXSJSJW0Hq7ylaD2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"pure-rand\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pure-rand/-/pure-rand-6.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bVWawvoZoBYpp6yIoQtQXHZjmz35RSVHnUOTefl8Vcjr8snTPY1wnpSPMWekcFwbxI6gtmT7rSYPFvz71ldiOA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"react-is\": {\n      \"version\": \"18.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/react-is/-/react-is-18.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/LLMVyas0ljjAtoYiPqYiL8VWXzUUdThrmU5+n20DZv+a+ClRoevUzw5JxU+Ieh5/c87ytoTBV9G1FiKfNJdmg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"require-directory\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/require-directory/-/require-directory-2.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fGxEI7+wsG9xrvdjsrlmL22OMTTiHRwAMroiEeMgq8gzoLC/PQr7RsRDSTLUg/bZAZtF+TVIkHc6/4RIKrui+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"resolve\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.22.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve/-/resolve-1.22.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NPRy+/ncIMeDlTAsuqwKIiferiawhefFJtkNSW0qZJEqMEb+qBt/77B/jGeeek+F0uOeN05CDa6HXbbIgtVX4w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"is-core-module\": \"^2.16.0\",\n        \"path-parse\": \"^1.0.7\",\n        \"supports-preserve-symlinks-flag\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"resolve-cwd\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve-cwd/-/resolve-cwd-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OrZaX2Mb+rJCpH/6CpSqt9xFVpN++x01XnN2ie9g6P5/3xelLAkXWVADpdz1IHD/KFfEXyE6V0U01OQ3UO2rEg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"resolve-from\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve-from/-/resolve-from-5.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qYg9KP24dD5qka9J47d0aVky0N+b4fTU89LN9iDnjB5waksiC49rvMB0PrUJQGoTmH50XPiqOvAjDfaijGxYZw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"resolve.exports\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve.exports/-/resolve.exports-2.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OcXjMsGdhL4XnbShKpAcSqPMzQoYkYyhbEaeSko47MjRP9NfEQMhZkXL1DoFlt9LWQn4YttrdnV6X2OiyzBi+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-6.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BR7VvDCVHO+q2xBEWskxS6DJE1qRnb7DxzUrogb71CWoSficBxYsiAGd+Kl0mmq/MprG9yArRkyrQxTO6XjMzA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"shebang-command\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/shebang-command/-/shebang-command-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kHxr2zZpYtdmrN1qDjrrX/Z1rR1kG8Dx+gkpK1G4eXmvXswmcE1hTWBWYUzlraYw1/yZp6YuDY77YtvbN0dmDA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"shebang-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/shebang-regex/-/shebang-regex-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7++dFhtcx3353uBaq8DDR4NuxBetBzC7ZQOhmTQInHEd6bSrXdiEyzCvG07Z44UYdLShWUyXt5M/yhz8ekcb1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"signal-exit\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/signal-exit/-/signal-exit-3.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wnD2ZE+l+SPC/uoS0vXeE9L1+0wuaMqKlfz9AMUo38JsyLSBWSFcHR1Rri62LZc12vLr1gb3jl7iwQhgwpAbGQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"sisteransi\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/sisteransi/-/sisteransi-1.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bLGGlR1QxBcynn2d5YmDX4MGjlZvy2MRBDRNHLJ8VI6l6+9FUiyTFNJ0IveOSP0bcXgVDPRcfGqA0pjaqUpfVg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"slash\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/slash/-/slash-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-g9Q1haeby36OSStwb4ntCGGGaKsaVSjQ68fBxoQcutl5fS1vuY18H3wSt3jFyFtrkx+Kz0V1G85A4MyAdDMi2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.6.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/source-map/-/source-map-0.6.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UjgapumWlbMhkBgzT7Ykc5YXUT46F0iKu8SGXq0bcwP5dz/h0Plj6enJqjz1Zbq2l5WaqYnrVbwWOWMyF3F47g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"source-map-support\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.5.13\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/source-map-support/-/source-map-support-0.5.13.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-SHSKFHadjVA5oR4PPqhtAVdcBWwRYVd6g6cAXnIbRiIwc2EhPrTuKUBdSLvlEKyIP3GCf89fltvcZiP9MMFA1w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"buffer-from\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"source-map\": \"^0.6.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"sprintf-js\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/sprintf-js/-/sprintf-js-1.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-D9cPgkvLlV3t3IzL0D0YLvGA9Ahk4PcvVwUbN0dSGr1aP0Nrt4AEnTUbuGvquEC0mA64Gqt1fzirlRs5ibXx8g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"stack-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/stack-utils/-/stack-utils-2.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XlkWvfIm6RmsWtNJx+uqtKLS8eqFbxUg0ZzLXqY0caEy9l7hruX8IpiDnjsLavoBgqCCR71TqWO8MaXYheJ3RQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"string-length\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/string-length/-/string-length-4.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+l6rNN5fYHNhZZy41RXsYptCjA2Igmq4EG7kZAYFQI1E1VTXarr6ZPXBg6eq7Y6eK4FEhY6AJlyuFIb/v/S0VQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"char-regex\": \"^1.0.2\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"string-width\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/string-width/-/string-width-4.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wKyQRQpjJ0sIp62ErSZdGsjMJWsap5oRNihHhu6G7JVO/9jIB6UyevL+tXuOqrng8j/cxKTWyWUwvSTriiZz/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"emoji-regex\": \"^8.0.0\",\n        \"is-fullwidth-code-point\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"strip-ansi\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-ansi/-/strip-ansi-6.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Y38VPSHcqkFrCpFnQ9vuSXmquuv5oXOKpGeT6aGrr3o3Gc9AlVa6JBfUSOCnbxGGZF+/0ooI7KrPuUSztUdU5A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"strip-bom\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-bom/-/strip-bom-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3xurFv5tEgii33Zi8Jtp55wEIILR9eh34FAW00PZf+JnSsTmV/ioewSgQl97JHvgjoRGwPShsWm+IdrxB35d0w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"strip-final-newline\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-final-newline/-/strip-final-newline-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BrpvfNAE3dcvq7ll3xVumzjKjZQ5tI1sEUIKr3Uoks0XUl45St3FlatVqef9prk4jRDzhW6WZg+3bk93y6pLjA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"strip-json-comments\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-json-comments/-/strip-json-comments-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6fPc+R4ihwqP6N/aIv2f1gMH8lOVtWQHoqC4yK6oSDVVocumAsfCqjkXnqiYMhmMwS/mEHLp7Vehlt3ql6lEig==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"supports-color\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-color/-/supports-color-7.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qpCAvRl9stuOHveKsn7HncJRvv501qIacKzQlO/+Lwxc9+0q2wLyv4Dfvt80/DPn2pqOBsJdDiogXGR9+OvwRw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"supports-preserve-symlinks-flag\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag/-/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag-1.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ot0WnXS9fgdkgIcePe6RHNk1WA8+muPa6cSjeR3V8K27q9BB1rTE3R1p7Hv0z1ZyAc8s6Vvv8DIyWf681MAt0w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"test-exclude\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/test-exclude/-/test-exclude-6.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-cAGWPIyOHU6zlmg88jwm7VRyXnMN7iV68OGAbYDk/Mh/xC/pzVPlQtY6ngoIH/5/tciuhGfvESU8GrHrcxD56w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.4\",\n        \"minimatch\": \"^3.0.4\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"tmpl\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/tmpl/-/tmpl-1.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3f0uOEAQwIqGuWW2MVzYg8fV/QNnc/IpuJNG837rLuczAaLVHslWHZQj4IGiEl5Hs3kkbhwL9Ab7Hrsmuj+Smw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"to-regex-range\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/to-regex-range/-/to-regex-range-5.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-65P7iz6X5yEr1cwcgvQxbbIw7Uk3gOy5dIdtZ4rDveLqhrdJP+Li/Hx6tyK0NEb+2GCyneCMJiGqrADCSNk8sQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"type-detect\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/type-detect/-/type-detect-4.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0fr/mIH1dlO+x7TlcMy+bIDqKPsw/70tVyeHW787goQjhmqaZe10uwLujubK9q9Lg6Fiho1KUKDYz0Z7k7g5/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"type-fest\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.21.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/type-fest/-/type-fest-0.21.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-t0rzBq87m3fVcduHDUFhKmyyX+9eo6WQjZvf51Ea/M0Q7+T374Jp1aUiyUl0GKxp8M/OETVHSDvmkyPgvX+X2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"undici-types\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.21.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/undici-types/-/undici-types-6.21.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iwDZqg0QAGrg9Rav5H4n0M64c3mkR59cJ6wQp+7C4nI0gsmExaedaYLNO44eT4AtBBwjbTiGPMlt2Md0T9H9JQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"update-browserslist-db\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/update-browserslist-db/-/update-browserslist-db-1.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UxhIZQ+QInVdunkDAaiazvvT/+fXL5Osr0JZlJulepYu6Jd7qJtDZjlur0emRlT71EN3ScPoE7gvsuIKKNavKw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"v8-to-istanbul\": {\n      \"version\": \"9.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/v8-to-istanbul/-/v8-to-istanbul-9.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kiGUalWN+rgBJ/1OHZsBtU4rXZOfj/7rKQxULKlIzwzQSvMJUUNgPwJEEh7gU6xEVxC0ahoOBvN2YI8GH6FNgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.12\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.1\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"walker\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/walker/-/walker-1.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ts/8E8l5b7kY0vlWLewOkDXMmPdLcVV4GmOQLyxuSswIJsweeFZtAsMF7k1Nszz+TYBQrlYRmzOnr398y1JemQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"which\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/which/-/which-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BLI3Tl1TW3Pvl70l3yq3Y64i+awpwXqsGBYWkkqMtnbXgrMD+yj7rhW0kuEDxzJaYXGjEW5ogapKNMEKNMjibA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"wrap-ansi\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/wrap-ansi/-/wrap-ansi-7.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-YVGIj2kamLSTxw6NsZjoBxfSwsn0ycdesmc4p+Q21c5zPuZ1pl+NfxVdxPtdHvmNVOQ6XSYG4AUtyt/Fi7D16Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"wrappy\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/wrappy/-/wrappy-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-l4Sp/DRseor9wL6EvV2+TuQn63dMkPjZ/sp9XkghTEbV9KlPS1xUsZ3u7/IQO4wxtcFB4bgpQPRcR3QCvezPcQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"write-file-atomic\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/write-file-atomic/-/write-file-atomic-4.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7KxauUdBmSdWnmpaGFg+ppNjKF8uNLry8LyzjauQDOVONfFLNKrKvQOxZ/VuTIcS/gge/YNahf5RIIQWTSarlg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"imurmurhash\": \"^0.1.4\",\n        \"signal-exit\": \"^3.0.7\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"y18n\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/y18n/-/y18n-5.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0pfFzegeDWJHJIAmTLRP2DwHjdF5s7jo9tuztdQxAhINCdvS+3nGINqPd00AphqJR/0LhANUS6/+7SCb98YOfA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"yallist\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yallist/-/yallist-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-a4UGQaWPH59mOXUYnAG2ewncQS4i4F43Tv3JoAM+s2VDAmS9NsK8GpDMLrCHPksFT7h3K6TOoUNn2pb7RoXx4g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"yargs\": {\n      \"version\": \"17.7.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yargs/-/yargs-17.7.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7dSzzRQ++CKnNI/krKnYRV7JKKPUXMEh61soaHKg9mrWEhzFWhFnxPxGl+69cD1Ou63C13NUPCnmIcrvqCuM6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"cliui\": \"^8.0.1\",\n        \"escalade\": \"^3.1.1\",\n        \"get-caller-file\": \"^2.0.5\",\n        \"require-directory\": \"^2.1.1\",\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.2.3\",\n        \"y18n\": \"^5.0.5\",\n        \"yargs-parser\": \"^21.1.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"yargs-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"21.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yargs-parser/-/yargs-parser-21.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tVpsJW7DdjecAiFpbIB1e3qxIQsE6NoPc5/eTdrbbIC4h0LVsWhnoa3g+m2HclBIujHzsxZ4VJVA+GUuc2/LBw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"yocto-queue\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yocto-queue/-/yocto-queue-0.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-rVksvsnNCdJ/ohGc6xgPwyN8eheCxsiLM8mxuE/t/mOVqJewPuO1miLpTHQiRgTKCLexL4MeAFVagts7HmNZ2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    }\n  }\n}\n","file":"package-lock.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  println(\"Hello World\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() \n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.l\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.lo\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log()\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(H)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"H\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"He\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hel\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hell\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hello\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hello \")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hello W\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hello Wo\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hello Wor\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hello Word\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hello Worl\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hello World\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof(variable);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  o\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  ob\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  obj\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  obje\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  objec\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  object\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  obje\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  obj\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  ob\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  o\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  c\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  co\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  con\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  cons\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const o\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ob\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const obj\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const obj \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ob\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const o\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const t\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ty\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const typ\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const type\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ty\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const t\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ty\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const t\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const p\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  cons\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const t\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const t \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const c\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ch\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const che\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const chec\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const check\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const che\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ch\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const c\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const t\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ty\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ty \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ty =\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ty = \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ty ={}\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ty =\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ty =\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ty = \n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const showAllTypes = require('../../exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker');\n\ndescribe('Show All Types function', () => {\n  test('should return an object with all the types', () => {\n    const result = showAllTypes();\n    \n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('object');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('array');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('string');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('number');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('boolean');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('null');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('undefined');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('nan');\n    \n    expect(result.object).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.array).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.string).toBe('string');\n    expect(result.number).toBe('number');\n    expect(result.boolean).toBe('boolean');\n    expect(result.null).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.undefined).toBe('undefined');\n    expect(result.nan).toBe('number');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex2.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ty = \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ty =\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ty =\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ty\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const \n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const check\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const t \n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const t\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const \n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  cons\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const \n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const p\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ty\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const \n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const t\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const ty\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const type\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const \n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const obj \n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const obj\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  const\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  object\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof(variable);\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof(variable );\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof(var);\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof();\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof()\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typ\n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n  }\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\\\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  \n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  c\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  co\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  con\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  cons\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const \n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const n\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const na\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam \n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam =\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = \n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = c\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = co\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = con\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = conf\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confi\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confir\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm \n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm ()\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm()\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm \n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm ()\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm ( )\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (n)\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (na)\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (nam)\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (name)\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (na)\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (n)\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm ()\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (N)\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (Na)\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (Nam)\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (Name)\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (Name?)\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (Name? )\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (Name)\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (Nam)\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (Na)\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (N)\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm ()\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"\")\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"N\")\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Na\")\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Nam\")\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name\")\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\")\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\",)\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\", )\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\")\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(n+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(na+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam+\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\"!\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const showAllTypes = require('../../exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker');\n\ndescribe('Show All Types function', () => {\n  test('should return an object with all the types', () => {\n    const result = showAllTypes();\n    \n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('object');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('array');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('string');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('number');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('boolean');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('null');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('undefined');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('nan');\n    \n    expect(result.object).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.array).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.string).toBe('string');\n    expect(result.number).toBe('number');\n    expect(result.boolean).toBe('boolean');\n    expect(result.null).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.undefined).toBe('undefined');\n    expect(result.nan).toBe('number');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex2.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam. +\" !\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.u +\" !\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.up +\" !\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.up= +\" !\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.up== +\" !\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.up +\" !\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.u +\" !\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam. +\" !\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?.\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n  \"\"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n  \"d\"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n  \"de\"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n  \"des\"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n  \"dess\"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n  \"de\"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n  \"dee\"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n  \"deez\"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n  \"deezz\"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n  \"deez z\"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n  \"deez nz\"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n  \"deez nuz\"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n  \"deez nutz\"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n  \"deez nutsz\"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n  \"deez nuts.z\"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n  \"deez nutsz.\"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam +\" !\")\n  \"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam. +\" !\")\n  \"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.t +\" !\")\n  \"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.to +\" !\")\n  \"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toU +\" !\")\n  \"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUp +\" !\")\n  \"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpp +\" !\")\n  \"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUppe +\" !\")\n  \"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpper +\" !\")\n  \"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperC +\" !\")\n  \"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperCa +\" !\")\n  \"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperCas +\" !\")\n  \"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperCase +\" !\")\n  \"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperCase +\" !\");\n  \"\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"const showAllTypes = require('../../exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker');\n\ndescribe('Show All Types function', () => {\n  test('should return an object with all the types', () => {\n    const result = showAllTypes();\n    \n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('object');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('array');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('string');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('number');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('boolean');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('null');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('undefined');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('nan');\n    \n    expect(result.object).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.array).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.string).toBe('string');\n    expect(result.number).toBe('number');\n    expect(result.boolean).toBe('boolean');\n    expect(result.null).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.undefined).toBe('undefined');\n    expect(result.nan).toBe('number');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex2.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const screamName = require('../../exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer');\n\ndescribe('Name Screamer function', () => {\n  test('should convert name to uppercase and add exclamation marks', () => {\n    expect(screamName('john')).toBe('JOHN!!!');\n    expect(screamName('Sarah')).toBe('SARAH!!!');\n    expect(screamName('bob smith')).toBe('BOB SMITH!!!');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex6.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperCase +\" !\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperCase +\" !!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperCase +\" !!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperCase +\"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const screamName = require('../../exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer');\n\ndescribe('Name Screamer function', () => {\n  test('should convert name to uppercase and add exclamation marks', () => {\n    expect(screamName('john')).toBe('JOHN!!!');\n    expect(screamName('Sarah')).toBe('SARAH!!!');\n    expect(screamName('bob smith')).toBe('BOB SMITH!!!');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex6.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperCase +\"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = confirm (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam =  (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = P (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = Pr (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = Pro (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = Prom (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = Promp (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = Prompt (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"Name?\",);\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", );\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", '');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"Name?\",' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const showAllTypes = require('../../exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker');\n\ndescribe('Show All Types function', () => {\n  test('should return an object with all the types', () => {\n    const result = showAllTypes();\n    \n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('object');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('array');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('string');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('number');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('boolean');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('null');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('undefined');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('nan');\n    \n    expect(result.object).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.array).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.string).toBe('string');\n    expect(result.number).toBe('number');\n    expect(result.boolean).toBe('boolean');\n    expect(result.null).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.undefined).toBe('undefined');\n    expect(result.nan).toBe('number');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex2.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const screamName = require('../../exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer');\n\ndescribe('Name Screamer function', () => {\n  test('should convert name to uppercase and add exclamation marks', () => {\n    expect(screamName('john')).toBe('JOHN!!!');\n    expect(screamName('Sarah')).toBe('SARAH!!!');\n    expect(screamName('bob smith')).toBe('BOB SMITH!!!');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex6.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"?\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"screamName\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"creamName\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"ScreamName\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"ScreamName?\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!\");\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"7:00:13 PM [info] Activating VS Code Recorder\n7:00:15 PM [info] Recording started\n","file":"extension-output-MattiaConsiglio.vs-code-recorder-#1-VS Code Recorder","language":"Log"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + \"!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + !!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const screamName = require('../../exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer');\n\ndescribe('Name Screamer function', () => {\n  test('should convert name to uppercase and add exclamation marks', () => {\n    expect(screamName('john')).toBe('JOHN!!!');\n    expect(screamName('Sarah')).toBe('SARAH!!!');\n    expect(screamName('bob smith')).toBe('BOB SMITH!!!');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex6.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const screamName = require('../../exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer');\n\ndescribe('Name Screamer function', () => {\n  test('should convert name to uppercase and add exclamation marks', () => {\n    expect(screamName('john')).toBe('JOHN!!!');\n    expect(screamName('Sarah')).toBe('SARAH!!!');\n    expect(screamName('bob smith')).toBe('BOB SMITH!!!');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex6.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  cons nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  con nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  co nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n  c nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   name = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(nam.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   name = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(nam.etoUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   name = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const screamName = require('../../exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer');\n\ndescribe('Name Screamer function', () => {\n  test('should convert name to uppercase and add exclamation marks', () => {\n    expect(screamName('john')).toBe('JOHN!!!');\n    expect(screamName('Sarah')).toBe('SARAH!!!');\n    expect(screamName('bob smith')).toBe('BOB SMITH!!!');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex6.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"## Instructions\n\n1. Install dependencies:\n   ```\n   npm install\n   ```\n\n2. Run tests for all exercises:\n   ```\n   npm test\n   ```\n\n3. Run tests by difficulty level:\n   ```\n   npm run test:easy\n   npm run test:medium\n   npm run test:hard\n   ```\n\n4. Run tests for a specific file:\n   ```\n   npx jest tests/easy/ex1.test.js\n   ```\n\nComplete the functions, run the test, and make sure they all pass. Then zip up the entire folder and send it to me via discord.\n","file":"README.md","language":"markdown"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   name = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   na = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   n = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   c = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   co = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   con = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   cons = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const  = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const n = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const na = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   \n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   n\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   na\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   nam\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name \n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name =\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = \n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = n\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = na\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.t\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.to\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.tou\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase \n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase +\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + \n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + ''\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase +\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + \n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + ''\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!'\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!'\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!'\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  return(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  return(name);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  return(name);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const screamName = require('../../exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer');\n\ndescribe('Name Screamer function', () => {\n  test('should convert name to uppercase and add exclamation marks', () => {\n    expect(screamName('john')).toBe('JOHN!!!');\n    expect(screamName('Sarah')).toBe('SARAH!!!');\n    expect(screamName('bob smith')).toBe('BOB SMITH!!!');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex6.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const showAllTypes = require('../../exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker');\n\ndescribe('Show All Types function', () => {\n  test('should return an object with all the types', () => {\n    const result = showAllTypes();\n    \n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('object');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('array');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('string');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('number');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('boolean');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('null');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('undefined');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('nan');\n    \n    expect(result.object).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.array).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.string).toBe('string');\n    expect(result.number).toBe('number');\n    expect(result.boolean).toBe('boolean');\n    expect(result.null).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.undefined).toBe('undefined');\n    expect(result.nan).toBe('number');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex2.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    t\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    ty\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typ\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    type\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeo\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5\n    t\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5\n    ty\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5\n    typ\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5\n    type\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5\n    type \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5\n    type ''\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5\n    type 'o'\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5\n    type 'ok'\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5\n    typeo 'ok'\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5\n    typeof 'ok'\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5\n    typeof 'ok';\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    t\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    ty\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    tyy\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typy\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typey\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeoy\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeofy\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof []y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];\\y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];\n    y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];\n    ty\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];\n    tyy\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];\n    typy\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];\n    typey\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];\n    type y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];\n    type oy\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];\n    typey\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];\n    typeoy\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];\n    typeofy\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];\n    typeof y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];\n    typeof {}y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];\n    typeof {};y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    \n  typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];\n    typeof {};y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    \n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];\n    typeof {};y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];\n    typeof {};y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};typeof {};\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];\n    typeof {};y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  typeof {};typeof {};\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof [];\n    typeof {};y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};typeof {};\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typetypeof {};y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};typeof {};\n    typeof 5;\n    typeoftypetypeof {};y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof {};\n    typeof 5;\n    typeoftypetypeof {};y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n     typeof [];typeof {};\n    typeof 5;\n    typeoftypetypeof {};y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n     typeof []; typeof [];typeof {};\n    typeof 5;\n    typeoftypetypeof {};y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof []; typeof [];typeof {};\n    typeof 5;\n    typeoftypetypeof {};y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof []; typeof [];typeof ;y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n     typeof [];typeof ;y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok'; typeof [];typeof ;y\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   const nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  return(name);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   cons nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  return(name);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   con nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  return(name);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   co nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  return(name);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   c nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  return(name);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  return(name);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   l nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  return(name);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   le nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  return(name);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  return(name);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const showAllTypes = require('../../exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker');\n\ndescribe('Show All Types function', () => {\n  test('should return an object with all the types', () => {\n    const result = showAllTypes();\n    \n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('object');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('array');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('string');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('number');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('boolean');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('null');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('undefined');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('nan');\n    \n    expect(result.object).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.array).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.string).toBe('string');\n    expect(result.number).toBe('number');\n    expect(result.boolean).toBe('boolean');\n    expect(result.null).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.undefined).toBe('undefined');\n    expect(result.nan).toBe('number');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex2.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof u\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof un\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof und\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof unde\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undef\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefi\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefin\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefind\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefine\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    t\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    ty\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typ\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    type\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeo\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof N\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof Na\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof Nan\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof NaN\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof NaN;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    \n  typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof NaN;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof NaN;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  \n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof NaN;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  l\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof NaN;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  le\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof NaN;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  lef\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof NaN;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof NaN;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let \n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof NaN;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let o\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof NaN;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let ob\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof NaN;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof NaN;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj \n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof NaN;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj =\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof NaN;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj ={}\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof NaN;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = {}\n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof NaN;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = \n    typeof {};\n    typeof [];\n    typeof 'ok';\n    typeof 5;\n    typeof false;\n    typeof null;\n    typeof undefined;\n    typeof NaN;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = \n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = \n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = \n  }\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ''\n  }\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ;\n  }\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ;\n    \n  }\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ;\n\n  }\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ;\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = \n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    \n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    a\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    ar\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr:\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr:[]\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: \n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: []\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    \n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    n\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    nn\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    nun\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    numn\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num:n\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num: n\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num: 5n\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num: 5,n\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num: 5,\n    n\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num: 5,\n    bn\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num: 5,\n    bon\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num: 5,\n    boon\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num: 5,\n    boo;n\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num: 5,\n    boo:n\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num: 5,\n    boo: n\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num: 5,\n    boo: fn\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num: 5,\n    boo: fan\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num: 5,\n    boo: faln\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num: 5,\n    boo: falen\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num: 5,\n    boo: fal\n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num: 5,\n    boo: fal\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num: 5,\n    boo: fals\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    \n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    s\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    st\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    si\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig;\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig:\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig:  \n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig:  \"\"\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"\"\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"t\"\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"th\"\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"thi\"\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this\"\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this \"\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this i\"\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is\"\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is \"\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a\"\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a \"\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a s\"\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a st\"\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a str\"\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a stri\"\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a strin\"\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\"\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    \n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    nu\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    nul\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    null\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    null:\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    nul\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    nu\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    \n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n \n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n :\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : \n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : nu\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : nul\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    \n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    u\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    un\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und \n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und :\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : \n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : u\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : un\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : und\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : unde\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined;\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined.\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined.arr\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined.ar\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined.a\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined.\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined.    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n        ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    a    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an;    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an:    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an:     ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: N    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: Na    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n  ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n  \n  ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n  \n\n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n    ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n  t  ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n  ty  ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n  typ  ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n  type  ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n  type   ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n  type o  ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n  type of  ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n  type   ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n  type  ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n  typeo  ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n  typeof  ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n  typeof   ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n  typeof ()  ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n  typeof (o)  ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n  typeof (ob)  ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n  typeof (obj)  ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n  typeof (obj);  ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n  typeof obj);  ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN   \n \n  typeof obj;  ","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n r typeof obj;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n re typeof obj;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n ret typeof obj;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n retu typeof obj;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n retur typeof obj;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n return typeof obj;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n return  typeof obj;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n return () typeof obj;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n return  (typeof obj;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n return  (typeof obj;)\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n return  (typeof obj)\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n return  (typeof obj);\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n return (typeof obj);\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n return(typeof obj);\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n return(typeof obj.);\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n return(typeof obj.g);\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n return(typeof obj.ge);\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n return(typeof obj.get);\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n return(typeof obj.g);\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n return(typeof obj.);\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n return(typeof obj);\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n returntypeof obj.);\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n returtypeof obj.);\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n retutypeof obj.);\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n rettypeof obj.);\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n retypeof obj.);\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n rtypeof obj.);\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n typeof obj.);\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n typeof obj.)\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n typeof obj.\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n typeof obj.i\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n typeof obj.in\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n typeof obj.inb\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n typeof obj.inbb\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n typeof obj.inbnb\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n typeof obj.inb\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n typeof obj.inbb\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n typeof obj.inbjb\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n typeof obj.inb\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n typeof obj.injb\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n typeof obj.ib\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n typeof obj.ibb\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n typeof obj.ibjb\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibjb\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.a;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ar;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.s;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.si;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.nu;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.b;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.bo;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.u;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.un;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.ibj;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.a;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;b\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  return(name);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  (name);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  console.log(name);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  console.logconsole.log(name);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   console.logconsole.log(name);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   console.log(name);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ' );\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\", ');\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\", );\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\",);\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   r\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   re\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   reu\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   reut\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   reutn\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   reutnr\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   reutnr \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   reutn\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   reut\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   reutr\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   reutrn\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   reutrn \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   reutr\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   reut\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   reu\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   re\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   ret\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   retu\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   retur\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return \n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return ()\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (n)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (na)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (nae)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (nam)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (name)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (name);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let  = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (name);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let n = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (name);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let ns = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (name);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nsm = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (name);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nsme = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (name);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let ns = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (name);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let n = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (name);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let na = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (name);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (name);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let name = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (name);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let namee = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (name);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let namewe = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (name);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    namee = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (name);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    namee = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (nam.e);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    namee = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (nam.te);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    namee = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (nam.toe);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    namee = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (nam.toUpperCasee);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    namee = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (nam.toUpperCase e);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    namee = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (nam.toUpperCase +e);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    namee = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (nam.toUpperCase + e);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    namee = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (nam.toUpperCase + ''e);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    namee = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (nam.toUpperCase + '!'e);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    namee = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (nam.toUpperCase + '!!'e);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    namee = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (nam.toUpperCase + '!!!'e);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    namee = prompt (\"Name?\");\n  ;\n   return (nam.toUpperCase + '!!!'e);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    namee = prompt (\"Name?\");\n ;\n   return (nam.toUpperCase + '!!!'e);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    namee = prompt (\"Name?\");;\n   return (nam.toUpperCase + '!!!'e);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    namee = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   return (nam.toUpperCase + '!!!'e);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    namee = prompt (\"Name?\";\n   return (nam.toUpperCase + '!!!'e);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    namee = prompt (\"Name?\";;\n   return (nam.toUpperCase + '!!!'e);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   return (name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt (\"?\");\n   return (name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt (\"?);\n   return (name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt (\");\n   return (name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt ();\n   return (name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   return (name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n    (name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   c (name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   co (name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   con (name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   cons (name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   conso (name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   consol (name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   console (name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   console. (name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   console.l (name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   console.lo (name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   console.log (name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   console.log(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   console.log(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   .log(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   .lo(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   .l(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   .(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   (name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   r(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   ru(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rut(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rutt(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rutnt(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rutet(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rutent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rutt(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rut(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rutut(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   ruturt(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   ruturnt(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rut(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rutent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rutentent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rutententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rutentententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rutententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rutentententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rutententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rutentententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rutententententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rutentententententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   ruttententententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   rutntententententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   tententententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   .logtententententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   console.logtententententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   console.log tententententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   console tententententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n    tententententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt();\n   return tententententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt ();\n   return tententententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt (\"?\");\n   return tententententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   return tententententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt (\"Name?\")\n   return tententententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt (\"Name?\");\n\n   return tententententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return tententententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return tentententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return tententententententeent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return tententententententent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return tentententententeent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return tente.toent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n    name = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return tenteent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let name = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return tenteent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return tenteent(name.toUpperCase + '!!!');\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  i\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if w\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if wi\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if wid\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if widt\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if width\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if width>\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if width>h\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if width>he\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if width>hei\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if width>h\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if width>he\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if width>hei\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if width>heig\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if width>heigh\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if width>height\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if width>height)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if (width>height)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if (width>height)\n    \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if (width>height)\n    {}\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if (width>height)\n    {}{}\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if (width>height)\n  {}{}\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if (width>height)\n  {}\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if (width >height)\n  {}\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if (width > height)\n  {}\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if (width > height)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function checkResolution(width, height) {\n  // Return \"landscape\" if width is greater than height\n  // Return \"portrait\" if height is greater than or equal to width\n  if (width > height)\n  \n  }\n}\n\nmodule.exports = checkResolution;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex3-resolution-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() \n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n  \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  r\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  re\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  ret\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  retu\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  retur\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return M\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Ma\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Mat\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.R\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.r\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.ra\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.rad\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.rado\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.radom\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.rad\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.ra\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.ran\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.rand\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.rando\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random()\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random(1)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random(1-)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random(1,)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random(1,6)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random:(1,6)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random (1,6)\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random (1,6);\n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\ns\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nst\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nstr\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\ns\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\ni\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nin\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nint\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\ni\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nf\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nff\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfof\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nforf\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor()f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(in)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(int)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(int )f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(int =)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(int = )f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(int = 0)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(int = 0 )f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(int = )f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(int =)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(int )f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(int)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(in)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i )f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i =)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = )f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0 )f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0;)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; )f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i )f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i <)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i >)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > )f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > s)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > st)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > str)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > str.)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > str.l)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > str.le)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > str.len)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > str.leng)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > str.lengt)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > str.length)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > str.length;)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > str.length; )f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > str.length; i)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > str.length; i+)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > str.length; i++)f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > str.length; i++){}f\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (name);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return (name;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return name;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random (1,6);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > str.length; i++)\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random (1,6);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"lockfileVersion\": 2,\n  \"requires\": true,\n  \"packages\": {\n    \"\": {\n      \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"license\": \"ISC\",\n      \"devDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@ampproject/remapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@ampproject/remapping/-/remapping-2.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-30iZtAPgz+LTIYoeivqYo853f02jBYSd5uGnGpkFV0M3xOt9aN73erkgYAmZU43x4VfqcnLxW9Kpg3R5LC4YYw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": \"^0.3.5\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.24\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/code-frame\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/code-frame/-/code-frame-7.26.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RJlIHRueQgwWitWgF8OdFYGZX328Ax5BCemNGlqHfplnRT9ESi8JkFlvaVYbS+UubVY6dpv87Fs2u5M29iNFVQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"js-tokens\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"picocolors\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/compat-data\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/compat-data/-/compat-data-7.26.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-oH5UPLMWR3L2wEFLnFJ1TZXqHufiTKAiLfqw5zkhS4dKXLJ10yVztfil/twG8EDTA4F/tvVNw9nOl4ZMslB8rQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/core\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/core/-/core-7.26.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-vMqyb7XCDMPvJFFOaT9kxtiRh42GwlZEg1/uIgtZshS5a/8OaduUfCi7kynKgc3Tw/6Uo2D+db9qBttghhmxwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@ampproject/remapping\": \"^2.2.0\",\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/helper-compilation-targets\": \"^7.26.5\",\n        \"@babel/helper-module-transforms\": \"^7.26.0\",\n        \"@babel/helpers\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.26.9\",\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"debug\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"gensync\": \"^1.0.0-beta.2\",\n        \"json5\": \"^2.2.3\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": {\n        \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n        \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/babel\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/generator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/generator/-/generator-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-VybsKvpiN1gU1sdMZIp7FcqphVVKEwcuj02x73uvcHE0PTihx1nlBcowYWhDwjpoAXRv43+gDzyggGnn1XZhVw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": \"^0.3.5\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.25\",\n        \"jsesc\": \"^3.0.2\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-compilation-targets\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-compilation-targets/-/helper-compilation-targets-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LVk7fbXml0H2xH34dFzKQ7TDZ2G4/rVTOrq9V+icbbadjbVxxeFeDsNHv2SrZeWoA+6ZiTyWYWtScEIW07EAcA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/compat-data\": \"^7.26.8\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-option\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"browserslist\": \"^4.24.0\",\n        \"lru-cache\": \"^5.1.1\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-module-imports\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-module-imports/-/helper-module-imports-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tnUA4RsrmflIM6W6RFTLFSXITtl0wKjgpnLgXyowocVPrbYrLUXSBXDgTs8BlbmIzIdlBySRQjINYs2BAkiLtw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-module-transforms\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-module-transforms/-/helper-module-transforms-7.26.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xO+xu6B5K2czEnQye6BHA7DolFFmS3LB7stHZFaOLb1pAwO1HWLS8fXA+eh0A2yIvltPVmx3eNNDBJA2SLHXFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-module-imports\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-plugin-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-plugin-utils/-/helper-plugin-utils-7.26.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RS+jZcRdZdRFzMyr+wcsaqOmld1/EqTghfaBGQQd/WnRdzdlvSZ//kF7U8VQTxf1ynZ4cjUcYgjVGx13ewNPMg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-string-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-string-parser/-/helper-string-parser-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-4A/SCr/2KLd5jrtOMFzaKjVtAei3+2r/NChoBNoZ3EyP/+GlhoaEGoWOZUmFmoITP7zOJyHIMm+DYRd8o3PvHA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-validator-identifier/-/helper-validator-identifier-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Ed61U6XJc3CVRfkERJWDz4dJwKe7iLmmJsbOGu9wSloNSFttHV0I8g6UAgb7qnK5ly5bGLPd4oXZlxCdANBOWQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-validator-option\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-validator-option/-/helper-validator-option-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-e/zv1co8pp55dNdEcCynfj9X7nyUKUXoUEwfXqaZt0omVOmDe9oOTdKStH4GmAw6zxMFs50ZayuMfHDKlO7Tfw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helpers\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helpers/-/helpers-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-U5eyP/CTFPuNE3qk+WZMxFkp/4zUzdceQlfzf7DdGdhp+Fezd7HD+i8Y24ZuTMKX3wQBld449jijbGq6OdGNQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/parser/-/parser-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iaepho73/2Pz7w2eMS0Q5f83+0RKI7i4xmiYeBmDzfRVbQtTOG7Ts0S4HzJVsTMGI9keU8rNfuZr8DKfSt7Yyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators/-/plugin-syntax-async-generators-7.8.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tycmZxkGfZaxhMRbXlPXuVFpdWlXpir2W4AMhSJgRKzk/eDlIXOhb2LHWoLpDF7TEHylV5zNhykX6KAgHJmTNw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint/-/plugin-syntax-bigint-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wnTnFlG+YxQm3vDxpGE57Pj0srRU4sHE/mDkt1qv2YJJSeUAec2ma4WLUnUPeKjyrfntVwe/N6dCXpU+zL3Npg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.12.13\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties/-/plugin-syntax-class-properties-7.12.13.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fm4idjKla0YahUNgFNLCB0qySdsoPiZP3iQE3rky0mBUtMZ23yDJ9SJdg6dXTSDnulOVqiF3Hgr9nbXvXTQZYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block/-/plugin-syntax-class-static-block-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-b+YyPmr6ldyNnM6sqYeMWE+bgJcJpO6yS4QD7ymxgH34GBPNDM/THBh8iunyvKIZztiwLH4CJZ0RxTk9emgpjw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes/-/plugin-syntax-import-attributes-7.26.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-e2dttdsJ1ZTpi3B9UYGLw41hifAubg19AtCu/2I/F1QNVclOBr1dYpTdmdyZ84Xiz43BS/tCUkMAZNLv12Pi+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta/-/plugin-syntax-import-meta-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Yqfm+XDx0+Prh3VSeEQCPU81yC+JWZ2pDPFSS4ZdpfZhp4MkFMaDC1UqseovEKwSUpnIL7+vK+Clp7bfh0iD7g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings/-/plugin-syntax-json-strings-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lY6kdGpWHvjoe2vk4WrAapEuBR69EMxZl+RoGRhrFGNYVK8mOPAW8VfbT/ZgrFbXlDNiiaxQnAtgVCZ6jv30EA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx/-/plugin-syntax-jsx-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ld6oezHQMZsZfp6pWtbjaNDF2tiiCYYDqQszHt5VV437lewP9aSi2Of99CK0D0XB21k7FLgnLcmQKyKzynfeAA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators/-/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-d8waShlpFDinQ5MtvGU9xDAOzKH47+FFoney2baFIoMr952hKOLp1HR7VszoZvOsV/4+RRszNY7D17ba0te0ig==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator/-/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-aSff4zPII1u2QD7y+F8oDsz19ew4IGEJg9SVW+bqwpwtfFleiQDMdzA/R+UlWDzfnHFCxxleFT0PMIrR36XLNQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator/-/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9H6YdfkcK/uOnY/K7/aA2xpzaAgkQn37yzWUMRK7OaPOqOpGS1+n0H5hxT9AUw9EsSjPW8SVyMJwYRtWs3X3ug==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread/-/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XoqMijGZb9y3y2XskN+P1wUGiVwWZ5JmoDRwx5+3GmEplNyVM2s2Dg8ILFQm8rWM48orGy5YpI5Bl8U1y7ydlA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding/-/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6VPD0Pc1lpTqw0aKoeRTMiB+kWhAoT24PA+ksWSBrFtl5SIRVpZlwN3NNPQjehA2E/91FV3RjLWoVTglWcSV3Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining/-/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KoK9ErH1MBlCPxV0VANkXW2/dw4vlbGDrFgz8bmUsBGYkFRcbRwMh6cIJubdPrkxRwuGdtCk0v/wPTKbQgBjkg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object/-/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0wVnp9dxJ72ZUJDV27ZfbSj6iHLoytYZmh3rFcxNnvsJF3ktkzLDZPy/mA17HGsaQT3/DQsWYX1f1QGWkCoVUg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await/-/plugin-syntax-top-level-await-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hx++upLv5U1rgYfwe1xBQUhRmU41NEvpUvrp8jkrSCdvGSnM5/qdRMtylJ6PG5OFkBaHkbTAKTnd3/YyESRHFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript/-/plugin-syntax-typescript-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hjMgRy5hb8uJJjUcdWunWVcoi9bGpJp8p5Ol1229PoN6aytsLwNMgmdftO23wnCLMfVmTwZDWMPNq/D1SY60JQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/template\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/template/-/template-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2ncevenBqXI6qRMukPlXwHKHchC7RyMuu4xv5JBXRfOGVcTy1mXCD12qrp7Jsoxll1EV3+9sE4GugBVRjT2jFA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/traverse\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/traverse/-/traverse-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-19lYZFzYVQkkHkl4Cy4WrAVcqBkgvV2YM2TU3xG6DIwO7O3ecbDPfW3yM3bjAGcqcQHi+CCtjMR3dIEHxsd6bA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"debug\": \"^4.3.1\",\n        \"globals\": \"^11.1.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/types\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/types/-/types-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-H45s8fVLYjbhFH62dIJ3WtmJ6RSPt/3DRO0ZcT2SUiYiQyz3BLVb9ADEnLl91m74aQPS3AzzeajZHYOalWe3bg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-string-parser\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@bcoe/v8-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@bcoe/v8-coverage/-/v8-coverage-0.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0hYQ8SB4Db5zvZB4axdMHGwEaQjkZzFjQiN9LVYvIFB2nSUHW9tYpxWriPrWDASIxiaXax83REcLxuSdnGPZtw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config/-/load-nyc-config-1.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-VjeHSlIzpv/NyD3N0YuHfXOPDIixcA1q2ZV98wsMqcYlPmv2n3Yb2lYP9XMElnaFVXg5A7YLTeLu6V84uQDjmQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"camelcase\": \"^5.3.1\",\n        \"find-up\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"get-package-type\": \"^0.1.0\",\n        \"js-yaml\": \"^3.13.1\",\n        \"resolve-from\": \"^5.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@istanbuljs/schema\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@istanbuljs/schema/-/schema-0.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ZXRY4jNvVgSVQ8DL3LTcakaAtXwTVUxE81hslsyD2AtoXW/wVob10HkOJ1X/pAlcI7D+2YoZKg5do8G/w6RYgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/console\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/console/-/console-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-5Ni4CU7XHQi32IJ398EEP4RrB8eV09sXP2ROqD4bksHrnTree52PsxvX8tpL8LvTZ3pFzXyPbNQReSN41CAhOg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/core\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/core/-/core-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-n7aeXWKMnGtDA48y8TLWJPJmLmmZ642Ceo78cYWEpiD7FzDgmNDV/GCVRorPABdXLJZ/9wzzgZAlHjXjxDHGsg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/reporters\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"ansi-escapes\": \"^4.2.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-changed-files\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-resolve-dependencies\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runner\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-watcher\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/environment\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/environment/-/environment-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-aQIfHDq33ExsN4jP1NWGXhxgQ/wixs60gDiKO+XVMd8Mn0NWPWgc34ZQDTb2jKaUWQ7MuwoitXAsN2XVXNMpAw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/expect\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/expect/-/expect-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-8uMeAMycttpva3P1lBHB8VciS9V0XAr3GymPpipdyQXbBcuhkLQOSe8E/p92RyAdToS6ZD1tFkX+CkhoECE0dQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/expect-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/expect-utils/-/expect-utils-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GlsNBWiFQFCVi9QVSx7f5AgMeLxe9YCCs5PuP2O2LdjDAA8Jh9eX7lA1Jq/xdXw3Wb3hyvlFNfZIfcRetSzYcA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/fake-timers\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/fake-timers/-/fake-timers-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-q4DH1Ha4TTFPdxLsqDXK1d3+ioSL7yL5oCMJZgDYm6i+6CygW5E5xVr/D1HdsGxjt1ZWSfUAs9OxSB/BNelWrQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@sinonjs/fake-timers\": \"^10.0.2\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/globals\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/globals/-/globals-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-mpiz3dutLbkW2MNFubUGUEVLkTGiqW6yLVTA+JbP6fI6J5iL9Y0Nlg8k95pcF8ctKwCS7WVxteBs29hhfAotzQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/reporters\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/reporters/-/reporters-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DApq0KJbJOEzAFYjHADNNxAE3KbhxQB1y5Kplb5Waqw6zVbuWatSnMjE5gs8FUgEPmNsnZA3NCWl9NG0ia04Pg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@bcoe/v8-coverage\": \"^0.2.3\",\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-report\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-source-maps\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-reports\": \"^3.1.3\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"string-length\": \"^4.0.1\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"v8-to-istanbul\": \"^9.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/schemas\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/schemas/-/schemas-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-mo5j5X+jIZmJQveBKeS/clAueipV7KgiX1vMgCxam1RNYiqE1w62n0/tJJnHtjW8ZHcQco5gY85jA3mi0L+nSA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/source-map/-/source-map-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MHjT95QuipcPrpLM+8JMSzFx6eHp5Bm+4XeFDJlwsvVBjmKNiIAvasGK2fxz2WbGRlnvqehFbh07MMa7n3YJnw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"callsites\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/test-result\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/test-result/-/test-result-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Fdx+tv6x1zlkJPcWXmMDAG2HBnaR9XPSd5aDWQVsfrZmLVT3lU1cwyxLgRmXR9yrq4NBoEm9BMsfgFzTQAbJYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/test-sequencer\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/test-sequencer/-/test-sequencer-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GQwJ5WZVrKnOJuiYiAF52UNUJXgTZx1NHjFSEB0qEMmSZKAkdMoIzw/Cj6x6NF4AvV23AUqDpFzQkN/eYCYTxw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/transform\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/transform/-/transform-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ok/BTPFzFKVMwO5eOHRrvnBVHdRy9IrsrW1GpMaQ9MCnilNLXQKmAX8s1YXDFaai9xJpac2ySzV0YeRRECr2Vw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": \"^6.1.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"fast-json-stable-stringify\": \"^2.1.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pirates\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"write-file-atomic\": \"^4.0.2\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/types\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/types/-/types-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-u3UPsIilWKOM3F9CXtrG8LEJmNxwoCQC/XVj4IKYXvvpx7QIi/Kg1LI5uDmDpKlac62NUtX7eLjRh+jVZcLOzw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/schemas\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-reports\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/yargs\": \"^17.0.8\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.3.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/gen-mapping/-/gen-mapping-0.3.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-imAbBGkb+ebQyxKgzv5Hu2nmROxoDOXHh80evxdoXNOrvAnVx7zimzc1Oo5h9RlfV4vPXaE2iM5pOFbvOCClWA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/set-array\": \"^1.2.1\",\n        \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": \"^1.4.10\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.24\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/resolve-uri\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/resolve-uri/-/resolve-uri-3.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bRISgCIjP20/tbWSPWMEi54QVPRZExkuD9lJL+UIxUKtwVJA8wW1Trb1jMs1RFXo1CBTNZ/5hpC9QvmKWdopKw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/set-array\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/set-array/-/set-array-1.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R8gLRTZeyp03ymzP/6Lil/28tGeGEzhx1q2k703KGWRAI1VdvPIXdG70VJc2pAMw3NA6JKL5hhFu1sJX0Mnn/A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec/-/sourcemap-codec-1.5.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gv3ZRaISU3fjPAgNsriBRqGWQL6quFx04YMPW/zD8XMLsU32mhCCbfbO6KZFLjvYpCZ8zyDEgqsgf+PwPaM7GQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.3.25\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/trace-mapping/-/trace-mapping-0.3.25.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-vNk6aEwybGtawWmy/PzwnGDOjCkLWSD2wqvjGGAgOAwCGWySYXfYoxt00IJkTF+8Lb57DwOb3Aa0o9CApepiYQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/resolve-uri\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": \"^1.4.14\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@sinclair/typebox\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.27.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinclair/typebox/-/typebox-0.27.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+Fj43pSMwJs4KRrH/938Uf+uAELIgVBmQzg/q1YG10djyfA3TnrU8N8XzqCh/okZdszqBQTZf96idMfE5lnwTA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@sinonjs/commons\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinonjs/commons/-/commons-3.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-K3mCHKQ9sVh8o1C9cxkwxaOmXoAMlDxC1mYyHrjqOWEcBjYr76t96zL2zlj5dUGZ3HSw240X1qgH3Mjf1yJWpQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@sinonjs/fake-timers\": {\n      \"version\": \"10.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinonjs/fake-timers/-/fake-timers-10.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-V4BG07kuYSUkTCSBHG8G8TNhM+F19jXFWnQtzj+we8DrkpSBCee9Z3Ms8yiGer/dlmhe35/Xdgyo3/0rQKg7YA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/babel__core\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.20.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__core/-/babel__core-7.20.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qoQprZvz5wQFJwMDqeseRXWv3rqMvhgpbXFfVyWhbx9X47POIA6i/+dXefEmZKoAgOaTdaIgNSMqMIU61yRyzA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.20.7\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.20.7\",\n        \"@types/babel__generator\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/babel__template\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/babel__traverse\": \"*\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/babel__generator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__generator/-/babel__generator-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ufFd2Xi92OAVPYsy+P4n7/U7e68fex0+Ee8gSG9KX7eo084CWiQ4sdxktvdl0bOPupXtVJPY19zk6EwWqUQ8lg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/babel__template\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.4.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__template/-/babel__template-7.4.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-h/NUaSyG5EyxBIp8YRxo4RMe2/qQgvyowRwVMzhYhBCONbW8PUsg4lkFMrhgZhUe5z3L3MiLDuvyJ/CaPa2A8A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.1.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/babel__traverse\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.20.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__traverse/-/babel__traverse-7.20.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-dkO5fhS7+/oos4ciWxyEyjWe48zmG6wbCheo/G2ZnHx4fs3EU6YC6UM8rk56gAjNJ9P3MTH2jo5jb92/K6wbng==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/graceful-fs\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/graceful-fs/-/graceful-fs-4.1.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-olP3sd1qOEe5dXTSaFvQG+02VdRXcdytWLAZsAq1PecU8uqQAhkrnbli7DagjtXKW/Bl7YJbUsa8MPcuc8LHEQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-lib-coverage/-/istanbul-lib-coverage-2.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2QF/t/auWm0lsy8XtKVPG19v3sSOQlJe/YHZgfjb/KBBHOGSV+J2q/S671rcq9uTBrLAXmZpqJiaQbMT+zNU1w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/istanbul-lib-report\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-lib-report/-/istanbul-lib-report-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NQn7AHQnk/RSLOxrBbGyJM/aVQ+pjj5HCgasFxc0K/KhoATfQ/47AyUl15I2yBUpihjmas+a+VJBOqecrFH+uA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/istanbul-reports\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-reports/-/istanbul-reports-3.0.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pk2B1NWalF9toCRu6gjBzR69syFjP4Od8WRAX+0mmf9lAjCRicLOWc+ZrxZHx/0XRjotgkF9t6iaMJ+aXcOdZQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/node\": {\n      \"version\": \"22.14.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/node/-/node-22.14.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-u0HuPQwe/dHrItgHHpmw3N2fYCR6x4ivMNbPHRkBVP4CvN+kiRrKHWk3i8tXiO/joPwXLMYvF9TTF0eqgHIuOw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/stack-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/stack-utils/-/stack-utils-2.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9aEbYZ3TbYMznPdcdr3SmIrLXwC/AKZXQeCf9Pgao5CKb8CyHuEX5jzWPTkvregvhRJHcpRO6BFoGW9ycaOkYw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/yargs\": {\n      \"version\": \"17.0.33\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/yargs/-/yargs-17.0.33.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WpxBCKWPLr4xSsHgz511rFJAM+wS28w2zEO1QDNY5zM/S8ok70NNfztH0xwhqKyaK0OHCbN98LDAZuy1ctxDkA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/yargs-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"21.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/yargs-parser/-/yargs-parser-21.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-I4q9QU9MQv4oEOz4tAHJtNz1cwuLxn2F3xcc2iV5WdqLPpUnj30aUuxt1mAxYTG+oe8CZMV/+6rU4S4gRDzqtQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/ansi-escapes\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-escapes/-/ansi-escapes-4.3.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gKXj5ALrKWQLsYG9jlTRmR/xKluxHV+Z9QEwNIgCfM1/uwPMCuzVVnh5mwTd+OuBZcwSIMbqssNWRm1lE51QaQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/ansi-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-regex/-/ansi-regex-5.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-quJQXlTSUGL2LH9SUXo8VwsY4soanhgo6LNSm84E1LBcE8s3O0wpdiRzyR9z/ZZJMlMWv37qOOb9pdJlMUEKFQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/ansi-styles\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-styles/-/ansi-styles-4.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zbB9rCJAT1rbjiVDb2hqKFHNYLxgtk8NURxZ3IZwD3F6NtxbXZQCnnSi1Lkx+IDohdPlFp222wVALIheZJQSEg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/anymatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/anymatch/-/anymatch-3.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KMReFUr0B4t+D+OBkjR3KYqvocp2XaSzO55UcB6mgQMd3KbcE+mWTyvVV7D/zsdEbNnV6acZUutkiHQXvTr1Rw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"normalize-path\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"picomatch\": \"^2.0.4\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/argparse\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/argparse/-/argparse-1.0.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-o5Roy6tNG4SL/FOkCAN6RzjiakZS25RLYFrcMttJqbdd8BWrnA+fGz57iN5Pb06pvBGvl5gQ0B48dJlslXvoTg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-jest/-/babel-jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BrvGY3xZSwEcCzKvKsCi2GgHqDqsYkOP4/by5xCgIwGXQxIEh+8ew3gmrE1y7XRR6LHZIj6yLYnUi/mm2KXKBg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@types/babel__core\": \"^7.1.14\",\n        \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": \"^6.1.1\",\n        \"babel-preset-jest\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-plugin-istanbul\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-plugin-istanbul/-/babel-plugin-istanbul-6.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Y1IQok9821cC9onCx5otgFfRm7Lm+I+wwxOx738M/WLPZ9Q42m4IG5W0FNX8WLL2gYMZo3JkuXIH2DOpWM+qwA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-plugin-utils\": \"^7.0.0\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": \"^5.0.4\",\n        \"test-exclude\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-plugin-istanbul/node_modules/istanbul-lib-instrument\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-instrument/-/istanbul-lib-instrument-5.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pzqtp31nLv/XFOzXGuvhCb8qhjmTVo5vjVk19XE4CRlSWz0KoeJ3bw9XsA7nOp9YBf4qHjwBxkDzKcME/J29Yg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.12.3\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.14.7\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-plugin-jest-hoist\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-plugin-jest-hoist/-/babel-plugin-jest-hoist-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ESAc/RJvGTFEzRwOTT4+lNDk/GNHMkKbNzsvT0qKRfDyyYTskxB5rnU2njIDYVxXCBHHEI1c0YwHob3WaYujOg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@types/babel__core\": \"^7.1.14\",\n        \"@types/babel__traverse\": \"^7.0.6\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-preset-current-node-syntax/-/babel-preset-current-node-syntax-1.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ldYss8SbBlWva1bs28q78Ju5Zq1F+8BrqBZZ0VFhLBvhh6lCpC2o3gDJi/5DRLs9FgYZCnmPYIVFU4lRXCkyUw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators\": \"^7.8.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties\": \"^7.12.13\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block\": \"^7.14.5\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes\": \"^7.24.7\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object\": \"^7.14.5\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await\": \"^7.14.5\"\n      },\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-preset-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-preset-jest/-/babel-preset-jest-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0B3bhxR6snWXJZtR/RliHTDPRgn1sNHOR0yVtq/IiQFyuOVjFS+wuio/R4gSNkyYmKmJB4wGZv2NZanmKmTnNA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"babel-plugin-jest-hoist\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/balanced-match\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/balanced-match/-/balanced-match-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3oSeUO0TMV67hN1AmbXsK4yaqU7tjiHlbxRDZOpH0KW9+CeX4bRAaX0Anxt0tx2MrpRpWwQaPwIlISEJhYU5Pw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/brace-expansion\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.11\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/brace-expansion/-/brace-expansion-1.1.11.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iCuPHDFgrHX7H2vEI/5xpz07zSHB00TpugqhmYtVmMO6518mCuRMoOYFldEBl0g187ufozdaHgWKcYFb61qGiA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"balanced-match\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"concat-map\": \"0.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/braces\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/braces/-/braces-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-yQbXgO/OSZVD2IsiLlro+7Hf6Q18EJrKSEsdoMzKePKXct3gvD8oLcOQdIzGupr5Fj+EDe8gO/lxc1BzfMpxvA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/browserslist\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.24.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/browserslist/-/browserslist-4.24.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KDi1Ny1gSePi1vm0q4oxSF8b4DR44GF4BbmS2YdhPLOEqd8pDviZOGH/GsmRwoWJ2+5Lr085X7naowMwKHDG1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n          \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"tidelift\",\n          \"url\": \"https://tidelift.com/funding/github/npm/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"github\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/ai\"\n        }\n      ],\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"caniuse-lite\": \"^1.0.30001688\",\n        \"electron-to-chromium\": \"^1.5.73\",\n        \"node-releases\": \"^2.0.19\",\n        \"update-browserslist-db\": \"^1.1.1\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": {\n        \"node\": \"^6 || ^7 || ^8 || ^9 || ^10 || ^11 || ^12 || >=13.7\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/bser\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/bser/-/bser-2.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gQxTNE/GAfIIrmHLUE3oJyp5FO6HRBfhjnw4/wMmA63ZGDJnWBmgY/lyQBpnDUkGmAhbSe39tx2d/iTOAfglwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/buffer-from\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/buffer-from/-/buffer-from-1.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-E+XQCRwSbaaiChtv6k6Dwgc+bx+Bs6vuKJHHl5kox/BaKbhiXzqQOwK4cO22yElGp2OCmjwVhT3HmxgyPGnJfQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/callsites\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/callsites/-/callsites-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-P8BjAsXvZS+VIDUI11hHCQEv74YT67YUi5JJFNWIqL235sBmjX4+qx9Muvls5ivyNENctx46xQLQ3aTuE7ssaQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/camelcase\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/camelcase/-/camelcase-5.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-L28STB170nwWS63UjtlEOE3dldQApaJXZkOI1uMFfzf3rRuPegHaHesyee+YxQ+W6SvRDQV6UrdOdRiR153wJg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/caniuse-lite\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.30001715\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/caniuse-lite/-/caniuse-lite-1.0.30001715.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7ptkFGMm2OAOgvZpwgA4yjQ5SQbrNVGdRjzH0pBdy1Fasvcr+KAeECmbCAECzTuDuoX0FCY8KzUxjf9+9kfZEw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n          \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"tidelift\",\n          \"url\": \"https://tidelift.com/funding/github/npm/caniuse-lite\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"github\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/ai\"\n        }\n      ]\n    },\n    \"node_modules/chalk\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/chalk/-/chalk-4.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-oKnbhFyRIXpUuez8iBMmyEa4nbj4IOQyuhc/wy9kY7/WVPcwIO9VA668Pu8RkO7+0G76SLROeyw9CpQ061i4mA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^7.1.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/char-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/char-regex/-/char-regex-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kWWXztvZ5SBQV+eRgKFeh8q5sLuZY2+8WUIzlxWVTg+oGwY14qylx1KbKzHd8P6ZYkAg0xyIDU9JMHhyJMZ1jw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/ci-info\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.9.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ci-info/-/ci-info-3.9.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NIxF55hv4nSqQswkAeiOi1r83xy8JldOFDTWiug55KBu9Jnblncd2U6ViHmYgHf01TPZS77NJBhBMKdWj9HQMQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"github\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/sibiraj-s\"\n        }\n      ],\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/cjs-module-lexer\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cjs-module-lexer/-/cjs-module-lexer-1.4.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9z8TZaGM1pfswYeXrUpzPrkx8UnWYdhJclsiYMm6x/w5+nN+8Tf/LnAgfLGQCm59qAOxU8WwHEq2vNwF6i4j+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/cliui\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cliui/-/cliui-8.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BSeNnyus75C4//NQ9gQt1/csTXyo/8Sb+afLAkzAptFuMsod9HFokGNudZpi/oQV73hnVK+sR+5PVRMd+Dr7YQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.2.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.1\",\n        \"wrap-ansi\": \"^7.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/co\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.6.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/co/-/co-4.6.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-QVb0dM5HvG+uaxitm8wONl7jltx8dqhfU33DcqtOZcLSVIKSDDLDi7+0LbAKiyI8hD9u42m2YxXSkMGWThaecQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/collect-v8-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/collect-v8-coverage/-/collect-v8-coverage-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lHl4d5/ONEbLlJvaJNtsF/Lz+WvB07u2ycqTYbdrq7UypDXailES4valYb2eWiJFxZlVmpGekfqoxQhzyFdT4Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/color-convert\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/color-convert/-/color-convert-2.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RRECPsj7iu/xb5oKYcsFHSppFNnsj/52OVTRKb4zP5onXwVF3zVmmToNcOfGC+CRDpfK/U584fMg38ZHCaElKQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/color-name\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/color-name/-/color-name-1.1.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-dOy+3AuW3a2wNbZHIuMZpTcgjGuLU/uBL/ubcZF9OXbDo8ff4O8yVp5Bf0efS8uEoYo5q4Fx7dY9OgQGXgAsQA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/concat-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/concat-map/-/concat-map-0.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/Srv4dswyQNBfohGpz9o6Yb3Gz3SrUDqBH5rTuhGR7ahtlbYKnVxw2bCFMRljaA7EXHaXZ8wsHdodFvbkhKmqg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/convert-source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/convert-source-map/-/convert-source-map-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Kvp459HrV2FEJ1CAsi1Ku+MY3kasH19TFykTz2xWmMeq6bk2NU3XXvfJ+Q61m0xktWwt+1HSYf3JZsTms3aRJg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/create-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/create-jest/-/create-jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Adz2bdH0Vq3F53KEMJOoftQFutWCukm6J24wbPWRO4k1kMY7gS7ds/uoJkNuV8wDCtWWnuwGcJwpWcih+zEW1Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"prompts\": \"^2.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/cross-spawn\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cross-spawn/-/cross-spawn-7.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-uV2QOWP2nWzsy2aMp8aRibhi9dlzF5Hgh5SHaB9OiTGEyDTiJJyx0uy51QXdyWbtAHNua4XJzUKca3OzKUd3vA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"path-key\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"shebang-command\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"which\": \"^2.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/debug\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/debug/-/debug-4.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6WTZ/IxCY/T6BALoZHaE4ctp9xm+Z5kY/pzYaCHRFeyVhojxlrm+46y68HA6hr0TcwEssoxNiDEUJQjfPZ/RYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/dedent\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/dedent/-/dedent-1.5.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NHQtfOOW68WD8lgypbLA5oT+Bt0xXJhiYvoR6SmmNXZfpzOGXwdKWmcwG8N7PwVVWV3eF/68nmD9BaJSsTBhyQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/deepmerge\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/deepmerge/-/deepmerge-4.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3sUqbMEc77XqpdNO7FRyRog+eW3ph+GYCbj+rK+uYyRMuwsVy0rMiVtPn+QJlKFvWP/1PYpapqYn0Me2knFn+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/detect-newline\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/detect-newline/-/detect-newline-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TLz+x/vEXm/Y7P7wn1EJFNLxYpUD4TgMosxY6fAVJUnJMbupHBOncxyWUG9OpTaH9EBD7uFI5LfEgmMOc54DsA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/diff-sequences\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/diff-sequences/-/diff-sequences-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-EjePK1srD3P08o2j4f0ExnylqRs5B9tJjcp9t1krH2qRi8CCdsYfwe9JgSLurFBWwq4uOlipzfk5fHNvwFKr8Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/electron-to-chromium\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.140\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/electron-to-chromium/-/electron-to-chromium-1.5.140.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-o82Rj+ONp4Ip7Cl1r7lrqx/pXhbp/lh9DpKcMNscFJdh8ebyRofnc7Sh01B4jx403RI0oqTBvlZ7OBIZLMr2+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/emittery\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.13.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/emittery/-/emittery-0.13.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DeWwawk6r5yR9jFgnDKYt4sLS0LmHJJi3ZOnb5/JdbYwj3nW+FxQnHIjhBKz8YLC7oRNPVM9NQ47I3CVx34eqQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": {\n        \"url\": \"https://github.com/sindresorhus/emittery?sponsor=1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/emoji-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/emoji-regex/-/emoji-regex-8.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MSjYzcWNOA0ewAHpz0MxpYFvwg6yjy1NG3xteoqz644VCo/RPgnr1/GGt+ic3iJTzQ8Eu3TdM14SawnVUmGE6A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/error-ex\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.3.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/error-ex/-/error-ex-1.3.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7dFHNmqeFSEt2ZBsCriorKnn3Z2pj+fd9kmI6QoWw4//DL+icEBfc0U7qJCisqrTsKTjw4fNFy2pW9OqStD84g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/escalade\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/escalade/-/escalade-3.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WUj2qlxaQtO4g6Pq5c29GTcWGDyd8itL8zTlipgECz3JesAiiOKotd8JU6otB3PACgG6xkJUyVhboMS+bje/jA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/escape-string-regexp\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/escape-string-regexp/-/escape-string-regexp-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UpzcLCXolUWcNu5HtVMHYdXJjArjsF9C0aNnquZYY4uW/Vu0miy5YoWvbV345HauVvcAUnpRuhMMcqTcGOY2+w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/esprima\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/esprima/-/esprima-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eGuFFw7Upda+g4p+QHvnW0RyTX/SVeJBDM/gCtMARO0cLuT2HcEKnTPvhjV6aGeqrCB/sbNop0Kszm0jsaWU4A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": {\n        \"esparse\": \"bin/esparse.js\",\n        \"esvalidate\": \"bin/esvalidate.js\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/execa\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/execa/-/execa-5.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-8uSpZZocAZRBAPIEINJj3Lo9HyGitllczc27Eh5YYojjMFMn8yHMDMaUHE2Jqfq05D/wucwI4JGURyXt1vchyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"cross-spawn\": \"^7.0.3\",\n        \"get-stream\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"human-signals\": \"^2.1.0\",\n        \"is-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"merge-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"npm-run-path\": \"^4.0.1\",\n        \"onetime\": \"^5.1.2\",\n        \"signal-exit\": \"^3.0.3\",\n        \"strip-final-newline\": \"^2.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/exit\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/exit/-/exit-0.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Zk/eNKV2zbjpKzrsQ+n1G6poVbErQxJ0LBOJXaKZ1EViLzH+hrLu9cdXI4zw9dBQJslwBEpbQ2P1oS7nDxs6jQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/expect\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/expect/-/expect-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2Zks0hf1VLFYI1kbh0I5jP3KHHyCHpkfyHBzsSXRFgl/Bg9mWYfMW8oD+PdMPlEwy5HNsR9JutYy6pMeOh61nw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/expect-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/fast-json-stable-stringify\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fast-json-stable-stringify/-/fast-json-stable-stringify-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lhd/wF+Lk98HZoTCtlVraHtfh5XYijIjalXck7saUtuanSDyLMxnHhSXEDJqHxD7msR8D0uCmqlkwjCV8xvwHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/fb-watchman\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fb-watchman/-/fb-watchman-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-p5161BqbuCaSnB8jIbzQHOlpgsPmK5rJVDfDKO91Axs5NC1uu3HRQm6wt9cd9/+GtQQIO53JdGXXoyDpTAsgYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/fill-range\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fill-range/-/fill-range-7.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-YsGpe3WHLK8ZYi4tWDg2Jy3ebRz2rXowDxnld4bkQB00cc/1Zw9AWnC0i9ztDJitivtQvaI9KaLyKrc+hBW0yg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/find-up\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/find-up/-/find-up-4.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-PpOwAdQ/YlXQ2vj8a3h8IipDuYRi3wceVQQGYWxNINccq40Anw7BlsEXCMbt1Zt+OLA6Fq9suIpIWD0OsnISlw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"locate-path\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"path-exists\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/fs.realpath\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fs.realpath/-/fs.realpath-1.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OO0pH2lK6a0hZnAdau5ItzHPI6pUlvI7jMVnxUQRtw4owF2wk8lOSabtGDCTP4Ggrg2MbGnWO9X8K1t4+fGMDw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/fsevents\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fsevents/-/fsevents-2.3.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-5xoDfX+fL7faATnagmWPpbFtwh/R77WmMMqqHGS65C3vvB0YHrgF+B1YmZ3441tMj5n63k0212XNoJwzlhffQw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"hasInstallScript\": true,\n      \"optional\": true,\n      \"os\": [\n        \"darwin\"\n      ],\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/function-bind\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/function-bind/-/function-bind-1.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7XHNxH7qX9xG5mIwxkhumTox/MIRNcOgDrxWsMt2pAr23WHp6MrRlN7FBSFpCpr+oVO0F744iUgR82nJMfG2SA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/gensync\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0-beta.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/gensync/-/gensync-1.0.0-beta.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3hN7NaskYvMDLQY55gnW3NQ+mesEAepTqlg+VEbj7zzqEMBVNhzcGYYeqFo/TlYz6eQiFcp1HcsCZO+nGgS8zg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/get-caller-file\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-caller-file/-/get-caller-file-2.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DyFP3BM/3YHTQOCUL/w0OZHR0lpKeGrxotcHWcqNEdnltqFwXVfhEBQ94eIo34AfQpo0rGki4cyIiftY06h2Fg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/get-package-type\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-package-type/-/get-package-type-0.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pjzuKtY64GYfWizNAJ0fr9VqttZkNiK2iS430LtIHzjBEr6bX8Am2zm4sW4Ro5wjWW5cAlRL1qAMTcXbjNAO2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/get-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-stream/-/get-stream-6.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ts6Wi+2j3jQjqi70w5AlN8DFnkSwC+MqmxEzdEALB2qXZYV3X/b1CTfgPLGJNMeAWxdPfU8FO1ms3NUfaHCPYg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/glob\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/glob/-/glob-7.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-nFR0zLpU2YCaRxwoCJvL6UvCH2JFyFVIvwTLsIf21AuHlMskA1hhTdk+LlYJtOlYt9v6dvszD2BGRqBL+iQK9Q==\",\n      \"deprecated\": \"Glob versions prior to v9 are no longer supported\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"fs.realpath\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"inflight\": \"^1.0.4\",\n        \"inherits\": \"2\",\n        \"minimatch\": \"^3.1.1\",\n        \"once\": \"^1.3.0\",\n        \"path-is-absolute\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/globals\": {\n      \"version\": \"11.12.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/globals/-/globals-11.12.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WOBp/EEGUiIsJSp7wcv/y6MO+lV9UoncWqxuFfm8eBwzWNgyfBd6Gz+IeKQ9jCmyhoH99g15M3T+QaVHFjizVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/graceful-fs\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.11\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/graceful-fs/-/graceful-fs-4.2.11.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RbJ5/jmFcNNCcDV5o9eTnBLJ/HszWV0P73bc+Ff4nS/rJj+YaS6IGyiOL0VoBYX+l1Wrl3k63h/KrH+nhJ0XvQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/has-flag\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/has-flag/-/has-flag-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-EykJT/Q1KjTWctppgIAgfSO0tKVuZUjhgMr17kqTumMl6Afv3EISleU7qZUzoXDFTAHTDC4NOoG/ZxU3EvlMPQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/hasown\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/hasown/-/hasown-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0hJU9SCPvmMzIBdZFqNPXWa6dqh7WdH0cII9y+CyS8rG3nL48Bclra9HmKhVVUHyPWNH5Y7xDwAB7bfgSjkUMQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/html-escaper\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/html-escaper/-/html-escaper-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-H2iMtd0I4Mt5eYiapRdIDjp+XzelXQ0tFE4JS7YFwFevXXMmOp9myNrUvCg0D6ws8iqkRPBfKHgbwig1SmlLfg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/human-signals\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/human-signals/-/human-signals-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-B4FFZ6q/T2jhhksgkbEW3HBvWIfDW85snkQgawt07S7J5QXTk6BkNV+0yAeZrM5QpMAdYlocGoljn0sJ/WQkFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/import-local\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/import-local/-/import-local-3.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2SPlun1JUPWoM6t3F0dw0FkCF/jWY8kttcY4f599GLTSjh2OCuuhdTkJQsEcZzBqbXZGKMK2OqW1oZsjtf/gQA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/imurmurhash\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/imurmurhash/-/imurmurhash-0.1.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JmXMZ6wuvDmLiHEml9ykzqO6lwFbof0GG4IkcGaENdCRDDmMVnny7s5HsIgHCbaq0w2MyPhDqkhTUgS2LU2PHA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/inflight\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/inflight/-/inflight-1.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-k92I/b08q4wvFscXCLvqfsHCrjrF7yiXsQuIVvVE7N82W3+aqpzuUdBbfhWcy/FZR3/4IgflMgKLOsvPDrGCJA==\",\n      \"deprecated\": \"This module is not supported, and leaks memory. Do not use it. Check out lru-cache if you want a good and tested way to coalesce async requests by a key value, which is much more comprehensive and powerful.\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/inherits\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/inherits/-/inherits-2.0.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-k/vGaX4/Yla3WzyMCvTQOXYeIHvqOKtnqBduzTHpzpQZzAskKMhZ2K+EnBiSM9zGSoIFeMpXKxa4dYeZIQqewQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-arrayish\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-arrayish/-/is-arrayish-0.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zz06S8t0ozoDXMG+ube26zeCTNXcKIPJZJi8hBrF4idCLms4CG9QtK7qBl1boi5ODzFpjswb5JPmHCbMpjaYzg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-core-module\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.16.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-core-module/-/is-core-module-2.16.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UfoeMA6fIJ8wTYFEUjelnaGI67v6+N7qXJEvQuIGa99l4xsCruSYOVSQ0uPANn4dAzm8lkYPaKLrrijLq7x23w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-fullwidth-code-point\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-fullwidth-code-point/-/is-fullwidth-code-point-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zymm5+u+sCsSWyD9qNaejV3DFvhCKclKdizYaJUuHA83RLjb7nSuGnddCHGv0hk+KY7BMAlsWeK4Ueg6EV6XQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-generator-fn\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-generator-fn/-/is-generator-fn-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-cTIB4yPYL/Grw0EaSzASzg6bBy9gqCofvWN8okThAYIxKJZC+udlRAmGbM0XLeniEJSs8uEgHPGuHSe1XsOLSQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-number\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-number/-/is-number-7.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-41Cifkg6e8TylSpdtTpeLVMqvSBEVzTttHvERD741+pnZ8ANv0004MRL43QKPDlK9cGvNp6NZWZUBlbGXYxxng==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-stream/-/is-stream-2.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hFoiJiTl63nn+kstHGBtewWSKnQLpyb155KHheA1l39uvtO9nWIop1p3udqPcUd/xbF1VLMO4n7OI6p7RbngDg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/isexe\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/isexe/-/isexe-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RHxMLp9lnKHGHRng9QFhRCMbYAcVpn69smSGcq3f36xjgVVWThj4qqLbTLlq7Ssj8B+fIQ1EuCEGI2lKsyQeIw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-coverage/-/istanbul-lib-coverage-3.2.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-O8dpsF+r0WV/8MNRKfnmrtCWhuKjxrq2w+jpzBL5UZKTi2LeVWnWOmWRxFlesJONmc+wLAGvKQZEOanko0LFTg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-instrument\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-instrument/-/istanbul-lib-instrument-6.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Vtgk7L/R2JHyyGW07spoFlB8/lpjiOLTjMdms6AFMraYt3BaJauod/NGrfnVG/y4Ix1JEuMRPDPEj2ua+zz1/Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.23.9\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.23.9\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.3\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^7.5.4\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-instrument/node_modules/semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-report\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-report/-/istanbul-lib-report-3.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GCfE1mtsHGOELCU8e/Z7YWzpmybrx/+dSTfLrvY8qRmaY6zXTKWn6WQIjaAFw069icm6GVMNkgu0NzI4iPZUNw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"make-dir\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^7.1.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-source-maps\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-source-maps/-/istanbul-lib-source-maps-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-n3s8EwkdFIJCG3BPKBYvskgXGoy88ARzvegkitk60NxRdwltLOTaH7CUiMRXvwYorl0Q712iEjcWB+fK/MrWVw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"debug\": \"^4.1.1\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"source-map\": \"^0.6.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-reports\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-reports/-/istanbul-reports-3.1.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BewmUXImeuRk2YY0PVbxgKAysvhRPUQE0h5QRM++nVWyubKGV0l8qQ5op8+B2DOmwSe63Jivj0BjkPQVf8fP5g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"html-escaper\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-report\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest/-/jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NIy3oAFp9shda19hy4HK0HRTWKtPJmGdnvywu01nOqNC2vZg+Z+fvJDxpMQA88eb2I9EcafcdjYgsDthnYTvGw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/core\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"import-local\": \"^3.0.2\",\n        \"jest-cli\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-changed-files\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-changed-files/-/jest-changed-files-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fEArFiwf1BpQ+4bXSprcDc3/x4HSzL4al2tozwVpDFpsxALjLYdyiIK4e5Vz66GQJIbXJ82+35PtysofptNX2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"execa\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-circus\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-circus/-/jest-circus-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3E1nCMgipcTkCocFwM90XXQab9bS+GMsjdpmPrlelaxwD93Ad8iVEjX/vvHPdLPnFf+L40u+5+iutRdA1N9myw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"co\": \"^4.6.0\",\n        \"dedent\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"is-generator-fn\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"jest-each\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"pure-rand\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"stack-utils\": \"^2.0.3\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-cli\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-cli/-/jest-cli-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OVVobw2IubN/GSYsxETi+gOe7Ka59EFMR/twOU3Jb2GnKKeMGJB5SGUUrEz3SFVmJASUdZUzy83sLNNQ2gZslg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/core\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"create-jest\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"import-local\": \"^3.0.2\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"yargs\": \"^17.3.1\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-config\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-config/-/jest-config-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-uXbpfeQ7R6TZBqI3/TxCU4q4ttk3u0PJeC+E0zbfSoSjq6bJ7buBPxzQPL0ifrkY4DNu4JUdk0ImlBUYi840eQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@jest/test-sequencer\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-jest\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"deepmerge\": \"^4.2.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-circus\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-environment-node\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runner\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"parse-json\": \"^5.2.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-json-comments\": \"^3.1.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": ,\n        \"ts-node\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-diff\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-diff/-/jest-diff-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LMIgiIrhigmPrs03JHpxUh2yISK3vLFPkAodPeo0+BuF7wA2FoQbkEg1u8gBYBThncu7e1oEDUfIXVuTqLRUjw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"diff-sequences\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-docblock\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-docblock/-/jest-docblock-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-q617Auw3A612guyaFgsbFeYpNP5t2aoUNLwBUbc/0kD1R4t9ixDbyFTHd1nok4epoVFpr7PmeWHrhvuV3XaJ4g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-each\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-each/-/jest-each-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gns+Er14+ZrEoC5fhOfYCY1LOHHr0TI+rQUHZS8Ttw2l7gl+80eHc/gFf2Ktkw0+SIACDTeWvpFcv3B04VembQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-environment-node\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-environment-node/-/jest-environment-node-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DOSwCRqXirTOyheM+4d5YZOrWcdu0LNZ87ewUoywbcb2XR4wKgqiG8vNeYwhjFMbEkfju7wx2GYH0P2gevGvFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-get-type\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-get-type/-/jest-get-type-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zrteXnqYxfQh7l5FHyL38jL39di8H8rHoecLH3JNxH3BwOrBsNeabdap5e0I23lD4HHI8W5VFBZqG4Eaq5LNcw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-haste-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-haste-map/-/jest-haste-map-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fP8u2pyfqx0K1rGn1R9pyE0/KTn+G7PxktWidOBTqFPLYX0b9ksaMFkhK5vrS3DVun09pckLdlx90QthlW7AmA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/graceful-fs\": \"^4.1.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"anymatch\": \"^3.0.3\",\n        \"fb-watchman\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"walker\": \"^1.0.8\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"optionalDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-leak-detector\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-leak-detector/-/jest-leak-detector-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kYA8IJcSYtST2BY9I+SMC32nDpBT3J2NvWJx8+JCuCdl/CR1I4EKUJROiP8XtCcxqgTTBGJNdbB1A8XRKbTetw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-matcher-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-matcher-utils/-/jest-matcher-utils-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-sBkD+Xi9DtcChsI3L3u0+N0opgPYnCRPtGcQYrgXmR+hmt/fYfWAL0xRXYU8eWOdfuLgBe0YCW3AFtnRLagq/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-diff\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-message-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-message-util/-/jest-message-util-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GBEV4GRADeP+qtB2+6u61stea8mGcOT4mCtrYISZwfu9/ISHFJ/5zOMXYbpBE9RsS5+Gb63DW4FgmnKJ79Kf6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.12.13\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/stack-utils\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"stack-utils\": \"^2.0.3\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-mock\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-mock/-/jest-mock-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ITOMZn+UkYS4ZFh83xYAOzWStloNzJFO2s8DWrE4lhtGD+AorgnbkiKERe4wQVBydIGPx059g6riW5Btp6Llnw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-pnp-resolver\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-pnp-resolver/-/jest-pnp-resolver-1.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+3NpwQEnRoIBtx4fyhblQDPgJI0H1IEIkX7ShLUjPGA7TtUTvI1oiKi3SR4oBR0hQhQR80l4WAe5RrXBwWMA8w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-regex-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-regex-util/-/jest-regex-util-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KJJBsRCyyLNWCNBOvZyRDnAIfUiRJ8v+hOBQYGn8gDyF3UegwiP4gwRR3/SDa42g1YbVycTidUF3rKjyLFDWbg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-resolve\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-resolve/-/jest-resolve-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-IOVhZSrg+UvVAshDSDtHyFCCBUl/Q3AAJv8iZ6ZjnZ74xzvwuzLXid9IIIPgTnY62SJjfuupMKZsZQRsCvxEgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-pnp-resolver\": \"^1.2.2\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"resolve\": \"^1.20.0\",\n        \"resolve.exports\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-resolve-dependencies\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-resolve-dependencies/-/jest-resolve-dependencies-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-un0zD/6qxJ+S0et7WxeI3H5XSe9lTBBR7bOHCHXkKR6luG5mwDDlIzVQ0V5cZCuoTgEdcdwzTghYkTWfubi+nA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-runner\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-runner/-/jest-runner-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fsc4N6cPCAahybGBfTRcq5wFR6fpLznMg47sY5aDpsoejOcVYFb07AHuSnR0liMcPTgBsA3ZJL6kFOjPdoNipQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"emittery\": \"^0.13.1\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-docblock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-environment-node\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-leak-detector\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-watcher\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"source-map-support\": \"0.5.13\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-runtime\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-runtime/-/jest-runtime-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gUnLjgwdGqW7B4LvOIkbKs9WGbn+QLqRQQ9juC6HndeDiezIwhDP+mhMwHWCEcfQ5RUXa6OPnFF8BJh5xegwwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/globals\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/source-map\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"cjs-module-lexer\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-bom\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-snapshot\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-snapshot/-/jest-snapshot-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Rm0BMWtxBcioHr1/OX5YCP8Uov4riHvKPknOGs804Zg9JGZgmIBkbtlxJC/7Z4msKYVbIJtfU+tKb8xlYNfdkw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@jest/expect-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-diff\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"natural-compare\": \"^1.4.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^7.5.3\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-snapshot/node_modules/semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-util/-/jest-util-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-z6EbKajIpqGKU56y5KBUgy1dt1ihhQJgWzUlZHArA/+X2ad7Cb5iF+AK1EWVL/Bo7Rz9uurpqw6SiBCefUbCGA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"picomatch\": \"^2.2.3\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-validate\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-validate/-/jest-validate-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ZB7wHqaRGVw/9hST/OuFUReG7M8vKeq0/J2egIGLdvjHCmYqGARhzXmtgi+gVeZ5uXFF219aOc3Ls2yLg27tkw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"camelcase\": \"^6.2.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"leven\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-validate/node_modules/camelcase\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/camelcase/-/camelcase-6.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Gmy6FhYlCY7uOElZUSbxo2UCDH8owEk996gkbrpsgGtrJLM3J7jGxl9Ic7Qwwj4ivOE5AWZWRMecDdF7hqGjFA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-watcher\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-watcher/-/jest-watcher-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-49Fg7WXkU3Vl2h6LbLtMQ/HyB6rXSIX7SqvBLQmssRBGN9I0PNvPmAmCWSOY6SOvrjhI/F7/bGAv9RtnsPA03g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"ansi-escapes\": \"^4.2.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"emittery\": \"^0.13.1\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"string-length\": \"^4.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-worker\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-worker/-/jest-worker-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eIz2msL/EzL9UFTFFx7jBTkeZfku0yUAyZZZmJ93H2TYEiroIx2PQjEXcwYtYl8zXCxb+PAmA2hLIt/6ZEkPHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"merge-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^8.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-worker/node_modules/supports-color\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-color/-/supports-color-8.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MpUEN2OodtUzxvKQl72cUF7RQ5EiHsGvSsVG0ia9c5RbWGL2CI4C7EpPS8UTBIplnlzZiNuV56w+FuNxy3ty2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/js-tokens\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/js-tokens/-/js-tokens-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RdJUflcE3cUzKiMqQgsCu06FPu9UdIJO0beYbPhHN4k6apgJtifcoCtT9bcxOpYBtpD2kCM6Sbzg4CausW/PKQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/js-yaml\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.14.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/js-yaml/-/js-yaml-3.14.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-okMH7OXXJ7YrN9Ok3/SXrnu4iX9yOk+25nqX4imS2npuvTYDmo/QEZoqwZkYaIDk3jVvBOTOIEgEhaLOynBS9g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jsesc\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jsesc/-/jsesc-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/sM3dO2FOzXjKQhJuo0Q173wf2KOo8t4I8vHy6lF9poUp7bKT0/NHE8fPX23PwfhnykfqnC2xRxOnVw5XuGIaA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/json-parse-even-better-errors\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/json-parse-even-better-errors/-/json-parse-even-better-errors-2.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xyFwyhro/JEof6Ghe2iz2NcXoj2sloNsWr/XsERDK/oiPCfaNhl5ONfp+jQdAZRQQ0IJWNzH9zIZF7li91kh2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/json5\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/json5/-/json5-2.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XmOWe7eyHYH14cLdVPoyg+GOH3rYX++KpzrylJwSW98t3Nk+U8XOl8FWKOgwtzdb8lXGf6zYwDUzeHMWfxasyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/kleur\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/kleur/-/kleur-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eTIzlVOSUR+JxdDFepEYcBMtZ9Qqdef+rnzWdRZuMbOywu5tO2w2N7rqjoANZ5k9vywhL6Br1VRjUIgTQx4E8w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/leven\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/leven/-/leven-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qsda+H8jTaUaN/x5vzW2rzc+8Rw4TAQ/4KjB46IwK5VH+IlVeeeje/EoZRpiXvIqjFgK84QffqPztGI3VBLG1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/lines-and-columns\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/lines-and-columns/-/lines-and-columns-1.2.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7ylylesZQ/PV29jhEDl3Ufjo6ZX7gCqJr5F7PKrqc93v7fzSymt1BpwEU8nAUXs8qzzvqhbjhK5QZg6Mt/HkBg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/locate-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/locate-path/-/locate-path-5.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-t7hw9pI+WvuwNJXwk5zVHpyhIqzg2qTlklJOf0mVxGSbe3Fp2VieZcduNYjaLDoy6p9uGpQEGWG87WpMKlNq8g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/lru-cache\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/lru-cache/-/lru-cache-5.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KpNARQA3Iwv+jTA0utUVVbrh+Jlrr1Fv0e56GGzAFOXN7dk/FviaDW8LHmK52DlcH4WP2n6gI8vN1aesBFgo9w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/make-dir\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/make-dir/-/make-dir-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hXdUTZYIVOt1Ex//jAQi+wTZZpUpwBj/0QsOzqegb3rGMMeJiSEu5xLHnYfBrRV4RH2+OCSOO95Is/7x1WJ4bw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/make-dir/node_modules/semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/makeerror\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.12\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/makeerror/-/makeerror-1.0.12.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JmqCvUhmt43madlpFzG4BQzG2Z3m6tvQDNKdClZnO3VbIudJYmxsT0FNJMeiB2+JTSlTQTSbU8QdesVmwJcmLg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/merge-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/merge-stream/-/merge-stream-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-abv/qOcuPfk3URPfDzmZU1LKmuw8kT+0nIHvKrKgFrwifol/doWcdA4ZqsWQ8ENrFKkd67Mfpo/LovbIUsbt3w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/micromatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/micromatch/-/micromatch-4.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-PXwfBhYu0hBCPw8Dn0E+WDYb7af3dSLVWKi3HGv84IdF4TyFoC0ysxFd0Goxw7nSv4T/PzEJQxsYsEiFCKo2BA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/mimic-fn\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/mimic-fn/-/mimic-fn-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OqbOk5oEQeAZ8WXWydlu9HJjz9WVdEIvamMCcXmuqUYjTknH/sqsWvhQ3vgwKFRR1HpjvNBKQ37nbJgYzGqGcg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/minimatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/minimatch/-/minimatch-3.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-J7p63hRiAjw1NDEww1W7i37+ByIrOWO5XQQAzZ3VOcL0PNybwpfmV/N05zFAzwQ9USyEcX6t3UO+K5aqBQOIHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/ms\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ms/-/ms-2.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6FlzubTLZG3J2a/NVCAleEhjzq5oxgHyaCU9yYXvcLsvoVaHJq/s5xXI6/XXP6tz7R9xAOtHnSO/tXtF3WRTlA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/natural-compare\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/natural-compare/-/natural-compare-1.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OWND8ei3VtNC9h7V60qff3SVobHr996CTwgxubgyQYEpg290h9J0buyECNNJexkFm5sOajh5G116RYA1c8ZMSw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/node-int64\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/node-int64/-/node-int64-0.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-O5lz91xSOeoXP6DulyHfllpq+Eg00MWitZIbtPfoSEvqIHdl5gfcY6hYzDWnj0qD5tz52PI08u9qUvSVeUBeHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/node-releases\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.19\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/node-releases/-/node-releases-2.0.19.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xxOWJsBKtzAq7DY0J+DTzuz58K8e7sJbdgwkbMWQe8UYB6ekmsQ45q0M/tJDsGaZmbC+l7n57UV8Hl5tHxO9uw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/normalize-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/normalize-path/-/normalize-path-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6eZs5Ls3WtCisHWp9S2GUy8dqkpGi4BVSz3GaqiE6ezub0512ESztXUwUB6C6IKbQkY2Pnb/mD4WYojCRwcwLA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/npm-run-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/npm-run-path/-/npm-run-path-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-S48WzZW777zhNIrn7gxOlISNAqi9ZC/uQFnRdbeIHhZhCA6UqpkOT8T1G7BvfdgP4Er8gF4sUbaS0i7QvIfCWw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/once\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/once/-/once-1.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lNaJgI+2Q5URQBkccEKHTQOPaXdUxnZZElQTZY0MFUAuaEqe1E+Nyvgdz/aIyNi6Z9MzO5dv1H8n58/GELp3+w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/onetime\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/onetime/-/onetime-5.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kbpaSSGJTWdAY5KPVeMOKXSrPtr8C8C7wodJbcsd51jRnmD+GZu8Y0VoU6Dm5Z4vWr0Ig/1NKuWRKf7j5aaYSg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/p-limit\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-limit/-/p-limit-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TYOanM3wGwNGsZN2cVTYPArw454xnXj5qmWF1bEoAc4+cU/ol7GVh7odevjp1FNHduHc3KZMcFduxU5Xc6uJRQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/p-locate\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-locate/-/p-locate-4.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R79ZZ/0wAxKGu3oYMlz8jy/kbhsNrS7SKZ7PxEHBgJ5+F2mtFW2fK2cOtBh1cHYkQsbzFV7I+EoRKe6Yt0oK7A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/p-locate/node_modules/p-limit\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-limit/-/p-limit-2.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-//88mFWSJx8lxCzwdAABTJL2MyWB12+eIY7MDL2SqLmAkeKU9qxRvWuSyTjm3FUmpBEMuFfckAIqEaVGUDxb6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/p-try\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-try/-/p-try-2.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R4nPAVTAU0B9D35/Gk3uJf/7XYbQcyohSKdvAxIRSNghFl4e71hVoGnBNQz9cWaXxO2I10KTC+3jMdvvoKw6dQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/parse-json\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/parse-json/-/parse-json-5.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ayCKvm/phCGxOkYRSCM82iDwct8/EonSEgCSxWxD7ve6jHggsFl4fZVQBPRNgQoKiuV/odhFrGzQXZwbifC8Rg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.0.0\",\n        \"error-ex\": \"^1.3.1\",\n        \"json-parse-even-better-errors\": \"^2.3.0\",\n        \"lines-and-columns\": \"^1.1.6\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/path-exists\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-exists/-/path-exists-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ak9Qy5Q7jYb2Wwcey5Fpvg2KoAc/ZIhLSLOSBmRmygPsGwkVVt0fZa0qrtMz+m6tJTAHfZQ8FnmB4MG4LWy7/w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/path-is-absolute\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-is-absolute/-/path-is-absolute-1.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-AVbw3UJ2e9bq64vSaS9Am0fje1Pa8pbGqTTsmXfaIiMpnr5DlDhfJOuLj9Sf95ZPVDAUerDfEk88MPmPe7UCQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/path-key\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-key/-/path-key-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ojmeN0qd+y0jszEtoY48r0Peq5dwMEkIlCOu6Q5f41lfkswXuKtYrhgoTpLnyIcHm24Uhqx+5Tqm2InSwLhE6Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/path-parse\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-parse/-/path-parse-1.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LDJzPVEEEPR+y48z93A0Ed0yXb8pAByGWo/k5YYdYgpY2/2EsOsksJrq7lOHxryrVOn1ejG6oAp8ahvOIQD8sw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/picocolors\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/picocolors/-/picocolors-1.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xceH2snhtb5M9liqDsmEw56le376mTZkEX/jEb/RxNFyegNul7eNslCXP9FDj/Lcu0X8KEyMceP2ntpaHrDEVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/picomatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/picomatch/-/picomatch-2.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JU3teHTNjmE2VCGFzuY8EXzCDVwEqB2a8fsIvwaStHhAWJEeVd1o1QD80CU6+ZdEXXSLbSsuLwJjkCBWqRQUVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pirates\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pirates/-/pirates-4.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TfySrs/5nm8fQJDcBDuUng3VOUKsd7S+zqvbOTiGXHfxX4wK31ard+hoNuvkicM/2YFzlpDgABOevKSsB4G/FA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pkg-dir\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pkg-dir/-/pkg-dir-4.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-HRDzbaKjC+AOWVXxAU/x54COGeIv9eb+6CkDSQoNTt4XyWoIJvuPsXizxu/Fr23EiekbtZwmh1IcIG/l/a10GQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pretty-format\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pretty-format/-/pretty-format-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Pdlw/oPxN+aXdmM9R00JVC9WVFoCLTKJvDVLgmJ+qAffBMxsV85l/Lu7sNx4zSzPyoL2euImuEwHhOXdEgNFZQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/schemas\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"react-is\": \"^18.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pretty-format/node_modules/ansi-styles\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-styles/-/ansi-styles-5.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Cxwpt2SfTzTtXcfOlzGEee8O+c+MmUgGrNiBcXnuWxuFJHe6a5Hz7qwhwe5OgaSYI0IJvkLqWX1ASG+cJOkEiA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/prompts\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.4.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/prompts/-/prompts-2.4.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NxNv/kLguCA7p3jE8oL2aEBsrJWgAakBpgmgK6lpPWV+WuOmY6r2/zbAVnP+T8bQlA0nzHXSJSJW0Hq7ylaD2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pure-rand\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pure-rand/-/pure-rand-6.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bVWawvoZoBYpp6yIoQtQXHZjmz35RSVHnUOTefl8Vcjr8snTPY1wnpSPMWekcFwbxI6gtmT7rSYPFvz71ldiOA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"individual\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/dubzzz\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n          \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/fast-check\"\n        }\n      ]\n    },\n    \"node_modules/react-is\": {\n      \"version\": \"18.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/react-is/-/react-is-18.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/LLMVyas0ljjAtoYiPqYiL8VWXzUUdThrmU5+n20DZv+a+ClRoevUzw5JxU+Ieh5/c87ytoTBV9G1FiKfNJdmg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/require-directory\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/require-directory/-/require-directory-2.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fGxEI7+wsG9xrvdjsrlmL22OMTTiHRwAMroiEeMgq8gzoLC/PQr7RsRDSTLUg/bZAZtF+TVIkHc6/4RIKrui+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/resolve\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.22.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve/-/resolve-1.22.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NPRy+/ncIMeDlTAsuqwKIiferiawhefFJtkNSW0qZJEqMEb+qBt/77B/jGeeek+F0uOeN05CDa6HXbbIgtVX4w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"is-core-module\": \"^2.16.0\",\n        \"path-parse\": \"^1.0.7\",\n        \"supports-preserve-symlinks-flag\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/resolve-cwd\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve-cwd/-/resolve-cwd-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OrZaX2Mb+rJCpH/6CpSqt9xFVpN++x01XnN2ie9g6P5/3xelLAkXWVADpdz1IHD/KFfEXyE6V0U01OQ3UO2rEg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/resolve-from\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve-from/-/resolve-from-5.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qYg9KP24dD5qka9J47d0aVky0N+b4fTU89LN9iDnjB5waksiC49rvMB0PrUJQGoTmH50XPiqOvAjDfaijGxYZw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/resolve.exports\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve.exports/-/resolve.exports-2.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OcXjMsGdhL4XnbShKpAcSqPMzQoYkYyhbEaeSko47MjRP9NfEQMhZkXL1DoFlt9LWQn4YttrdnV6X2OiyzBi+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-6.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BR7VvDCVHO+q2xBEWskxS6DJE1qRnb7DxzUrogb71CWoSficBxYsiAGd+Kl0mmq/MprG9yArRkyrQxTO6XjMzA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/shebang-command\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/shebang-command/-/shebang-command-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kHxr2zZpYtdmrN1qDjrrX/Z1rR1kG8Dx+gkpK1G4eXmvXswmcE1hTWBWYUzlraYw1/yZp6YuDY77YtvbN0dmDA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/shebang-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/shebang-regex/-/shebang-regex-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7++dFhtcx3353uBaq8DDR4NuxBetBzC7ZQOhmTQInHEd6bSrXdiEyzCvG07Z44UYdLShWUyXt5M/yhz8ekcb1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/signal-exit\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/signal-exit/-/signal-exit-3.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wnD2ZE+l+SPC/uoS0vXeE9L1+0wuaMqKlfz9AMUo38JsyLSBWSFcHR1Rri62LZc12vLr1gb3jl7iwQhgwpAbGQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/sisteransi\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/sisteransi/-/sisteransi-1.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bLGGlR1QxBcynn2d5YmDX4MGjlZvy2MRBDRNHLJ8VI6l6+9FUiyTFNJ0IveOSP0bcXgVDPRcfGqA0pjaqUpfVg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/slash\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/slash/-/slash-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-g9Q1haeby36OSStwb4ntCGGGaKsaVSjQ68fBxoQcutl5fS1vuY18H3wSt3jFyFtrkx+Kz0V1G85A4MyAdDMi2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.6.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/source-map/-/source-map-0.6.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UjgapumWlbMhkBgzT7Ykc5YXUT46F0iKu8SGXq0bcwP5dz/h0Plj6enJqjz1Zbq2l5WaqYnrVbwWOWMyF3F47g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/source-map-support\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.5.13\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/source-map-support/-/source-map-support-0.5.13.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-SHSKFHadjVA5oR4PPqhtAVdcBWwRYVd6g6cAXnIbRiIwc2EhPrTuKUBdSLvlEKyIP3GCf89fltvcZiP9MMFA1w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"buffer-from\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"source-map\": \"^0.6.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/sprintf-js\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/sprintf-js/-/sprintf-js-1.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-D9cPgkvLlV3t3IzL0D0YLvGA9Ahk4PcvVwUbN0dSGr1aP0Nrt4AEnTUbuGvquEC0mA64Gqt1fzirlRs5ibXx8g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/stack-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/stack-utils/-/stack-utils-2.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XlkWvfIm6RmsWtNJx+uqtKLS8eqFbxUg0ZzLXqY0caEy9l7hruX8IpiDnjsLavoBgqCCR71TqWO8MaXYheJ3RQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/string-length\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/string-length/-/string-length-4.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+l6rNN5fYHNhZZy41RXsYptCjA2Igmq4EG7kZAYFQI1E1VTXarr6ZPXBg6eq7Y6eK4FEhY6AJlyuFIb/v/S0VQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"char-regex\": \"^1.0.2\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/string-width\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/string-width/-/string-width-4.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wKyQRQpjJ0sIp62ErSZdGsjMJWsap5oRNihHhu6G7JVO/9jIB6UyevL+tXuOqrng8j/cxKTWyWUwvSTriiZz/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"emoji-regex\": \"^8.0.0\",\n        \"is-fullwidth-code-point\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/strip-ansi\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-ansi/-/strip-ansi-6.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Y38VPSHcqkFrCpFnQ9vuSXmquuv5oXOKpGeT6aGrr3o3Gc9AlVa6JBfUSOCnbxGGZF+/0ooI7KrPuUSztUdU5A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/strip-bom\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-bom/-/strip-bom-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3xurFv5tEgii33Zi8Jtp55wEIILR9eh34FAW00PZf+JnSsTmV/ioewSgQl97JHvgjoRGwPShsWm+IdrxB35d0w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/strip-final-newline\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-final-newline/-/strip-final-newline-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BrpvfNAE3dcvq7ll3xVumzjKjZQ5tI1sEUIKr3Uoks0XUl45St3FlatVqef9prk4jRDzhW6WZg+3bk93y6pLjA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/strip-json-comments\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-json-comments/-/strip-json-comments-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6fPc+R4ihwqP6N/aIv2f1gMH8lOVtWQHoqC4yK6oSDVVocumAsfCqjkXnqiYMhmMwS/mEHLp7Vehlt3ql6lEig==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/supports-color\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-color/-/supports-color-7.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qpCAvRl9stuOHveKsn7HncJRvv501qIacKzQlO/+Lwxc9+0q2wLyv4Dfvt80/DPn2pqOBsJdDiogXGR9+OvwRw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag/-/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag-1.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ot0WnXS9fgdkgIcePe6RHNk1WA8+muPa6cSjeR3V8K27q9BB1rTE3R1p7Hv0z1ZyAc8s6Vvv8DIyWf681MAt0w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/test-exclude\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/test-exclude/-/test-exclude-6.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-cAGWPIyOHU6zlmg88jwm7VRyXnMN7iV68OGAbYDk/Mh/xC/pzVPlQtY6ngoIH/5/tciuhGfvESU8GrHrcxD56w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.4\",\n        \"minimatch\": \"^3.0.4\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/tmpl\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/tmpl/-/tmpl-1.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3f0uOEAQwIqGuWW2MVzYg8fV/QNnc/IpuJNG837rLuczAaLVHslWHZQj4IGiEl5Hs3kkbhwL9Ab7Hrsmuj+Smw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/to-regex-range\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/to-regex-range/-/to-regex-range-5.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-65P7iz6X5yEr1cwcgvQxbbIw7Uk3gOy5dIdtZ4rDveLqhrdJP+Li/Hx6tyK0NEb+2GCyneCMJiGqrADCSNk8sQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/type-detect\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/type-detect/-/type-detect-4.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0fr/mIH1dlO+x7TlcMy+bIDqKPsw/70tVyeHW787goQjhmqaZe10uwLujubK9q9Lg6Fiho1KUKDYz0Z7k7g5/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/type-fest\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.21.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/type-fest/-/type-fest-0.21.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-t0rzBq87m3fVcduHDUFhKmyyX+9eo6WQjZvf51Ea/M0Q7+T374Jp1aUiyUl0GKxp8M/OETVHSDvmkyPgvX+X2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/undici-types\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.21.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/undici-types/-/undici-types-6.21.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iwDZqg0QAGrg9Rav5H4n0M64c3mkR59cJ6wQp+7C4nI0gsmExaedaYLNO44eT4AtBBwjbTiGPMlt2Md0T9H9JQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/update-browserslist-db\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/update-browserslist-db/-/update-browserslist-db-1.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UxhIZQ+QInVdunkDAaiazvvT/+fXL5Osr0JZlJulepYu6Jd7qJtDZjlur0emRlT71EN3ScPoE7gvsuIKKNavKw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n          \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"tidelift\",\n          \"url\": \"https://tidelift.com/funding/github/npm/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"github\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/ai\"\n        }\n      ],\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/v8-to-istanbul\": {\n      \"version\": \"9.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/v8-to-istanbul/-/v8-to-istanbul-9.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kiGUalWN+rgBJ/1OHZsBtU4rXZOfj/7rKQxULKlIzwzQSvMJUUNgPwJEEh7gU6xEVxC0ahoOBvN2YI8GH6FNgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.12\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.1\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/walker\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/walker/-/walker-1.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ts/8E8l5b7kY0vlWLewOkDXMmPdLcVV4GmOQLyxuSswIJsweeFZtAsMF7k1Nszz+TYBQrlYRmzOnr398y1JemQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/which\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/which/-/which-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BLI3Tl1TW3Pvl70l3yq3Y64i+awpwXqsGBYWkkqMtnbXgrMD+yj7rhW0kuEDxzJaYXGjEW5ogapKNMEKNMjibA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/wrap-ansi\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/wrap-ansi/-/wrap-ansi-7.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-YVGIj2kamLSTxw6NsZjoBxfSwsn0ycdesmc4p+Q21c5zPuZ1pl+NfxVdxPtdHvmNVOQ6XSYG4AUtyt/Fi7D16Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/wrappy\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/wrappy/-/wrappy-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-l4Sp/DRseor9wL6EvV2+TuQn63dMkPjZ/sp9XkghTEbV9KlPS1xUsZ3u7/IQO4wxtcFB4bgpQPRcR3QCvezPcQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/write-file-atomic\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/write-file-atomic/-/write-file-atomic-4.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7KxauUdBmSdWnmpaGFg+ppNjKF8uNLry8LyzjauQDOVONfFLNKrKvQOxZ/VuTIcS/gge/YNahf5RIIQWTSarlg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"imurmurhash\": \"^0.1.4\",\n        \"signal-exit\": \"^3.0.7\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/y18n\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/y18n/-/y18n-5.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0pfFzegeDWJHJIAmTLRP2DwHjdF5s7jo9tuztdQxAhINCdvS+3nGINqPd00AphqJR/0LhANUS6/+7SCb98YOfA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/yallist\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yallist/-/yallist-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-a4UGQaWPH59mOXUYnAG2ewncQS4i4F43Tv3JoAM+s2VDAmS9NsK8GpDMLrCHPksFT7h3K6TOoUNn2pb7RoXx4g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/yargs\": {\n      \"version\": \"17.7.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yargs/-/yargs-17.7.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7dSzzRQ++CKnNI/krKnYRV7JKKPUXMEh61soaHKg9mrWEhzFWhFnxPxGl+69cD1Ou63C13NUPCnmIcrvqCuM6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"cliui\": \"^8.0.1\",\n        \"escalade\": \"^3.1.1\",\n        \"get-caller-file\": \"^2.0.5\",\n        \"require-directory\": \"^2.1.1\",\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.2.3\",\n        \"y18n\": \"^5.0.5\",\n        \"yargs-parser\": \"^21.1.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/yargs-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"21.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yargs-parser/-/yargs-parser-21.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tVpsJW7DdjecAiFpbIB1e3qxIQsE6NoPc5/eTdrbbIC4h0LVsWhnoa3g+m2HclBIujHzsxZ4VJVA+GUuc2/LBw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/yocto-queue\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yocto-queue/-/yocto-queue-0.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-rVksvsnNCdJ/ohGc6xgPwyN8eheCxsiLM8mxuE/t/mOVqJewPuO1miLpTHQiRgTKCLexL4MeAFVagts7HmNZ2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    }\n  },\n  \"dependencies\": {\n    \"@ampproject/remapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@ampproject/remapping/-/remapping-2.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-30iZtAPgz+LTIYoeivqYo853f02jBYSd5uGnGpkFV0M3xOt9aN73erkgYAmZU43x4VfqcnLxW9Kpg3R5LC4YYw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": \"^0.3.5\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.24\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/code-frame\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/code-frame/-/code-frame-7.26.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RJlIHRueQgwWitWgF8OdFYGZX328Ax5BCemNGlqHfplnRT9ESi8JkFlvaVYbS+UubVY6dpv87Fs2u5M29iNFVQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"js-tokens\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"picocolors\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/compat-data\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/compat-data/-/compat-data-7.26.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-oH5UPLMWR3L2wEFLnFJ1TZXqHufiTKAiLfqw5zkhS4dKXLJ10yVztfil/twG8EDTA4F/tvVNw9nOl4ZMslB8rQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/core\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/core/-/core-7.26.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-vMqyb7XCDMPvJFFOaT9kxtiRh42GwlZEg1/uIgtZshS5a/8OaduUfCi7kynKgc3Tw/6Uo2D+db9qBttghhmxwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@ampproject/remapping\": \"^2.2.0\",\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/helper-compilation-targets\": \"^7.26.5\",\n        \"@babel/helper-module-transforms\": \"^7.26.0\",\n        \"@babel/helpers\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.26.9\",\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"debug\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"gensync\": \"^1.0.0-beta.2\",\n        \"json5\": \"^2.2.3\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/generator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/generator/-/generator-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-VybsKvpiN1gU1sdMZIp7FcqphVVKEwcuj02x73uvcHE0PTihx1nlBcowYWhDwjpoAXRv43+gDzyggGnn1XZhVw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": \"^0.3.5\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.25\",\n        \"jsesc\": \"^3.0.2\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-compilation-targets\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-compilation-targets/-/helper-compilation-targets-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LVk7fbXml0H2xH34dFzKQ7TDZ2G4/rVTOrq9V+icbbadjbVxxeFeDsNHv2SrZeWoA+6ZiTyWYWtScEIW07EAcA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/compat-data\": \"^7.26.8\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-option\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"browserslist\": \"^4.24.0\",\n        \"lru-cache\": \"^5.1.1\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-module-imports\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-module-imports/-/helper-module-imports-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tnUA4RsrmflIM6W6RFTLFSXITtl0wKjgpnLgXyowocVPrbYrLUXSBXDgTs8BlbmIzIdlBySRQjINYs2BAkiLtw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-module-transforms\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-module-transforms/-/helper-module-transforms-7.26.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xO+xu6B5K2czEnQye6BHA7DolFFmS3LB7stHZFaOLb1pAwO1HWLS8fXA+eh0A2yIvltPVmx3eNNDBJA2SLHXFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-module-imports\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-plugin-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-plugin-utils/-/helper-plugin-utils-7.26.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RS+jZcRdZdRFzMyr+wcsaqOmld1/EqTghfaBGQQd/WnRdzdlvSZ//kF7U8VQTxf1ynZ4cjUcYgjVGx13ewNPMg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-string-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-string-parser/-/helper-string-parser-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-4A/SCr/2KLd5jrtOMFzaKjVtAei3+2r/NChoBNoZ3EyP/+GlhoaEGoWOZUmFmoITP7zOJyHIMm+DYRd8o3PvHA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-validator-identifier/-/helper-validator-identifier-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Ed61U6XJc3CVRfkERJWDz4dJwKe7iLmmJsbOGu9wSloNSFttHV0I8g6UAgb7qnK5ly5bGLPd4oXZlxCdANBOWQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-validator-option\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-validator-option/-/helper-validator-option-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-e/zv1co8pp55dNdEcCynfj9X7nyUKUXoUEwfXqaZt0omVOmDe9oOTdKStH4GmAw6zxMFs50ZayuMfHDKlO7Tfw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/helpers\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helpers/-/helpers-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-U5eyP/CTFPuNE3qk+WZMxFkp/4zUzdceQlfzf7DdGdhp+Fezd7HD+i8Y24ZuTMKX3wQBld449jijbGq6OdGNQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/parser/-/parser-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iaepho73/2Pz7w2eMS0Q5f83+0RKI7i4xmiYeBmDzfRVbQtTOG7Ts0S4HzJVsTMGI9keU8rNfuZr8DKfSt7Yyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators/-/plugin-syntax-async-generators-7.8.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tycmZxkGfZaxhMRbXlPXuVFpdWlXpir2W4AMhSJgRKzk/eDlIXOhb2LHWoLpDF7TEHylV5zNhykX6KAgHJmTNw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint/-/plugin-syntax-bigint-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wnTnFlG+YxQm3vDxpGE57Pj0srRU4sHE/mDkt1qv2YJJSeUAec2ma4WLUnUPeKjyrfntVwe/N6dCXpU+zL3Npg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.12.13\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties/-/plugin-syntax-class-properties-7.12.13.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fm4idjKla0YahUNgFNLCB0qySdsoPiZP3iQE3rky0mBUtMZ23yDJ9SJdg6dXTSDnulOVqiF3Hgr9nbXvXTQZYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block/-/plugin-syntax-class-static-block-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-b+YyPmr6ldyNnM6sqYeMWE+bgJcJpO6yS4QD7ymxgH34GBPNDM/THBh8iunyvKIZztiwLH4CJZ0RxTk9emgpjw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes/-/plugin-syntax-import-attributes-7.26.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-e2dttdsJ1ZTpi3B9UYGLw41hifAubg19AtCu/2I/F1QNVclOBr1dYpTdmdyZ84Xiz43BS/tCUkMAZNLv12Pi+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta/-/plugin-syntax-import-meta-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Yqfm+XDx0+Prh3VSeEQCPU81yC+JWZ2pDPFSS4ZdpfZhp4MkFMaDC1UqseovEKwSUpnIL7+vK+Clp7bfh0iD7g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings/-/plugin-syntax-json-strings-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lY6kdGpWHvjoe2vk4WrAapEuBR69EMxZl+RoGRhrFGNYVK8mOPAW8VfbT/ZgrFbXlDNiiaxQnAtgVCZ6jv30EA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx/-/plugin-syntax-jsx-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ld6oezHQMZsZfp6pWtbjaNDF2tiiCYYDqQszHt5VV437lewP9aSi2Of99CK0D0XB21k7FLgnLcmQKyKzynfeAA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators/-/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-d8waShlpFDinQ5MtvGU9xDAOzKH47+FFoney2baFIoMr952hKOLp1HR7VszoZvOsV/4+RRszNY7D17ba0te0ig==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator/-/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-aSff4zPII1u2QD7y+F8oDsz19ew4IGEJg9SVW+bqwpwtfFleiQDMdzA/R+UlWDzfnHFCxxleFT0PMIrR36XLNQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator/-/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9H6YdfkcK/uOnY/K7/aA2xpzaAgkQn37yzWUMRK7OaPOqOpGS1+n0H5hxT9AUw9EsSjPW8SVyMJwYRtWs3X3ug==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread/-/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XoqMijGZb9y3y2XskN+P1wUGiVwWZ5JmoDRwx5+3GmEplNyVM2s2Dg8ILFQm8rWM48orGy5YpI5Bl8U1y7ydlA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding/-/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6VPD0Pc1lpTqw0aKoeRTMiB+kWhAoT24PA+ksWSBrFtl5SIRVpZlwN3NNPQjehA2E/91FV3RjLWoVTglWcSV3Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining/-/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KoK9ErH1MBlCPxV0VANkXW2/dw4vlbGDrFgz8bmUsBGYkFRcbRwMh6cIJubdPrkxRwuGdtCk0v/wPTKbQgBjkg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object/-/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0wVnp9dxJ72ZUJDV27ZfbSj6iHLoytYZmh3rFcxNnvsJF3ktkzLDZPy/mA17HGsaQT3/DQsWYX1f1QGWkCoVUg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await/-/plugin-syntax-top-level-await-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hx++upLv5U1rgYfwe1xBQUhRmU41NEvpUvrp8jkrSCdvGSnM5/qdRMtylJ6PG5OFkBaHkbTAKTnd3/YyESRHFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript/-/plugin-syntax-typescript-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hjMgRy5hb8uJJjUcdWunWVcoi9bGpJp8p5Ol1229PoN6aytsLwNMgmdftO23wnCLMfVmTwZDWMPNq/D1SY60JQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/template\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/template/-/template-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2ncevenBqXI6qRMukPlXwHKHchC7RyMuu4xv5JBXRfOGVcTy1mXCD12qrp7Jsoxll1EV3+9sE4GugBVRjT2jFA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/traverse\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/traverse/-/traverse-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-19lYZFzYVQkkHkl4Cy4WrAVcqBkgvV2YM2TU3xG6DIwO7O3ecbDPfW3yM3bjAGcqcQHi+CCtjMR3dIEHxsd6bA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"debug\": \"^4.3.1\",\n        \"globals\": \"^11.1.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/types\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/types/-/types-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-H45s8fVLYjbhFH62dIJ3WtmJ6RSPt/3DRO0ZcT2SUiYiQyz3BLVb9ADEnLl91m74aQPS3AzzeajZHYOalWe3bg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-string-parser\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@bcoe/v8-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@bcoe/v8-coverage/-/v8-coverage-0.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0hYQ8SB4Db5zvZB4axdMHGwEaQjkZzFjQiN9LVYvIFB2nSUHW9tYpxWriPrWDASIxiaXax83REcLxuSdnGPZtw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config/-/load-nyc-config-1.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-VjeHSlIzpv/NyD3N0YuHfXOPDIixcA1q2ZV98wsMqcYlPmv2n3Yb2lYP9XMElnaFVXg5A7YLTeLu6V84uQDjmQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"camelcase\": \"^5.3.1\",\n        \"find-up\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"get-package-type\": \"^0.1.0\",\n        \"js-yaml\": \"^3.13.1\",\n        \"resolve-from\": \"^5.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@istanbuljs/schema\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@istanbuljs/schema/-/schema-0.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ZXRY4jNvVgSVQ8DL3LTcakaAtXwTVUxE81hslsyD2AtoXW/wVob10HkOJ1X/pAlcI7D+2YoZKg5do8G/w6RYgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@jest/console\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/console/-/console-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-5Ni4CU7XHQi32IJ398EEP4RrB8eV09sXP2ROqD4bksHrnTree52PsxvX8tpL8LvTZ3pFzXyPbNQReSN41CAhOg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/core\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/core/-/core-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-n7aeXWKMnGtDA48y8TLWJPJmLmmZ642Ceo78cYWEpiD7FzDgmNDV/GCVRorPABdXLJZ/9wzzgZAlHjXjxDHGsg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/reporters\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"ansi-escapes\": \"^4.2.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-changed-files\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-resolve-dependencies\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runner\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-watcher\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/environment\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/environment/-/environment-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-aQIfHDq33ExsN4jP1NWGXhxgQ/wixs60gDiKO+XVMd8Mn0NWPWgc34ZQDTb2jKaUWQ7MuwoitXAsN2XVXNMpAw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/expect\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/expect/-/expect-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-8uMeAMycttpva3P1lBHB8VciS9V0XAr3GymPpipdyQXbBcuhkLQOSe8E/p92RyAdToS6ZD1tFkX+CkhoECE0dQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/expect-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/expect-utils/-/expect-utils-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GlsNBWiFQFCVi9QVSx7f5AgMeLxe9YCCs5PuP2O2LdjDAA8Jh9eX7lA1Jq/xdXw3Wb3hyvlFNfZIfcRetSzYcA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@jest/fake-timers\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/fake-timers/-/fake-timers-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-q4DH1Ha4TTFPdxLsqDXK1d3+ioSL7yL5oCMJZgDYm6i+6CygW5E5xVr/D1HdsGxjt1ZWSfUAs9OxSB/BNelWrQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@sinonjs/fake-timers\": \"^10.0.2\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/globals\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/globals/-/globals-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-mpiz3dutLbkW2MNFubUGUEVLkTGiqW6yLVTA+JbP6fI6J5iL9Y0Nlg8k95pcF8ctKwCS7WVxteBs29hhfAotzQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/reporters\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/reporters/-/reporters-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DApq0KJbJOEzAFYjHADNNxAE3KbhxQB1y5Kplb5Waqw6zVbuWatSnMjE5gs8FUgEPmNsnZA3NCWl9NG0ia04Pg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@bcoe/v8-coverage\": \"^0.2.3\",\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-report\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-source-maps\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-reports\": \"^3.1.3\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"string-length\": \"^4.0.1\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"v8-to-istanbul\": \"^9.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/schemas\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/schemas/-/schemas-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-mo5j5X+jIZmJQveBKeS/clAueipV7KgiX1vMgCxam1RNYiqE1w62n0/tJJnHtjW8ZHcQco5gY85jA3mi0L+nSA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@jest/source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/source-map/-/source-map-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MHjT95QuipcPrpLM+8JMSzFx6eHp5Bm+4XeFDJlwsvVBjmKNiIAvasGK2fxz2WbGRlnvqehFbh07MMa7n3YJnw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"callsites\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/test-result\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/test-result/-/test-result-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Fdx+tv6x1zlkJPcWXmMDAG2HBnaR9XPSd5aDWQVsfrZmLVT3lU1cwyxLgRmXR9yrq4NBoEm9BMsfgFzTQAbJYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/test-sequencer\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/test-sequencer/-/test-sequencer-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GQwJ5WZVrKnOJuiYiAF52UNUJXgTZx1NHjFSEB0qEMmSZKAkdMoIzw/Cj6x6NF4AvV23AUqDpFzQkN/eYCYTxw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/transform\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/transform/-/transform-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ok/BTPFzFKVMwO5eOHRrvnBVHdRy9IrsrW1GpMaQ9MCnilNLXQKmAX8s1YXDFaai9xJpac2ySzV0YeRRECr2Vw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": \"^6.1.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"fast-json-stable-stringify\": \"^2.1.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pirates\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"write-file-atomic\": \"^4.0.2\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/types\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/types/-/types-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-u3UPsIilWKOM3F9CXtrG8LEJmNxwoCQC/XVj4IKYXvvpx7QIi/Kg1LI5uDmDpKlac62NUtX7eLjRh+jVZcLOzw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/schemas\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-reports\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/yargs\": \"^17.0.8\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.3.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/gen-mapping/-/gen-mapping-0.3.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-imAbBGkb+ebQyxKgzv5Hu2nmROxoDOXHh80evxdoXNOrvAnVx7zimzc1Oo5h9RlfV4vPXaE2iM5pOFbvOCClWA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/set-array\": \"^1.2.1\",\n        \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": \"^1.4.10\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.24\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/resolve-uri\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/resolve-uri/-/resolve-uri-3.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bRISgCIjP20/tbWSPWMEi54QVPRZExkuD9lJL+UIxUKtwVJA8wW1Trb1jMs1RFXo1CBTNZ/5hpC9QvmKWdopKw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/set-array\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/set-array/-/set-array-1.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R8gLRTZeyp03ymzP/6Lil/28tGeGEzhx1q2k703KGWRAI1VdvPIXdG70VJc2pAMw3NA6JKL5hhFu1sJX0Mnn/A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec/-/sourcemap-codec-1.5.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gv3ZRaISU3fjPAgNsriBRqGWQL6quFx04YMPW/zD8XMLsU32mhCCbfbO6KZFLjvYpCZ8zyDEgqsgf+PwPaM7GQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.3.25\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/trace-mapping/-/trace-mapping-0.3.25.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-vNk6aEwybGtawWmy/PzwnGDOjCkLWSD2wqvjGGAgOAwCGWySYXfYoxt00IJkTF+8Lb57DwOb3Aa0o9CApepiYQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/resolve-uri\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": \"^1.4.14\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@sinclair/typebox\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.27.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinclair/typebox/-/typebox-0.27.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+Fj43pSMwJs4KRrH/938Uf+uAELIgVBmQzg/q1YG10djyfA3TnrU8N8XzqCh/okZdszqBQTZf96idMfE5lnwTA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@sinonjs/commons\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinonjs/commons/-/commons-3.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-K3mCHKQ9sVh8o1C9cxkwxaOmXoAMlDxC1mYyHrjqOWEcBjYr76t96zL2zlj5dUGZ3HSw240X1qgH3Mjf1yJWpQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@sinonjs/fake-timers\": {\n      \"version\": \"10.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinonjs/fake-timers/-/fake-timers-10.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-V4BG07kuYSUkTCSBHG8G8TNhM+F19jXFWnQtzj+we8DrkpSBCee9Z3Ms8yiGer/dlmhe35/Xdgyo3/0rQKg7YA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/babel__core\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.20.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__core/-/babel__core-7.20.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qoQprZvz5wQFJwMDqeseRXWv3rqMvhgpbXFfVyWhbx9X47POIA6i/+dXefEmZKoAgOaTdaIgNSMqMIU61yRyzA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.20.7\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.20.7\",\n        \"@types/babel__generator\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/babel__template\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/babel__traverse\": \"*\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@types/babel__generator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__generator/-/babel__generator-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ufFd2Xi92OAVPYsy+P4n7/U7e68fex0+Ee8gSG9KX7eo084CWiQ4sdxktvdl0bOPupXtVJPY19zk6EwWqUQ8lg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/babel__template\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.4.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__template/-/babel__template-7.4.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-h/NUaSyG5EyxBIp8YRxo4RMe2/qQgvyowRwVMzhYhBCONbW8PUsg4lkFMrhgZhUe5z3L3MiLDuvyJ/CaPa2A8A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.1.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@types/babel__traverse\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.20.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__traverse/-/babel__traverse-7.20.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-dkO5fhS7+/oos4ciWxyEyjWe48zmG6wbCheo/G2ZnHx4fs3EU6YC6UM8rk56gAjNJ9P3MTH2jo5jb92/K6wbng==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/graceful-fs\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/graceful-fs/-/graceful-fs-4.1.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-olP3sd1qOEe5dXTSaFvQG+02VdRXcdytWLAZsAq1PecU8uqQAhkrnbli7DagjtXKW/Bl7YJbUsa8MPcuc8LHEQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-lib-coverage/-/istanbul-lib-coverage-2.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2QF/t/auWm0lsy8XtKVPG19v3sSOQlJe/YHZgfjb/KBBHOGSV+J2q/S671rcq9uTBrLAXmZpqJiaQbMT+zNU1w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@types/istanbul-lib-report\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-lib-report/-/istanbul-lib-report-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NQn7AHQnk/RSLOxrBbGyJM/aVQ+pjj5HCgasFxc0K/KhoATfQ/47AyUl15I2yBUpihjmas+a+VJBOqecrFH+uA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/istanbul-reports\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-reports/-/istanbul-reports-3.0.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pk2B1NWalF9toCRu6gjBzR69syFjP4Od8WRAX+0mmf9lAjCRicLOWc+ZrxZHx/0XRjotgkF9t6iaMJ+aXcOdZQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/node\": {\n      \"version\": \"22.14.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/node/-/node-22.14.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-u0HuPQwe/dHrItgHHpmw3N2fYCR6x4ivMNbPHRkBVP4CvN+kiRrKHWk3i8tXiO/joPwXLMYvF9TTF0eqgHIuOw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/stack-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/stack-utils/-/stack-utils-2.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9aEbYZ3TbYMznPdcdr3SmIrLXwC/AKZXQeCf9Pgao5CKb8CyHuEX5jzWPTkvregvhRJHcpRO6BFoGW9ycaOkYw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@types/yargs\": {\n      \"version\": \"17.0.33\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/yargs/-/yargs-17.0.33.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WpxBCKWPLr4xSsHgz511rFJAM+wS28w2zEO1QDNY5zM/S8ok70NNfztH0xwhqKyaK0OHCbN98LDAZuy1ctxDkA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/yargs-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"21.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/yargs-parser/-/yargs-parser-21.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-I4q9QU9MQv4oEOz4tAHJtNz1cwuLxn2F3xcc2iV5WdqLPpUnj30aUuxt1mAxYTG+oe8CZMV/+6rU4S4gRDzqtQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"ansi-escapes\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-escapes/-/ansi-escapes-4.3.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gKXj5ALrKWQLsYG9jlTRmR/xKluxHV+Z9QEwNIgCfM1/uwPMCuzVVnh5mwTd+OuBZcwSIMbqssNWRm1lE51QaQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"ansi-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-regex/-/ansi-regex-5.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-quJQXlTSUGL2LH9SUXo8VwsY4soanhgo6LNSm84E1LBcE8s3O0wpdiRzyR9z/ZZJMlMWv37qOOb9pdJlMUEKFQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"ansi-styles\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-styles/-/ansi-styles-4.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zbB9rCJAT1rbjiVDb2hqKFHNYLxgtk8NURxZ3IZwD3F6NtxbXZQCnnSi1Lkx+IDohdPlFp222wVALIheZJQSEg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"anymatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/anymatch/-/anymatch-3.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KMReFUr0B4t+D+OBkjR3KYqvocp2XaSzO55UcB6mgQMd3KbcE+mWTyvVV7D/zsdEbNnV6acZUutkiHQXvTr1Rw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"normalize-path\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"picomatch\": \"^2.0.4\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"argparse\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/argparse/-/argparse-1.0.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-o5Roy6tNG4SL/FOkCAN6RzjiakZS25RLYFrcMttJqbdd8BWrnA+fGz57iN5Pb06pvBGvl5gQ0B48dJlslXvoTg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"babel-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-jest/-/babel-jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BrvGY3xZSwEcCzKvKsCi2GgHqDqsYkOP4/by5xCgIwGXQxIEh+8ew3gmrE1y7XRR6LHZIj6yLYnUi/mm2KXKBg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@types/babel__core\": \"^7.1.14\",\n        \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": \"^6.1.1\",\n        \"babel-preset-jest\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-plugin-istanbul/-/babel-plugin-istanbul-6.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Y1IQok9821cC9onCx5otgFfRm7Lm+I+wwxOx738M/WLPZ9Q42m4IG5W0FNX8WLL2gYMZo3JkuXIH2DOpWM+qwA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-plugin-utils\": \"^7.0.0\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": \"^5.0.4\",\n        \"test-exclude\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": {\n          \"version\": \"5.2.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-instrument/-/istanbul-lib-instrument-5.2.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-pzqtp31nLv/XFOzXGuvhCb8qhjmTVo5vjVk19XE4CRlSWz0KoeJ3bw9XsA7nOp9YBf4qHjwBxkDzKcME/J29Yg==\",\n          \"dev\": true,\n          \"requires\": {\n            \"@babel/core\": \"^7.12.3\",\n            \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.14.7\",\n            \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n            \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.2.0\",\n            \"semver\": \"^6.3.0\"\n          }\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"babel-plugin-jest-hoist\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-plugin-jest-hoist/-/babel-plugin-jest-hoist-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ESAc/RJvGTFEzRwOTT4+lNDk/GNHMkKbNzsvT0qKRfDyyYTskxB5rnU2njIDYVxXCBHHEI1c0YwHob3WaYujOg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@types/babel__core\": \"^7.1.14\",\n        \"@types/babel__traverse\": \"^7.0.6\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-preset-current-node-syntax/-/babel-preset-current-node-syntax-1.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ldYss8SbBlWva1bs28q78Ju5Zq1F+8BrqBZZ0VFhLBvhh6lCpC2o3gDJi/5DRLs9FgYZCnmPYIVFU4lRXCkyUw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators\": \"^7.8.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties\": \"^7.12.13\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block\": \"^7.14.5\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes\": \"^7.24.7\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object\": \"^7.14.5\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await\": \"^7.14.5\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"babel-preset-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-preset-jest/-/babel-preset-jest-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0B3bhxR6snWXJZtR/RliHTDPRgn1sNHOR0yVtq/IiQFyuOVjFS+wuio/R4gSNkyYmKmJB4wGZv2NZanmKmTnNA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"babel-plugin-jest-hoist\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"balanced-match\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/balanced-match/-/balanced-match-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3oSeUO0TMV67hN1AmbXsK4yaqU7tjiHlbxRDZOpH0KW9+CeX4bRAaX0Anxt0tx2MrpRpWwQaPwIlISEJhYU5Pw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"brace-expansion\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.11\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/brace-expansion/-/brace-expansion-1.1.11.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iCuPHDFgrHX7H2vEI/5xpz07zSHB00TpugqhmYtVmMO6518mCuRMoOYFldEBl0g187ufozdaHgWKcYFb61qGiA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"balanced-match\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"concat-map\": \"0.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"braces\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/braces/-/braces-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-yQbXgO/OSZVD2IsiLlro+7Hf6Q18EJrKSEsdoMzKePKXct3gvD8oLcOQdIzGupr5Fj+EDe8gO/lxc1BzfMpxvA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"browserslist\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.24.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/browserslist/-/browserslist-4.24.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KDi1Ny1gSePi1vm0q4oxSF8b4DR44GF4BbmS2YdhPLOEqd8pDviZOGH/GsmRwoWJ2+5Lr085X7naowMwKHDG1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"caniuse-lite\": \"^1.0.30001688\",\n        \"electron-to-chromium\": \"^1.5.73\",\n        \"node-releases\": \"^2.0.19\",\n        \"update-browserslist-db\": \"^1.1.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"bser\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/bser/-/bser-2.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gQxTNE/GAfIIrmHLUE3oJyp5FO6HRBfhjnw4/wMmA63ZGDJnWBmgY/lyQBpnDUkGmAhbSe39tx2d/iTOAfglwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"buffer-from\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/buffer-from/-/buffer-from-1.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-E+XQCRwSbaaiChtv6k6Dwgc+bx+Bs6vuKJHHl5kox/BaKbhiXzqQOwK4cO22yElGp2OCmjwVhT3HmxgyPGnJfQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"callsites\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/callsites/-/callsites-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-P8BjAsXvZS+VIDUI11hHCQEv74YT67YUi5JJFNWIqL235sBmjX4+qx9Muvls5ivyNENctx46xQLQ3aTuE7ssaQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"camelcase\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/camelcase/-/camelcase-5.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-L28STB170nwWS63UjtlEOE3dldQApaJXZkOI1uMFfzf3rRuPegHaHesyee+YxQ+W6SvRDQV6UrdOdRiR153wJg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"caniuse-lite\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.30001715\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/caniuse-lite/-/caniuse-lite-1.0.30001715.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7ptkFGMm2OAOgvZpwgA4yjQ5SQbrNVGdRjzH0pBdy1Fasvcr+KAeECmbCAECzTuDuoX0FCY8KzUxjf9+9kfZEw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"chalk\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/chalk/-/chalk-4.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-oKnbhFyRIXpUuez8iBMmyEa4nbj4IOQyuhc/wy9kY7/WVPcwIO9VA668Pu8RkO7+0G76SLROeyw9CpQ061i4mA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^7.1.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"char-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/char-regex/-/char-regex-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kWWXztvZ5SBQV+eRgKFeh8q5sLuZY2+8WUIzlxWVTg+oGwY14qylx1KbKzHd8P6ZYkAg0xyIDU9JMHhyJMZ1jw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"ci-info\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.9.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ci-info/-/ci-info-3.9.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NIxF55hv4nSqQswkAeiOi1r83xy8JldOFDTWiug55KBu9Jnblncd2U6ViHmYgHf01TPZS77NJBhBMKdWj9HQMQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"cjs-module-lexer\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cjs-module-lexer/-/cjs-module-lexer-1.4.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9z8TZaGM1pfswYeXrUpzPrkx8UnWYdhJclsiYMm6x/w5+nN+8Tf/LnAgfLGQCm59qAOxU8WwHEq2vNwF6i4j+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"cliui\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cliui/-/cliui-8.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BSeNnyus75C4//NQ9gQt1/csTXyo/8Sb+afLAkzAptFuMsod9HFokGNudZpi/oQV73hnVK+sR+5PVRMd+Dr7YQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.2.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.1\",\n        \"wrap-ansi\": \"^7.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"co\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.6.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/co/-/co-4.6.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-QVb0dM5HvG+uaxitm8wONl7jltx8dqhfU33DcqtOZcLSVIKSDDLDi7+0LbAKiyI8hD9u42m2YxXSkMGWThaecQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"collect-v8-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/collect-v8-coverage/-/collect-v8-coverage-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lHl4d5/ONEbLlJvaJNtsF/Lz+WvB07u2ycqTYbdrq7UypDXailES4valYb2eWiJFxZlVmpGekfqoxQhzyFdT4Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"color-convert\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/color-convert/-/color-convert-2.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RRECPsj7iu/xb5oKYcsFHSppFNnsj/52OVTRKb4zP5onXwVF3zVmmToNcOfGC+CRDpfK/U584fMg38ZHCaElKQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"color-name\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/color-name/-/color-name-1.1.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-dOy+3AuW3a2wNbZHIuMZpTcgjGuLU/uBL/ubcZF9OXbDo8ff4O8yVp5Bf0efS8uEoYo5q4Fx7dY9OgQGXgAsQA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"concat-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/concat-map/-/concat-map-0.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/Srv4dswyQNBfohGpz9o6Yb3Gz3SrUDqBH5rTuhGR7ahtlbYKnVxw2bCFMRljaA7EXHaXZ8wsHdodFvbkhKmqg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"convert-source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/convert-source-map/-/convert-source-map-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Kvp459HrV2FEJ1CAsi1Ku+MY3kasH19TFykTz2xWmMeq6bk2NU3XXvfJ+Q61m0xktWwt+1HSYf3JZsTms3aRJg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"create-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/create-jest/-/create-jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Adz2bdH0Vq3F53KEMJOoftQFutWCukm6J24wbPWRO4k1kMY7gS7ds/uoJkNuV8wDCtWWnuwGcJwpWcih+zEW1Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"prompts\": \"^2.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"cross-spawn\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cross-spawn/-/cross-spawn-7.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-uV2QOWP2nWzsy2aMp8aRibhi9dlzF5Hgh5SHaB9OiTGEyDTiJJyx0uy51QXdyWbtAHNua4XJzUKca3OzKUd3vA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"path-key\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"shebang-command\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"which\": \"^2.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"debug\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/debug/-/debug-4.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6WTZ/IxCY/T6BALoZHaE4ctp9xm+Z5kY/pzYaCHRFeyVhojxlrm+46y68HA6hr0TcwEssoxNiDEUJQjfPZ/RYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"dedent\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/dedent/-/dedent-1.5.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NHQtfOOW68WD8lgypbLA5oT+Bt0xXJhiYvoR6SmmNXZfpzOGXwdKWmcwG8N7PwVVWV3eF/68nmD9BaJSsTBhyQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {}\n    },\n    \"deepmerge\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/deepmerge/-/deepmerge-4.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3sUqbMEc77XqpdNO7FRyRog+eW3ph+GYCbj+rK+uYyRMuwsVy0rMiVtPn+QJlKFvWP/1PYpapqYn0Me2knFn+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"detect-newline\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/detect-newline/-/detect-newline-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TLz+x/vEXm/Y7P7wn1EJFNLxYpUD4TgMosxY6fAVJUnJMbupHBOncxyWUG9OpTaH9EBD7uFI5LfEgmMOc54DsA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"diff-sequences\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/diff-sequences/-/diff-sequences-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-EjePK1srD3P08o2j4f0ExnylqRs5B9tJjcp9t1krH2qRi8CCdsYfwe9JgSLurFBWwq4uOlipzfk5fHNvwFKr8Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"electron-to-chromium\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.140\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/electron-to-chromium/-/electron-to-chromium-1.5.140.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-o82Rj+ONp4Ip7Cl1r7lrqx/pXhbp/lh9DpKcMNscFJdh8ebyRofnc7Sh01B4jx403RI0oqTBvlZ7OBIZLMr2+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"emittery\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.13.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/emittery/-/emittery-0.13.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DeWwawk6r5yR9jFgnDKYt4sLS0LmHJJi3ZOnb5/JdbYwj3nW+FxQnHIjhBKz8YLC7oRNPVM9NQ47I3CVx34eqQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"emoji-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/emoji-regex/-/emoji-regex-8.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MSjYzcWNOA0ewAHpz0MxpYFvwg6yjy1NG3xteoqz644VCo/RPgnr1/GGt+ic3iJTzQ8Eu3TdM14SawnVUmGE6A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"error-ex\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.3.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/error-ex/-/error-ex-1.3.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7dFHNmqeFSEt2ZBsCriorKnn3Z2pj+fd9kmI6QoWw4//DL+icEBfc0U7qJCisqrTsKTjw4fNFy2pW9OqStD84g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"escalade\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/escalade/-/escalade-3.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WUj2qlxaQtO4g6Pq5c29GTcWGDyd8itL8zTlipgECz3JesAiiOKotd8JU6otB3PACgG6xkJUyVhboMS+bje/jA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"escape-string-regexp\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/escape-string-regexp/-/escape-string-regexp-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UpzcLCXolUWcNu5HtVMHYdXJjArjsF9C0aNnquZYY4uW/Vu0miy5YoWvbV345HauVvcAUnpRuhMMcqTcGOY2+w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"esprima\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/esprima/-/esprima-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eGuFFw7Upda+g4p+QHvnW0RyTX/SVeJBDM/gCtMARO0cLuT2HcEKnTPvhjV6aGeqrCB/sbNop0Kszm0jsaWU4A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"execa\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/execa/-/execa-5.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-8uSpZZocAZRBAPIEINJj3Lo9HyGitllczc27Eh5YYojjMFMn8yHMDMaUHE2Jqfq05D/wucwI4JGURyXt1vchyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"cross-spawn\": \"^7.0.3\",\n        \"get-stream\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"human-signals\": \"^2.1.0\",\n        \"is-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"merge-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"npm-run-path\": \"^4.0.1\",\n        \"onetime\": \"^5.1.2\",\n        \"signal-exit\": \"^3.0.3\",\n        \"strip-final-newline\": \"^2.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"exit\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/exit/-/exit-0.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Zk/eNKV2zbjpKzrsQ+n1G6poVbErQxJ0LBOJXaKZ1EViLzH+hrLu9cdXI4zw9dBQJslwBEpbQ2P1oS7nDxs6jQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"expect\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/expect/-/expect-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2Zks0hf1VLFYI1kbh0I5jP3KHHyCHpkfyHBzsSXRFgl/Bg9mWYfMW8oD+PdMPlEwy5HNsR9JutYy6pMeOh61nw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/expect-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"fast-json-stable-stringify\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fast-json-stable-stringify/-/fast-json-stable-stringify-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lhd/wF+Lk98HZoTCtlVraHtfh5XYijIjalXck7saUtuanSDyLMxnHhSXEDJqHxD7msR8D0uCmqlkwjCV8xvwHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"fb-watchman\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fb-watchman/-/fb-watchman-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-p5161BqbuCaSnB8jIbzQHOlpgsPmK5rJVDfDKO91Axs5NC1uu3HRQm6wt9cd9/+GtQQIO53JdGXXoyDpTAsgYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"fill-range\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fill-range/-/fill-range-7.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-YsGpe3WHLK8ZYi4tWDg2Jy3ebRz2rXowDxnld4bkQB00cc/1Zw9AWnC0i9ztDJitivtQvaI9KaLyKrc+hBW0yg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"find-up\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/find-up/-/find-up-4.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-PpOwAdQ/YlXQ2vj8a3h8IipDuYRi3wceVQQGYWxNINccq40Anw7BlsEXCMbt1Zt+OLA6Fq9suIpIWD0OsnISlw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"locate-path\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"path-exists\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"fs.realpath\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fs.realpath/-/fs.realpath-1.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OO0pH2lK6a0hZnAdau5ItzHPI6pUlvI7jMVnxUQRtw4owF2wk8lOSabtGDCTP4Ggrg2MbGnWO9X8K1t4+fGMDw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"fsevents\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fsevents/-/fsevents-2.3.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-5xoDfX+fL7faATnagmWPpbFtwh/R77WmMMqqHGS65C3vvB0YHrgF+B1YmZ3441tMj5n63k0212XNoJwzlhffQw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"optional\": true\n    },\n    \"function-bind\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/function-bind/-/function-bind-1.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7XHNxH7qX9xG5mIwxkhumTox/MIRNcOgDrxWsMt2pAr23WHp6MrRlN7FBSFpCpr+oVO0F744iUgR82nJMfG2SA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"gensync\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0-beta.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/gensync/-/gensync-1.0.0-beta.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3hN7NaskYvMDLQY55gnW3NQ+mesEAepTqlg+VEbj7zzqEMBVNhzcGYYeqFo/TlYz6eQiFcp1HcsCZO+nGgS8zg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"get-caller-file\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-caller-file/-/get-caller-file-2.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DyFP3BM/3YHTQOCUL/w0OZHR0lpKeGrxotcHWcqNEdnltqFwXVfhEBQ94eIo34AfQpo0rGki4cyIiftY06h2Fg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"get-package-type\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-package-type/-/get-package-type-0.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pjzuKtY64GYfWizNAJ0fr9VqttZkNiK2iS430LtIHzjBEr6bX8Am2zm4sW4Ro5wjWW5cAlRL1qAMTcXbjNAO2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"get-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-stream/-/get-stream-6.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ts6Wi+2j3jQjqi70w5AlN8DFnkSwC+MqmxEzdEALB2qXZYV3X/b1CTfgPLGJNMeAWxdPfU8FO1ms3NUfaHCPYg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"glob\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/glob/-/glob-7.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-nFR0zLpU2YCaRxwoCJvL6UvCH2JFyFVIvwTLsIf21AuHlMskA1hhTdk+LlYJtOlYt9v6dvszD2BGRqBL+iQK9Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"fs.realpath\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"inflight\": \"^1.0.4\",\n        \"inherits\": \"2\",\n        \"minimatch\": \"^3.1.1\",\n        \"once\": \"^1.3.0\",\n        \"path-is-absolute\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"globals\": {\n      \"version\": \"11.12.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/globals/-/globals-11.12.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WOBp/EEGUiIsJSp7wcv/y6MO+lV9UoncWqxuFfm8eBwzWNgyfBd6Gz+IeKQ9jCmyhoH99g15M3T+QaVHFjizVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"graceful-fs\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.11\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/graceful-fs/-/graceful-fs-4.2.11.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RbJ5/jmFcNNCcDV5o9eTnBLJ/HszWV0P73bc+Ff4nS/rJj+YaS6IGyiOL0VoBYX+l1Wrl3k63h/KrH+nhJ0XvQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"has-flag\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/has-flag/-/has-flag-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-EykJT/Q1KjTWctppgIAgfSO0tKVuZUjhgMr17kqTumMl6Afv3EISleU7qZUzoXDFTAHTDC4NOoG/ZxU3EvlMPQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"hasown\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/hasown/-/hasown-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0hJU9SCPvmMzIBdZFqNPXWa6dqh7WdH0cII9y+CyS8rG3nL48Bclra9HmKhVVUHyPWNH5Y7xDwAB7bfgSjkUMQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"html-escaper\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/html-escaper/-/html-escaper-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-H2iMtd0I4Mt5eYiapRdIDjp+XzelXQ0tFE4JS7YFwFevXXMmOp9myNrUvCg0D6ws8iqkRPBfKHgbwig1SmlLfg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"human-signals\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/human-signals/-/human-signals-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-B4FFZ6q/T2jhhksgkbEW3HBvWIfDW85snkQgawt07S7J5QXTk6BkNV+0yAeZrM5QpMAdYlocGoljn0sJ/WQkFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"import-local\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/import-local/-/import-local-3.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2SPlun1JUPWoM6t3F0dw0FkCF/jWY8kttcY4f599GLTSjh2OCuuhdTkJQsEcZzBqbXZGKMK2OqW1oZsjtf/gQA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"imurmurhash\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/imurmurhash/-/imurmurhash-0.1.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JmXMZ6wuvDmLiHEml9ykzqO6lwFbof0GG4IkcGaENdCRDDmMVnny7s5HsIgHCbaq0w2MyPhDqkhTUgS2LU2PHA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"inflight\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/inflight/-/inflight-1.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-k92I/b08q4wvFscXCLvqfsHCrjrF7yiXsQuIVvVE7N82W3+aqpzuUdBbfhWcy/FZR3/4IgflMgKLOsvPDrGCJA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"inherits\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/inherits/-/inherits-2.0.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-k/vGaX4/Yla3WzyMCvTQOXYeIHvqOKtnqBduzTHpzpQZzAskKMhZ2K+EnBiSM9zGSoIFeMpXKxa4dYeZIQqewQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-arrayish\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-arrayish/-/is-arrayish-0.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zz06S8t0ozoDXMG+ube26zeCTNXcKIPJZJi8hBrF4idCLms4CG9QtK7qBl1boi5ODzFpjswb5JPmHCbMpjaYzg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-core-module\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.16.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-core-module/-/is-core-module-2.16.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UfoeMA6fIJ8wTYFEUjelnaGI67v6+N7qXJEvQuIGa99l4xsCruSYOVSQ0uPANn4dAzm8lkYPaKLrrijLq7x23w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"is-fullwidth-code-point\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-fullwidth-code-point/-/is-fullwidth-code-point-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zymm5+u+sCsSWyD9qNaejV3DFvhCKclKdizYaJUuHA83RLjb7nSuGnddCHGv0hk+KY7BMAlsWeK4Ueg6EV6XQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-generator-fn\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-generator-fn/-/is-generator-fn-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-cTIB4yPYL/Grw0EaSzASzg6bBy9gqCofvWN8okThAYIxKJZC+udlRAmGbM0XLeniEJSs8uEgHPGuHSe1XsOLSQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-number\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-number/-/is-number-7.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-41Cifkg6e8TylSpdtTpeLVMqvSBEVzTttHvERD741+pnZ8ANv0004MRL43QKPDlK9cGvNp6NZWZUBlbGXYxxng==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-stream/-/is-stream-2.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hFoiJiTl63nn+kstHGBtewWSKnQLpyb155KHheA1l39uvtO9nWIop1p3udqPcUd/xbF1VLMO4n7OI6p7RbngDg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"isexe\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/isexe/-/isexe-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RHxMLp9lnKHGHRng9QFhRCMbYAcVpn69smSGcq3f36xjgVVWThj4qqLbTLlq7Ssj8B+fIQ1EuCEGI2lKsyQeIw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-coverage/-/istanbul-lib-coverage-3.2.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-O8dpsF+r0WV/8MNRKfnmrtCWhuKjxrq2w+jpzBL5UZKTi2LeVWnWOmWRxFlesJONmc+wLAGvKQZEOanko0LFTg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-instrument/-/istanbul-lib-instrument-6.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Vtgk7L/R2JHyyGW07spoFlB8/lpjiOLTjMdms6AFMraYt3BaJauod/NGrfnVG/y4Ix1JEuMRPDPEj2ua+zz1/Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.23.9\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.23.9\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.3\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^7.5.4\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"semver\": {\n          \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"istanbul-lib-report\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-report/-/istanbul-lib-report-3.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GCfE1mtsHGOELCU8e/Z7YWzpmybrx/+dSTfLrvY8qRmaY6zXTKWn6WQIjaAFw069icm6GVMNkgu0NzI4iPZUNw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"make-dir\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^7.1.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"istanbul-lib-source-maps\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-source-maps/-/istanbul-lib-source-maps-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-n3s8EwkdFIJCG3BPKBYvskgXGoy88ARzvegkitk60NxRdwltLOTaH7CUiMRXvwYorl0Q712iEjcWB+fK/MrWVw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"debug\": \"^4.1.1\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"source-map\": \"^0.6.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"istanbul-reports\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-reports/-/istanbul-reports-3.1.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BewmUXImeuRk2YY0PVbxgKAysvhRPUQE0h5QRM++nVWyubKGV0l8qQ5op8+B2DOmwSe63Jivj0BjkPQVf8fP5g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"html-escaper\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-report\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest/-/jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NIy3oAFp9shda19hy4HK0HRTWKtPJmGdnvywu01nOqNC2vZg+Z+fvJDxpMQA88eb2I9EcafcdjYgsDthnYTvGw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/core\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"import-local\": \"^3.0.2\",\n        \"jest-cli\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-changed-files\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-changed-files/-/jest-changed-files-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fEArFiwf1BpQ+4bXSprcDc3/x4HSzL4al2tozwVpDFpsxALjLYdyiIK4e5Vz66GQJIbXJ82+35PtysofptNX2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"execa\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-circus\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-circus/-/jest-circus-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3E1nCMgipcTkCocFwM90XXQab9bS+GMsjdpmPrlelaxwD93Ad8iVEjX/vvHPdLPnFf+L40u+5+iutRdA1N9myw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"co\": \"^4.6.0\",\n        \"dedent\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"is-generator-fn\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"jest-each\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"pure-rand\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"stack-utils\": \"^2.0.3\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-cli\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-cli/-/jest-cli-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OVVobw2IubN/GSYsxETi+gOe7Ka59EFMR/twOU3Jb2GnKKeMGJB5SGUUrEz3SFVmJASUdZUzy83sLNNQ2gZslg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/core\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"create-jest\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"import-local\": \"^3.0.2\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"yargs\": \"^17.3.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-config\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-config/-/jest-config-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-uXbpfeQ7R6TZBqI3/TxCU4q4ttk3u0PJeC+E0zbfSoSjq6bJ7buBPxzQPL0ifrkY4DNu4JUdk0ImlBUYi840eQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@jest/test-sequencer\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-jest\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"deepmerge\": \"^4.2.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-circus\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-environment-node\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runner\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"parse-json\": \"^5.2.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-json-comments\": \"^3.1.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-diff\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-diff/-/jest-diff-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LMIgiIrhigmPrs03JHpxUh2yISK3vLFPkAodPeo0+BuF7wA2FoQbkEg1u8gBYBThncu7e1oEDUfIXVuTqLRUjw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"diff-sequences\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-docblock\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-docblock/-/jest-docblock-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-q617Auw3A612guyaFgsbFeYpNP5t2aoUNLwBUbc/0kD1R4t9ixDbyFTHd1nok4epoVFpr7PmeWHrhvuV3XaJ4g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"jest-each\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-each/-/jest-each-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gns+Er14+ZrEoC5fhOfYCY1LOHHr0TI+rQUHZS8Ttw2l7gl+80eHc/gFf2Ktkw0+SIACDTeWvpFcv3B04VembQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-environment-node\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-environment-node/-/jest-environment-node-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DOSwCRqXirTOyheM+4d5YZOrWcdu0LNZ87ewUoywbcb2XR4wKgqiG8vNeYwhjFMbEkfju7wx2GYH0P2gevGvFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-get-type\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-get-type/-/jest-get-type-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zrteXnqYxfQh7l5FHyL38jL39di8H8rHoecLH3JNxH3BwOrBsNeabdap5e0I23lD4HHI8W5VFBZqG4Eaq5LNcw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"jest-haste-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-haste-map/-/jest-haste-map-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fP8u2pyfqx0K1rGn1R9pyE0/KTn+G7PxktWidOBTqFPLYX0b9ksaMFkhK5vrS3DVun09pckLdlx90QthlW7AmA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/graceful-fs\": \"^4.1.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"anymatch\": \"^3.0.3\",\n        \"fb-watchman\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"fsevents\": \"^2.3.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"walker\": \"^1.0.8\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-leak-detector\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-leak-detector/-/jest-leak-detector-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kYA8IJcSYtST2BY9I+SMC32nDpBT3J2NvWJx8+JCuCdl/CR1I4EKUJROiP8XtCcxqgTTBGJNdbB1A8XRKbTetw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-matcher-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-matcher-utils/-/jest-matcher-utils-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-sBkD+Xi9DtcChsI3L3u0+N0opgPYnCRPtGcQYrgXmR+hmt/fYfWAL0xRXYU8eWOdfuLgBe0YCW3AFtnRLagq/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-diff\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-message-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-message-util/-/jest-message-util-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GBEV4GRADeP+qtB2+6u61stea8mGcOT4mCtrYISZwfu9/ISHFJ/5zOMXYbpBE9RsS5+Gb63DW4FgmnKJ79Kf6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.12.13\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/stack-utils\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"stack-utils\": \"^2.0.3\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-mock\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-mock/-/jest-mock-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ITOMZn+UkYS4ZFh83xYAOzWStloNzJFO2s8DWrE4lhtGD+AorgnbkiKERe4wQVBydIGPx059g6riW5Btp6Llnw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-pnp-resolver\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-pnp-resolver/-/jest-pnp-resolver-1.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+3NpwQEnRoIBtx4fyhblQDPgJI0H1IEIkX7ShLUjPGA7TtUTvI1oiKi3SR4oBR0hQhQR80l4WAe5RrXBwWMA8w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {}\n    },\n    \"jest-regex-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-regex-util/-/jest-regex-util-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KJJBsRCyyLNWCNBOvZyRDnAIfUiRJ8v+hOBQYGn8gDyF3UegwiP4gwRR3/SDa42g1YbVycTidUF3rKjyLFDWbg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"jest-resolve\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-resolve/-/jest-resolve-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-IOVhZSrg+UvVAshDSDtHyFCCBUl/Q3AAJv8iZ6ZjnZ74xzvwuzLXid9IIIPgTnY62SJjfuupMKZsZQRsCvxEgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-pnp-resolver\": \"^1.2.2\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"resolve\": \"^1.20.0\",\n        \"resolve.exports\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-resolve-dependencies\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-resolve-dependencies/-/jest-resolve-dependencies-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-un0zD/6qxJ+S0et7WxeI3H5XSe9lTBBR7bOHCHXkKR6luG5mwDDlIzVQ0V5cZCuoTgEdcdwzTghYkTWfubi+nA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-runner\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-runner/-/jest-runner-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fsc4N6cPCAahybGBfTRcq5wFR6fpLznMg47sY5aDpsoejOcVYFb07AHuSnR0liMcPTgBsA3ZJL6kFOjPdoNipQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"emittery\": \"^0.13.1\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-docblock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-environment-node\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-leak-detector\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-watcher\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"source-map-support\": \"0.5.13\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-runtime\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-runtime/-/jest-runtime-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gUnLjgwdGqW7B4LvOIkbKs9WGbn+QLqRQQ9juC6HndeDiezIwhDP+mhMwHWCEcfQ5RUXa6OPnFF8BJh5xegwwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/globals\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/source-map\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"cjs-module-lexer\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-bom\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-snapshot\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-snapshot/-/jest-snapshot-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Rm0BMWtxBcioHr1/OX5YCP8Uov4riHvKPknOGs804Zg9JGZgmIBkbtlxJC/7Z4msKYVbIJtfU+tKb8xlYNfdkw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@jest/expect-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-diff\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"natural-compare\": \"^1.4.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^7.5.3\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"semver\": {\n          \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-util/-/jest-util-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-z6EbKajIpqGKU56y5KBUgy1dt1ihhQJgWzUlZHArA/+X2ad7Cb5iF+AK1EWVL/Bo7Rz9uurpqw6SiBCefUbCGA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"picomatch\": \"^2.2.3\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-validate\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-validate/-/jest-validate-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ZB7wHqaRGVw/9hST/OuFUReG7M8vKeq0/J2egIGLdvjHCmYqGARhzXmtgi+gVeZ5uXFF219aOc3Ls2yLg27tkw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"camelcase\": \"^6.2.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"leven\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"camelcase\": {\n          \"version\": \"6.3.0\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/camelcase/-/camelcase-6.3.0.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-Gmy6FhYlCY7uOElZUSbxo2UCDH8owEk996gkbrpsgGtrJLM3J7jGxl9Ic7Qwwj4ivOE5AWZWRMecDdF7hqGjFA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-watcher\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-watcher/-/jest-watcher-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-49Fg7WXkU3Vl2h6LbLtMQ/HyB6rXSIX7SqvBLQmssRBGN9I0PNvPmAmCWSOY6SOvrjhI/F7/bGAv9RtnsPA03g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"ansi-escapes\": \"^4.2.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"emittery\": \"^0.13.1\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"string-length\": \"^4.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-worker\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-worker/-/jest-worker-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eIz2msL/EzL9UFTFFx7jBTkeZfku0yUAyZZZmJ93H2TYEiroIx2PQjEXcwYtYl8zXCxb+PAmA2hLIt/6ZEkPHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"merge-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^8.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"supports-color\": {\n          \"version\": \"8.1.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-color/-/supports-color-8.1.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-MpUEN2OodtUzxvKQl72cUF7RQ5EiHsGvSsVG0ia9c5RbWGL2CI4C7EpPS8UTBIplnlzZiNuV56w+FuNxy3ty2Q==\",\n          \"dev\": true,\n          \"requires\": \n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"js-tokens\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/js-tokens/-/js-tokens-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RdJUflcE3cUzKiMqQgsCu06FPu9UdIJO0beYbPhHN4k6apgJtifcoCtT9bcxOpYBtpD2kCM6Sbzg4CausW/PKQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"js-yaml\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.14.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/js-yaml/-/js-yaml-3.14.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-okMH7OXXJ7YrN9Ok3/SXrnu4iX9yOk+25nqX4imS2npuvTYDmo/QEZoqwZkYaIDk3jVvBOTOIEgEhaLOynBS9g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"jsesc\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jsesc/-/jsesc-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/sM3dO2FOzXjKQhJuo0Q173wf2KOo8t4I8vHy6lF9poUp7bKT0/NHE8fPX23PwfhnykfqnC2xRxOnVw5XuGIaA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"json-parse-even-better-errors\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/json-parse-even-better-errors/-/json-parse-even-better-errors-2.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xyFwyhro/JEof6Ghe2iz2NcXoj2sloNsWr/XsERDK/oiPCfaNhl5ONfp+jQdAZRQQ0IJWNzH9zIZF7li91kh2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"json5\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/json5/-/json5-2.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XmOWe7eyHYH14cLdVPoyg+GOH3rYX++KpzrylJwSW98t3Nk+U8XOl8FWKOgwtzdb8lXGf6zYwDUzeHMWfxasyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"kleur\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/kleur/-/kleur-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eTIzlVOSUR+JxdDFepEYcBMtZ9Qqdef+rnzWdRZuMbOywu5tO2w2N7rqjoANZ5k9vywhL6Br1VRjUIgTQx4E8w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"leven\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/leven/-/leven-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qsda+H8jTaUaN/x5vzW2rzc+8Rw4TAQ/4KjB46IwK5VH+IlVeeeje/EoZRpiXvIqjFgK84QffqPztGI3VBLG1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"lines-and-columns\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/lines-and-columns/-/lines-and-columns-1.2.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7ylylesZQ/PV29jhEDl3Ufjo6ZX7gCqJr5F7PKrqc93v7fzSymt1BpwEU8nAUXs8qzzvqhbjhK5QZg6Mt/HkBg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"locate-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/locate-path/-/locate-path-5.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-t7hw9pI+WvuwNJXwk5zVHpyhIqzg2qTlklJOf0mVxGSbe3Fp2VieZcduNYjaLDoy6p9uGpQEGWG87WpMKlNq8g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"lru-cache\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/lru-cache/-/lru-cache-5.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KpNARQA3Iwv+jTA0utUVVbrh+Jlrr1Fv0e56GGzAFOXN7dk/FviaDW8LHmK52DlcH4WP2n6gI8vN1aesBFgo9w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"make-dir\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/make-dir/-/make-dir-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hXdUTZYIVOt1Ex//jAQi+wTZZpUpwBj/0QsOzqegb3rGMMeJiSEu5xLHnYfBrRV4RH2+OCSOO95Is/7x1WJ4bw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": ,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"semver\": {\n          \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"makeerror\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.12\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/makeerror/-/makeerror-1.0.12.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JmqCvUhmt43madlpFzG4BQzG2Z3m6tvQDNKdClZnO3VbIudJYmxsT0FNJMeiB2+JTSlTQTSbU8QdesVmwJcmLg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"merge-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/merge-stream/-/merge-stream-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-abv/qOcuPfk3URPfDzmZU1LKmuw8kT+0nIHvKrKgFrwifol/doWcdA4ZqsWQ8ENrFKkd67Mfpo/LovbIUsbt3w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"micromatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/micromatch/-/micromatch-4.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-PXwfBhYu0hBCPw8Dn0E+WDYb7af3dSLVWKi3HGv84IdF4TyFoC0ysxFd0Goxw7nSv4T/PzEJQxsYsEiFCKo2BA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"mimic-fn\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/mimic-fn/-/mimic-fn-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OqbOk5oEQeAZ8WXWydlu9HJjz9WVdEIvamMCcXmuqUYjTknH/sqsWvhQ3vgwKFRR1HpjvNBKQ37nbJgYzGqGcg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"minimatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/minimatch/-/minimatch-3.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-J7p63hRiAjw1NDEww1W7i37+ByIrOWO5XQQAzZ3VOcL0PNybwpfmV/N05zFAzwQ9USyEcX6t3UO+K5aqBQOIHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"ms\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ms/-/ms-2.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6FlzubTLZG3J2a/NVCAleEhjzq5oxgHyaCU9yYXvcLsvoVaHJq/s5xXI6/XXP6tz7R9xAOtHnSO/tXtF3WRTlA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"natural-compare\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/natural-compare/-/natural-compare-1.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OWND8ei3VtNC9h7V60qff3SVobHr996CTwgxubgyQYEpg290h9J0buyECNNJexkFm5sOajh5G116RYA1c8ZMSw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node-int64\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/node-int64/-/node-int64-0.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-O5lz91xSOeoXP6DulyHfllpq+Eg00MWitZIbtPfoSEvqIHdl5gfcY6hYzDWnj0qD5tz52PI08u9qUvSVeUBeHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node-releases\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.19\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/node-releases/-/node-releases-2.0.19.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xxOWJsBKtzAq7DY0J+DTzuz58K8e7sJbdgwkbMWQe8UYB6ekmsQ45q0M/tJDsGaZmbC+l7n57UV8Hl5tHxO9uw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"normalize-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/normalize-path/-/normalize-path-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6eZs5Ls3WtCisHWp9S2GUy8dqkpGi4BVSz3GaqiE6ezub0512ESztXUwUB6C6IKbQkY2Pnb/mD4WYojCRwcwLA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"npm-run-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/npm-run-path/-/npm-run-path-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-S48WzZW777zhNIrn7gxOlISNAqi9ZC/uQFnRdbeIHhZhCA6UqpkOT8T1G7BvfdgP4Er8gF4sUbaS0i7QvIfCWw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"once\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/once/-/once-1.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lNaJgI+2Q5URQBkccEKHTQOPaXdUxnZZElQTZY0MFUAuaEqe1E+Nyvgdz/aIyNi6Z9MzO5dv1H8n58/GELp3+w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"onetime\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/onetime/-/onetime-5.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kbpaSSGJTWdAY5KPVeMOKXSrPtr8C8C7wodJbcsd51jRnmD+GZu8Y0VoU6Dm5Z4vWr0Ig/1NKuWRKf7j5aaYSg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"p-limit\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-limit/-/p-limit-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TYOanM3wGwNGsZN2cVTYPArw454xnXj5qmWF1bEoAc4+cU/ol7GVh7odevjp1FNHduHc3KZMcFduxU5Xc6uJRQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"p-locate\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-locate/-/p-locate-4.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R79ZZ/0wAxKGu3oYMlz8jy/kbhsNrS7SKZ7PxEHBgJ5+F2mtFW2fK2cOtBh1cHYkQsbzFV7I+EoRKe6Yt0oK7A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": ,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"p-limit\": {\n          \"version\": \"2.3.0\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-limit/-/p-limit-2.3.0.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-//88mFWSJx8lxCzwdAABTJL2MyWB12+eIY7MDL2SqLmAkeKU9qxRvWuSyTjm3FUmpBEMuFfckAIqEaVGUDxb6w==\",\n          \"dev\": true,\n          \"requires\": \n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"p-try\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-try/-/p-try-2.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R4nPAVTAU0B9D35/Gk3uJf/7XYbQcyohSKdvAxIRSNghFl4e71hVoGnBNQz9cWaXxO2I10KTC+3jMdvvoKw6dQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"parse-json\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/parse-json/-/parse-json-5.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ayCKvm/phCGxOkYRSCM82iDwct8/EonSEgCSxWxD7ve6jHggsFl4fZVQBPRNgQoKiuV/odhFrGzQXZwbifC8Rg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.0.0\",\n        \"error-ex\": \"^1.3.1\",\n        \"json-parse-even-better-errors\": \"^2.3.0\",\n        \"lines-and-columns\": \"^1.1.6\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"path-exists\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-exists/-/path-exists-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ak9Qy5Q7jYb2Wwcey5Fpvg2KoAc/ZIhLSLOSBmRmygPsGwkVVt0fZa0qrtMz+m6tJTAHfZQ8FnmB4MG4LWy7/w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"path-is-absolute\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-is-absolute/-/path-is-absolute-1.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-AVbw3UJ2e9bq64vSaS9Am0fje1Pa8pbGqTTsmXfaIiMpnr5DlDhfJOuLj9Sf95ZPVDAUerDfEk88MPmPe7UCQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"path-key\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-key/-/path-key-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ojmeN0qd+y0jszEtoY48r0Peq5dwMEkIlCOu6Q5f41lfkswXuKtYrhgoTpLnyIcHm24Uhqx+5Tqm2InSwLhE6Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"path-parse\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-parse/-/path-parse-1.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LDJzPVEEEPR+y48z93A0Ed0yXb8pAByGWo/k5YYdYgpY2/2EsOsksJrq7lOHxryrVOn1ejG6oAp8ahvOIQD8sw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"picocolors\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/picocolors/-/picocolors-1.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xceH2snhtb5M9liqDsmEw56le376mTZkEX/jEb/RxNFyegNul7eNslCXP9FDj/Lcu0X8KEyMceP2ntpaHrDEVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"picomatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/picomatch/-/picomatch-2.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JU3teHTNjmE2VCGFzuY8EXzCDVwEqB2a8fsIvwaStHhAWJEeVd1o1QD80CU6+ZdEXXSLbSsuLwJjkCBWqRQUVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"pirates\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pirates/-/pirates-4.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TfySrs/5nm8fQJDcBDuUng3VOUKsd7S+zqvbOTiGXHfxX4wK31ard+hoNuvkicM/2YFzlpDgABOevKSsB4G/FA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"pkg-dir\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pkg-dir/-/pkg-dir-4.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-HRDzbaKjC+AOWVXxAU/x54COGeIv9eb+6CkDSQoNTt4XyWoIJvuPsXizxu/Fr23EiekbtZwmh1IcIG/l/a10GQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"pretty-format\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pretty-format/-/pretty-format-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Pdlw/oPxN+aXdmM9R00JVC9WVFoCLTKJvDVLgmJ+qAffBMxsV85l/Lu7sNx4zSzPyoL2euImuEwHhOXdEgNFZQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/schemas\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"react-is\": \"^18.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": {\n          \"version\": \"5.2.0\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-styles/-/ansi-styles-5.2.0.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-Cxwpt2SfTzTtXcfOlzGEee8O+c+MmUgGrNiBcXnuWxuFJHe6a5Hz7qwhwe5OgaSYI0IJvkLqWX1ASG+cJOkEiA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"prompts\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.4.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/prompts/-/prompts-2.4.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NxNv/kLguCA7p3jE8oL2aEBsrJWgAakBpgmgK6lpPWV+WuOmY6r2/zbAVnP+T8bQlA0nzHXSJSJW0Hq7ylaD2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"pure-rand\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pure-rand/-/pure-rand-6.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bVWawvoZoBYpp6yIoQtQXHZjmz35RSVHnUOTefl8Vcjr8snTPY1wnpSPMWekcFwbxI6gtmT7rSYPFvz71ldiOA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"react-is\": {\n      \"version\": \"18.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/react-is/-/react-is-18.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/LLMVyas0ljjAtoYiPqYiL8VWXzUUdThrmU5+n20DZv+a+ClRoevUzw5JxU+Ieh5/c87ytoTBV9G1FiKfNJdmg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"require-directory\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/require-directory/-/require-directory-2.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fGxEI7+wsG9xrvdjsrlmL22OMTTiHRwAMroiEeMgq8gzoLC/PQr7RsRDSTLUg/bZAZtF+TVIkHc6/4RIKrui+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"resolve\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.22.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve/-/resolve-1.22.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NPRy+/ncIMeDlTAsuqwKIiferiawhefFJtkNSW0qZJEqMEb+qBt/77B/jGeeek+F0uOeN05CDa6HXbbIgtVX4w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"is-core-module\": \"^2.16.0\",\n        \"path-parse\": \"^1.0.7\",\n        \"supports-preserve-symlinks-flag\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"resolve-cwd\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve-cwd/-/resolve-cwd-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OrZaX2Mb+rJCpH/6CpSqt9xFVpN++x01XnN2ie9g6P5/3xelLAkXWVADpdz1IHD/KFfEXyE6V0U01OQ3UO2rEg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"resolve-from\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve-from/-/resolve-from-5.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qYg9KP24dD5qka9J47d0aVky0N+b4fTU89LN9iDnjB5waksiC49rvMB0PrUJQGoTmH50XPiqOvAjDfaijGxYZw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"resolve.exports\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve.exports/-/resolve.exports-2.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OcXjMsGdhL4XnbShKpAcSqPMzQoYkYyhbEaeSko47MjRP9NfEQMhZkXL1DoFlt9LWQn4YttrdnV6X2OiyzBi+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-6.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BR7VvDCVHO+q2xBEWskxS6DJE1qRnb7DxzUrogb71CWoSficBxYsiAGd+Kl0mmq/MprG9yArRkyrQxTO6XjMzA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"shebang-command\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/shebang-command/-/shebang-command-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kHxr2zZpYtdmrN1qDjrrX/Z1rR1kG8Dx+gkpK1G4eXmvXswmcE1hTWBWYUzlraYw1/yZp6YuDY77YtvbN0dmDA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"shebang-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/shebang-regex/-/shebang-regex-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7++dFhtcx3353uBaq8DDR4NuxBetBzC7ZQOhmTQInHEd6bSrXdiEyzCvG07Z44UYdLShWUyXt5M/yhz8ekcb1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"signal-exit\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/signal-exit/-/signal-exit-3.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wnD2ZE+l+SPC/uoS0vXeE9L1+0wuaMqKlfz9AMUo38JsyLSBWSFcHR1Rri62LZc12vLr1gb3jl7iwQhgwpAbGQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"sisteransi\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/sisteransi/-/sisteransi-1.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bLGGlR1QxBcynn2d5YmDX4MGjlZvy2MRBDRNHLJ8VI6l6+9FUiyTFNJ0IveOSP0bcXgVDPRcfGqA0pjaqUpfVg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"slash\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/slash/-/slash-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-g9Q1haeby36OSStwb4ntCGGGaKsaVSjQ68fBxoQcutl5fS1vuY18H3wSt3jFyFtrkx+Kz0V1G85A4MyAdDMi2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.6.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/source-map/-/source-map-0.6.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UjgapumWlbMhkBgzT7Ykc5YXUT46F0iKu8SGXq0bcwP5dz/h0Plj6enJqjz1Zbq2l5WaqYnrVbwWOWMyF3F47g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"source-map-support\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.5.13\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/source-map-support/-/source-map-support-0.5.13.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-SHSKFHadjVA5oR4PPqhtAVdcBWwRYVd6g6cAXnIbRiIwc2EhPrTuKUBdSLvlEKyIP3GCf89fltvcZiP9MMFA1w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"buffer-from\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"source-map\": \"^0.6.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"sprintf-js\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/sprintf-js/-/sprintf-js-1.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-D9cPgkvLlV3t3IzL0D0YLvGA9Ahk4PcvVwUbN0dSGr1aP0Nrt4AEnTUbuGvquEC0mA64Gqt1fzirlRs5ibXx8g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"stack-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/stack-utils/-/stack-utils-2.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XlkWvfIm6RmsWtNJx+uqtKLS8eqFbxUg0ZzLXqY0caEy9l7hruX8IpiDnjsLavoBgqCCR71TqWO8MaXYheJ3RQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"string-length\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/string-length/-/string-length-4.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+l6rNN5fYHNhZZy41RXsYptCjA2Igmq4EG7kZAYFQI1E1VTXarr6ZPXBg6eq7Y6eK4FEhY6AJlyuFIb/v/S0VQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"char-regex\": \"^1.0.2\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"string-width\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/string-width/-/string-width-4.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wKyQRQpjJ0sIp62ErSZdGsjMJWsap5oRNihHhu6G7JVO/9jIB6UyevL+tXuOqrng8j/cxKTWyWUwvSTriiZz/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"emoji-regex\": \"^8.0.0\",\n        \"is-fullwidth-code-point\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"strip-ansi\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-ansi/-/strip-ansi-6.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Y38VPSHcqkFrCpFnQ9vuSXmquuv5oXOKpGeT6aGrr3o3Gc9AlVa6JBfUSOCnbxGGZF+/0ooI7KrPuUSztUdU5A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"strip-bom\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-bom/-/strip-bom-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3xurFv5tEgii33Zi8Jtp55wEIILR9eh34FAW00PZf+JnSsTmV/ioewSgQl97JHvgjoRGwPShsWm+IdrxB35d0w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"strip-final-newline\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-final-newline/-/strip-final-newline-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BrpvfNAE3dcvq7ll3xVumzjKjZQ5tI1sEUIKr3Uoks0XUl45St3FlatVqef9prk4jRDzhW6WZg+3bk93y6pLjA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"strip-json-comments\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-json-comments/-/strip-json-comments-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6fPc+R4ihwqP6N/aIv2f1gMH8lOVtWQHoqC4yK6oSDVVocumAsfCqjkXnqiYMhmMwS/mEHLp7Vehlt3ql6lEig==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"supports-color\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-color/-/supports-color-7.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qpCAvRl9stuOHveKsn7HncJRvv501qIacKzQlO/+Lwxc9+0q2wLyv4Dfvt80/DPn2pqOBsJdDiogXGR9+OvwRw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"supports-preserve-symlinks-flag\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag/-/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag-1.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ot0WnXS9fgdkgIcePe6RHNk1WA8+muPa6cSjeR3V8K27q9BB1rTE3R1p7Hv0z1ZyAc8s6Vvv8DIyWf681MAt0w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"test-exclude\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/test-exclude/-/test-exclude-6.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-cAGWPIyOHU6zlmg88jwm7VRyXnMN7iV68OGAbYDk/Mh/xC/pzVPlQtY6ngoIH/5/tciuhGfvESU8GrHrcxD56w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.4\",\n        \"minimatch\": \"^3.0.4\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"tmpl\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/tmpl/-/tmpl-1.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3f0uOEAQwIqGuWW2MVzYg8fV/QNnc/IpuJNG837rLuczAaLVHslWHZQj4IGiEl5Hs3kkbhwL9Ab7Hrsmuj+Smw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"to-regex-range\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/to-regex-range/-/to-regex-range-5.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-65P7iz6X5yEr1cwcgvQxbbIw7Uk3gOy5dIdtZ4rDveLqhrdJP+Li/Hx6tyK0NEb+2GCyneCMJiGqrADCSNk8sQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"type-detect\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/type-detect/-/type-detect-4.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0fr/mIH1dlO+x7TlcMy+bIDqKPsw/70tVyeHW787goQjhmqaZe10uwLujubK9q9Lg6Fiho1KUKDYz0Z7k7g5/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"type-fest\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.21.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/type-fest/-/type-fest-0.21.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-t0rzBq87m3fVcduHDUFhKmyyX+9eo6WQjZvf51Ea/M0Q7+T374Jp1aUiyUl0GKxp8M/OETVHSDvmkyPgvX+X2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"undici-types\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.21.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/undici-types/-/undici-types-6.21.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iwDZqg0QAGrg9Rav5H4n0M64c3mkR59cJ6wQp+7C4nI0gsmExaedaYLNO44eT4AtBBwjbTiGPMlt2Md0T9H9JQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"update-browserslist-db\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/update-browserslist-db/-/update-browserslist-db-1.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UxhIZQ+QInVdunkDAaiazvvT/+fXL5Osr0JZlJulepYu6Jd7qJtDZjlur0emRlT71EN3ScPoE7gvsuIKKNavKw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"v8-to-istanbul\": {\n      \"version\": \"9.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/v8-to-istanbul/-/v8-to-istanbul-9.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kiGUalWN+rgBJ/1OHZsBtU4rXZOfj/7rKQxULKlIzwzQSvMJUUNgPwJEEh7gU6xEVxC0ahoOBvN2YI8GH6FNgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.12\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.1\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"walker\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/walker/-/walker-1.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ts/8E8l5b7kY0vlWLewOkDXMmPdLcVV4GmOQLyxuSswIJsweeFZtAsMF7k1Nszz+TYBQrlYRmzOnr398y1JemQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"which\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/which/-/which-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BLI3Tl1TW3Pvl70l3yq3Y64i+awpwXqsGBYWkkqMtnbXgrMD+yj7rhW0kuEDxzJaYXGjEW5ogapKNMEKNMjibA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"wrap-ansi\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/wrap-ansi/-/wrap-ansi-7.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-YVGIj2kamLSTxw6NsZjoBxfSwsn0ycdesmc4p+Q21c5zPuZ1pl+NfxVdxPtdHvmNVOQ6XSYG4AUtyt/Fi7D16Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"wrappy\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/wrappy/-/wrappy-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-l4Sp/DRseor9wL6EvV2+TuQn63dMkPjZ/sp9XkghTEbV9KlPS1xUsZ3u7/IQO4wxtcFB4bgpQPRcR3QCvezPcQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"write-file-atomic\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/write-file-atomic/-/write-file-atomic-4.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7KxauUdBmSdWnmpaGFg+ppNjKF8uNLry8LyzjauQDOVONfFLNKrKvQOxZ/VuTIcS/gge/YNahf5RIIQWTSarlg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"imurmurhash\": \"^0.1.4\",\n        \"signal-exit\": \"^3.0.7\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"y18n\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/y18n/-/y18n-5.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0pfFzegeDWJHJIAmTLRP2DwHjdF5s7jo9tuztdQxAhINCdvS+3nGINqPd00AphqJR/0LhANUS6/+7SCb98YOfA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"yallist\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yallist/-/yallist-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-a4UGQaWPH59mOXUYnAG2ewncQS4i4F43Tv3JoAM+s2VDAmS9NsK8GpDMLrCHPksFT7h3K6TOoUNn2pb7RoXx4g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"yargs\": {\n      \"version\": \"17.7.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yargs/-/yargs-17.7.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7dSzzRQ++CKnNI/krKnYRV7JKKPUXMEh61soaHKg9mrWEhzFWhFnxPxGl+69cD1Ou63C13NUPCnmIcrvqCuM6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"cliui\": \"^8.0.1\",\n        \"escalade\": \"^3.1.1\",\n        \"get-caller-file\": \"^2.0.5\",\n        \"require-directory\": \"^2.1.1\",\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.2.3\",\n        \"y18n\": \"^5.0.5\",\n        \"yargs-parser\": \"^21.1.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"yargs-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"21.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yargs-parser/-/yargs-parser-21.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tVpsJW7DdjecAiFpbIB1e3qxIQsE6NoPc5/eTdrbbIC4h0LVsWhnoa3g+m2HclBIujHzsxZ4VJVA+GUuc2/LBw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"yocto-queue\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yocto-queue/-/yocto-queue-0.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-rVksvsnNCdJ/ohGc6xgPwyN8eheCxsiLM8mxuE/t/mOVqJewPuO1miLpTHQiRgTKCLexL4MeAFVagts7HmNZ2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    }\n  }\n}\n","file":"package-lock.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random ;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random *;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * ;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * 6;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * 6-;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * 6- ;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * 6;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * 6 ;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * 6 -;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * 6 - ;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * 6 ;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * 6;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * ;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * ();\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6-);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6-1);\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6-1)+;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6-1)+1;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6-1) +1;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6-1) + 1;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6- 1) + 1;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6 - 1) + 1;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"lockfileVersion\": 2,\n  \"requires\": true,\n  \"packages\": {\n    \"\": {\n      \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"license\": \"ISC\",\n      \"devDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@ampproject/remapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@ampproject/remapping/-/remapping-2.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-30iZtAPgz+LTIYoeivqYo853f02jBYSd5uGnGpkFV0M3xOt9aN73erkgYAmZU43x4VfqcnLxW9Kpg3R5LC4YYw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": \"^0.3.5\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.24\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/code-frame\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/code-frame/-/code-frame-7.26.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RJlIHRueQgwWitWgF8OdFYGZX328Ax5BCemNGlqHfplnRT9ESi8JkFlvaVYbS+UubVY6dpv87Fs2u5M29iNFVQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"js-tokens\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"picocolors\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/compat-data\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/compat-data/-/compat-data-7.26.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-oH5UPLMWR3L2wEFLnFJ1TZXqHufiTKAiLfqw5zkhS4dKXLJ10yVztfil/twG8EDTA4F/tvVNw9nOl4ZMslB8rQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/core\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/core/-/core-7.26.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-vMqyb7XCDMPvJFFOaT9kxtiRh42GwlZEg1/uIgtZshS5a/8OaduUfCi7kynKgc3Tw/6Uo2D+db9qBttghhmxwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@ampproject/remapping\": \"^2.2.0\",\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/helper-compilation-targets\": \"^7.26.5\",\n        \"@babel/helper-module-transforms\": \"^7.26.0\",\n        \"@babel/helpers\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.26.9\",\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"debug\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"gensync\": \"^1.0.0-beta.2\",\n        \"json5\": \"^2.2.3\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": {\n        \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n        \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/babel\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/generator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/generator/-/generator-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-VybsKvpiN1gU1sdMZIp7FcqphVVKEwcuj02x73uvcHE0PTihx1nlBcowYWhDwjpoAXRv43+gDzyggGnn1XZhVw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": \"^0.3.5\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.25\",\n        \"jsesc\": \"^3.0.2\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-compilation-targets\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-compilation-targets/-/helper-compilation-targets-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LVk7fbXml0H2xH34dFzKQ7TDZ2G4/rVTOrq9V+icbbadjbVxxeFeDsNHv2SrZeWoA+6ZiTyWYWtScEIW07EAcA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/compat-data\": \"^7.26.8\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-option\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"browserslist\": \"^4.24.0\",\n        \"lru-cache\": \"^5.1.1\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-module-imports\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-module-imports/-/helper-module-imports-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tnUA4RsrmflIM6W6RFTLFSXITtl0wKjgpnLgXyowocVPrbYrLUXSBXDgTs8BlbmIzIdlBySRQjINYs2BAkiLtw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-module-transforms\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-module-transforms/-/helper-module-transforms-7.26.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xO+xu6B5K2czEnQye6BHA7DolFFmS3LB7stHZFaOLb1pAwO1HWLS8fXA+eh0A2yIvltPVmx3eNNDBJA2SLHXFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-module-imports\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-plugin-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-plugin-utils/-/helper-plugin-utils-7.26.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RS+jZcRdZdRFzMyr+wcsaqOmld1/EqTghfaBGQQd/WnRdzdlvSZ//kF7U8VQTxf1ynZ4cjUcYgjVGx13ewNPMg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-string-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-string-parser/-/helper-string-parser-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-4A/SCr/2KLd5jrtOMFzaKjVtAei3+2r/NChoBNoZ3EyP/+GlhoaEGoWOZUmFmoITP7zOJyHIMm+DYRd8o3PvHA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-validator-identifier/-/helper-validator-identifier-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Ed61U6XJc3CVRfkERJWDz4dJwKe7iLmmJsbOGu9wSloNSFttHV0I8g6UAgb7qnK5ly5bGLPd4oXZlxCdANBOWQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helper-validator-option\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-validator-option/-/helper-validator-option-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-e/zv1co8pp55dNdEcCynfj9X7nyUKUXoUEwfXqaZt0omVOmDe9oOTdKStH4GmAw6zxMFs50ZayuMfHDKlO7Tfw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/helpers\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helpers/-/helpers-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-U5eyP/CTFPuNE3qk+WZMxFkp/4zUzdceQlfzf7DdGdhp+Fezd7HD+i8Y24ZuTMKX3wQBld449jijbGq6OdGNQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/parser/-/parser-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iaepho73/2Pz7w2eMS0Q5f83+0RKI7i4xmiYeBmDzfRVbQtTOG7Ts0S4HzJVsTMGI9keU8rNfuZr8DKfSt7Yyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators/-/plugin-syntax-async-generators-7.8.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tycmZxkGfZaxhMRbXlPXuVFpdWlXpir2W4AMhSJgRKzk/eDlIXOhb2LHWoLpDF7TEHylV5zNhykX6KAgHJmTNw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint/-/plugin-syntax-bigint-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wnTnFlG+YxQm3vDxpGE57Pj0srRU4sHE/mDkt1qv2YJJSeUAec2ma4WLUnUPeKjyrfntVwe/N6dCXpU+zL3Npg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.12.13\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties/-/plugin-syntax-class-properties-7.12.13.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fm4idjKla0YahUNgFNLCB0qySdsoPiZP3iQE3rky0mBUtMZ23yDJ9SJdg6dXTSDnulOVqiF3Hgr9nbXvXTQZYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block/-/plugin-syntax-class-static-block-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-b+YyPmr6ldyNnM6sqYeMWE+bgJcJpO6yS4QD7ymxgH34GBPNDM/THBh8iunyvKIZztiwLH4CJZ0RxTk9emgpjw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes/-/plugin-syntax-import-attributes-7.26.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-e2dttdsJ1ZTpi3B9UYGLw41hifAubg19AtCu/2I/F1QNVclOBr1dYpTdmdyZ84Xiz43BS/tCUkMAZNLv12Pi+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta/-/plugin-syntax-import-meta-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Yqfm+XDx0+Prh3VSeEQCPU81yC+JWZ2pDPFSS4ZdpfZhp4MkFMaDC1UqseovEKwSUpnIL7+vK+Clp7bfh0iD7g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings/-/plugin-syntax-json-strings-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lY6kdGpWHvjoe2vk4WrAapEuBR69EMxZl+RoGRhrFGNYVK8mOPAW8VfbT/ZgrFbXlDNiiaxQnAtgVCZ6jv30EA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx/-/plugin-syntax-jsx-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ld6oezHQMZsZfp6pWtbjaNDF2tiiCYYDqQszHt5VV437lewP9aSi2Of99CK0D0XB21k7FLgnLcmQKyKzynfeAA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators/-/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-d8waShlpFDinQ5MtvGU9xDAOzKH47+FFoney2baFIoMr952hKOLp1HR7VszoZvOsV/4+RRszNY7D17ba0te0ig==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator/-/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-aSff4zPII1u2QD7y+F8oDsz19ew4IGEJg9SVW+bqwpwtfFleiQDMdzA/R+UlWDzfnHFCxxleFT0PMIrR36XLNQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator/-/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9H6YdfkcK/uOnY/K7/aA2xpzaAgkQn37yzWUMRK7OaPOqOpGS1+n0H5hxT9AUw9EsSjPW8SVyMJwYRtWs3X3ug==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread/-/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XoqMijGZb9y3y2XskN+P1wUGiVwWZ5JmoDRwx5+3GmEplNyVM2s2Dg8ILFQm8rWM48orGy5YpI5Bl8U1y7ydlA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding/-/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6VPD0Pc1lpTqw0aKoeRTMiB+kWhAoT24PA+ksWSBrFtl5SIRVpZlwN3NNPQjehA2E/91FV3RjLWoVTglWcSV3Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining/-/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KoK9ErH1MBlCPxV0VANkXW2/dw4vlbGDrFgz8bmUsBGYkFRcbRwMh6cIJubdPrkxRwuGdtCk0v/wPTKbQgBjkg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object/-/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0wVnp9dxJ72ZUJDV27ZfbSj6iHLoytYZmh3rFcxNnvsJF3ktkzLDZPy/mA17HGsaQT3/DQsWYX1f1QGWkCoVUg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await/-/plugin-syntax-top-level-await-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hx++upLv5U1rgYfwe1xBQUhRmU41NEvpUvrp8jkrSCdvGSnM5/qdRMtylJ6PG5OFkBaHkbTAKTnd3/YyESRHFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript/-/plugin-syntax-typescript-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hjMgRy5hb8uJJjUcdWunWVcoi9bGpJp8p5Ol1229PoN6aytsLwNMgmdftO23wnCLMfVmTwZDWMPNq/D1SY60JQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/template\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/template/-/template-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2ncevenBqXI6qRMukPlXwHKHchC7RyMuu4xv5JBXRfOGVcTy1mXCD12qrp7Jsoxll1EV3+9sE4GugBVRjT2jFA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/traverse\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/traverse/-/traverse-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-19lYZFzYVQkkHkl4Cy4WrAVcqBkgvV2YM2TU3xG6DIwO7O3ecbDPfW3yM3bjAGcqcQHi+CCtjMR3dIEHxsd6bA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"debug\": \"^4.3.1\",\n        \"globals\": \"^11.1.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@babel/types\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/types/-/types-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-H45s8fVLYjbhFH62dIJ3WtmJ6RSPt/3DRO0ZcT2SUiYiQyz3BLVb9ADEnLl91m74aQPS3AzzeajZHYOalWe3bg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-string-parser\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@bcoe/v8-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@bcoe/v8-coverage/-/v8-coverage-0.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0hYQ8SB4Db5zvZB4axdMHGwEaQjkZzFjQiN9LVYvIFB2nSUHW9tYpxWriPrWDASIxiaXax83REcLxuSdnGPZtw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config/-/load-nyc-config-1.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-VjeHSlIzpv/NyD3N0YuHfXOPDIixcA1q2ZV98wsMqcYlPmv2n3Yb2lYP9XMElnaFVXg5A7YLTeLu6V84uQDjmQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"camelcase\": \"^5.3.1\",\n        \"find-up\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"get-package-type\": \"^0.1.0\",\n        \"js-yaml\": \"^3.13.1\",\n        \"resolve-from\": \"^5.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@istanbuljs/schema\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@istanbuljs/schema/-/schema-0.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ZXRY4jNvVgSVQ8DL3LTcakaAtXwTVUxE81hslsyD2AtoXW/wVob10HkOJ1X/pAlcI7D+2YoZKg5do8G/w6RYgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/console\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/console/-/console-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-5Ni4CU7XHQi32IJ398EEP4RrB8eV09sXP2ROqD4bksHrnTree52PsxvX8tpL8LvTZ3pFzXyPbNQReSN41CAhOg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/core\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/core/-/core-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-n7aeXWKMnGtDA48y8TLWJPJmLmmZ642Ceo78cYWEpiD7FzDgmNDV/GCVRorPABdXLJZ/9wzzgZAlHjXjxDHGsg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/reporters\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"ansi-escapes\": \"^4.2.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-changed-files\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-resolve-dependencies\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runner\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-watcher\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/environment\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/environment/-/environment-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-aQIfHDq33ExsN4jP1NWGXhxgQ/wixs60gDiKO+XVMd8Mn0NWPWgc34ZQDTb2jKaUWQ7MuwoitXAsN2XVXNMpAw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/expect\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/expect/-/expect-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-8uMeAMycttpva3P1lBHB8VciS9V0XAr3GymPpipdyQXbBcuhkLQOSe8E/p92RyAdToS6ZD1tFkX+CkhoECE0dQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/expect-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/expect-utils/-/expect-utils-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GlsNBWiFQFCVi9QVSx7f5AgMeLxe9YCCs5PuP2O2LdjDAA8Jh9eX7lA1Jq/xdXw3Wb3hyvlFNfZIfcRetSzYcA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/fake-timers\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/fake-timers/-/fake-timers-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-q4DH1Ha4TTFPdxLsqDXK1d3+ioSL7yL5oCMJZgDYm6i+6CygW5E5xVr/D1HdsGxjt1ZWSfUAs9OxSB/BNelWrQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@sinonjs/fake-timers\": \"^10.0.2\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/globals\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/globals/-/globals-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-mpiz3dutLbkW2MNFubUGUEVLkTGiqW6yLVTA+JbP6fI6J5iL9Y0Nlg8k95pcF8ctKwCS7WVxteBs29hhfAotzQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/reporters\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/reporters/-/reporters-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DApq0KJbJOEzAFYjHADNNxAE3KbhxQB1y5Kplb5Waqw6zVbuWatSnMjE5gs8FUgEPmNsnZA3NCWl9NG0ia04Pg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@bcoe/v8-coverage\": \"^0.2.3\",\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-report\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-source-maps\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-reports\": \"^3.1.3\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"string-length\": \"^4.0.1\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"v8-to-istanbul\": \"^9.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/schemas\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/schemas/-/schemas-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-mo5j5X+jIZmJQveBKeS/clAueipV7KgiX1vMgCxam1RNYiqE1w62n0/tJJnHtjW8ZHcQco5gY85jA3mi0L+nSA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/source-map/-/source-map-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MHjT95QuipcPrpLM+8JMSzFx6eHp5Bm+4XeFDJlwsvVBjmKNiIAvasGK2fxz2WbGRlnvqehFbh07MMa7n3YJnw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"callsites\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/test-result\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/test-result/-/test-result-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Fdx+tv6x1zlkJPcWXmMDAG2HBnaR9XPSd5aDWQVsfrZmLVT3lU1cwyxLgRmXR9yrq4NBoEm9BMsfgFzTQAbJYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/test-sequencer\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/test-sequencer/-/test-sequencer-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GQwJ5WZVrKnOJuiYiAF52UNUJXgTZx1NHjFSEB0qEMmSZKAkdMoIzw/Cj6x6NF4AvV23AUqDpFzQkN/eYCYTxw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/transform\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/transform/-/transform-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ok/BTPFzFKVMwO5eOHRrvnBVHdRy9IrsrW1GpMaQ9MCnilNLXQKmAX8s1YXDFaai9xJpac2ySzV0YeRRECr2Vw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": \"^6.1.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"fast-json-stable-stringify\": \"^2.1.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pirates\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"write-file-atomic\": \"^4.0.2\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jest/types\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/types/-/types-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-u3UPsIilWKOM3F9CXtrG8LEJmNxwoCQC/XVj4IKYXvvpx7QIi/Kg1LI5uDmDpKlac62NUtX7eLjRh+jVZcLOzw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/schemas\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-reports\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/yargs\": \"^17.0.8\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.3.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/gen-mapping/-/gen-mapping-0.3.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-imAbBGkb+ebQyxKgzv5Hu2nmROxoDOXHh80evxdoXNOrvAnVx7zimzc1Oo5h9RlfV4vPXaE2iM5pOFbvOCClWA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/set-array\": \"^1.2.1\",\n        \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": \"^1.4.10\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.24\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/resolve-uri\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/resolve-uri/-/resolve-uri-3.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bRISgCIjP20/tbWSPWMEi54QVPRZExkuD9lJL+UIxUKtwVJA8wW1Trb1jMs1RFXo1CBTNZ/5hpC9QvmKWdopKw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/set-array\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/set-array/-/set-array-1.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R8gLRTZeyp03ymzP/6Lil/28tGeGEzhx1q2k703KGWRAI1VdvPIXdG70VJc2pAMw3NA6JKL5hhFu1sJX0Mnn/A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec/-/sourcemap-codec-1.5.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gv3ZRaISU3fjPAgNsriBRqGWQL6quFx04YMPW/zD8XMLsU32mhCCbfbO6KZFLjvYpCZ8zyDEgqsgf+PwPaM7GQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.3.25\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/trace-mapping/-/trace-mapping-0.3.25.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-vNk6aEwybGtawWmy/PzwnGDOjCkLWSD2wqvjGGAgOAwCGWySYXfYoxt00IJkTF+8Lb57DwOb3Aa0o9CApepiYQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/resolve-uri\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": \"^1.4.14\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@sinclair/typebox\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.27.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinclair/typebox/-/typebox-0.27.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+Fj43pSMwJs4KRrH/938Uf+uAELIgVBmQzg/q1YG10djyfA3TnrU8N8XzqCh/okZdszqBQTZf96idMfE5lnwTA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@sinonjs/commons\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinonjs/commons/-/commons-3.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-K3mCHKQ9sVh8o1C9cxkwxaOmXoAMlDxC1mYyHrjqOWEcBjYr76t96zL2zlj5dUGZ3HSw240X1qgH3Mjf1yJWpQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@sinonjs/fake-timers\": {\n      \"version\": \"10.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinonjs/fake-timers/-/fake-timers-10.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-V4BG07kuYSUkTCSBHG8G8TNhM+F19jXFWnQtzj+we8DrkpSBCee9Z3Ms8yiGer/dlmhe35/Xdgyo3/0rQKg7YA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/babel__core\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.20.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__core/-/babel__core-7.20.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qoQprZvz5wQFJwMDqeseRXWv3rqMvhgpbXFfVyWhbx9X47POIA6i/+dXefEmZKoAgOaTdaIgNSMqMIU61yRyzA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.20.7\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.20.7\",\n        \"@types/babel__generator\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/babel__template\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/babel__traverse\": \"*\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/babel__generator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__generator/-/babel__generator-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ufFd2Xi92OAVPYsy+P4n7/U7e68fex0+Ee8gSG9KX7eo084CWiQ4sdxktvdl0bOPupXtVJPY19zk6EwWqUQ8lg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/babel__template\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.4.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__template/-/babel__template-7.4.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-h/NUaSyG5EyxBIp8YRxo4RMe2/qQgvyowRwVMzhYhBCONbW8PUsg4lkFMrhgZhUe5z3L3MiLDuvyJ/CaPa2A8A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.1.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/babel__traverse\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.20.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__traverse/-/babel__traverse-7.20.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-dkO5fhS7+/oos4ciWxyEyjWe48zmG6wbCheo/G2ZnHx4fs3EU6YC6UM8rk56gAjNJ9P3MTH2jo5jb92/K6wbng==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/graceful-fs\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/graceful-fs/-/graceful-fs-4.1.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-olP3sd1qOEe5dXTSaFvQG+02VdRXcdytWLAZsAq1PecU8uqQAhkrnbli7DagjtXKW/Bl7YJbUsa8MPcuc8LHEQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-lib-coverage/-/istanbul-lib-coverage-2.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2QF/t/auWm0lsy8XtKVPG19v3sSOQlJe/YHZgfjb/KBBHOGSV+J2q/S671rcq9uTBrLAXmZpqJiaQbMT+zNU1w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/istanbul-lib-report\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-lib-report/-/istanbul-lib-report-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NQn7AHQnk/RSLOxrBbGyJM/aVQ+pjj5HCgasFxc0K/KhoATfQ/47AyUl15I2yBUpihjmas+a+VJBOqecrFH+uA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/istanbul-reports\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-reports/-/istanbul-reports-3.0.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pk2B1NWalF9toCRu6gjBzR69syFjP4Od8WRAX+0mmf9lAjCRicLOWc+ZrxZHx/0XRjotgkF9t6iaMJ+aXcOdZQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/node\": {\n      \"version\": \"22.14.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/node/-/node-22.14.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-u0HuPQwe/dHrItgHHpmw3N2fYCR6x4ivMNbPHRkBVP4CvN+kiRrKHWk3i8tXiO/joPwXLMYvF9TTF0eqgHIuOw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/stack-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/stack-utils/-/stack-utils-2.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9aEbYZ3TbYMznPdcdr3SmIrLXwC/AKZXQeCf9Pgao5CKb8CyHuEX5jzWPTkvregvhRJHcpRO6BFoGW9ycaOkYw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/yargs\": {\n      \"version\": \"17.0.33\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/yargs/-/yargs-17.0.33.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WpxBCKWPLr4xSsHgz511rFJAM+wS28w2zEO1QDNY5zM/S8ok70NNfztH0xwhqKyaK0OHCbN98LDAZuy1ctxDkA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/@types/yargs-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"21.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/yargs-parser/-/yargs-parser-21.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-I4q9QU9MQv4oEOz4tAHJtNz1cwuLxn2F3xcc2iV5WdqLPpUnj30aUuxt1mAxYTG+oe8CZMV/+6rU4S4gRDzqtQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/ansi-escapes\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-escapes/-/ansi-escapes-4.3.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gKXj5ALrKWQLsYG9jlTRmR/xKluxHV+Z9QEwNIgCfM1/uwPMCuzVVnh5mwTd+OuBZcwSIMbqssNWRm1lE51QaQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/ansi-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-regex/-/ansi-regex-5.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-quJQXlTSUGL2LH9SUXo8VwsY4soanhgo6LNSm84E1LBcE8s3O0wpdiRzyR9z/ZZJMlMWv37qOOb9pdJlMUEKFQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/ansi-styles\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-styles/-/ansi-styles-4.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zbB9rCJAT1rbjiVDb2hqKFHNYLxgtk8NURxZ3IZwD3F6NtxbXZQCnnSi1Lkx+IDohdPlFp222wVALIheZJQSEg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/anymatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/anymatch/-/anymatch-3.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KMReFUr0B4t+D+OBkjR3KYqvocp2XaSzO55UcB6mgQMd3KbcE+mWTyvVV7D/zsdEbNnV6acZUutkiHQXvTr1Rw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"normalize-path\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"picomatch\": \"^2.0.4\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/argparse\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/argparse/-/argparse-1.0.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-o5Roy6tNG4SL/FOkCAN6RzjiakZS25RLYFrcMttJqbdd8BWrnA+fGz57iN5Pb06pvBGvl5gQ0B48dJlslXvoTg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-jest/-/babel-jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BrvGY3xZSwEcCzKvKsCi2GgHqDqsYkOP4/by5xCgIwGXQxIEh+8ew3gmrE1y7XRR6LHZIj6yLYnUi/mm2KXKBg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@types/babel__core\": \"^7.1.14\",\n        \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": \"^6.1.1\",\n        \"babel-preset-jest\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-plugin-istanbul\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-plugin-istanbul/-/babel-plugin-istanbul-6.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Y1IQok9821cC9onCx5otgFfRm7Lm+I+wwxOx738M/WLPZ9Q42m4IG5W0FNX8WLL2gYMZo3JkuXIH2DOpWM+qwA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-plugin-utils\": \"^7.0.0\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": \"^5.0.4\",\n        \"test-exclude\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-plugin-istanbul/node_modules/istanbul-lib-instrument\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-instrument/-/istanbul-lib-instrument-5.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pzqtp31nLv/XFOzXGuvhCb8qhjmTVo5vjVk19XE4CRlSWz0KoeJ3bw9XsA7nOp9YBf4qHjwBxkDzKcME/J29Yg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.12.3\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.14.7\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-plugin-jest-hoist\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-plugin-jest-hoist/-/babel-plugin-jest-hoist-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ESAc/RJvGTFEzRwOTT4+lNDk/GNHMkKbNzsvT0qKRfDyyYTskxB5rnU2njIDYVxXCBHHEI1c0YwHob3WaYujOg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@types/babel__core\": \"^7.1.14\",\n        \"@types/babel__traverse\": \"^7.0.6\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-preset-current-node-syntax/-/babel-preset-current-node-syntax-1.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ldYss8SbBlWva1bs28q78Ju5Zq1F+8BrqBZZ0VFhLBvhh6lCpC2o3gDJi/5DRLs9FgYZCnmPYIVFU4lRXCkyUw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators\": \"^7.8.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties\": \"^7.12.13\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block\": \"^7.14.5\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes\": \"^7.24.7\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object\": \"^7.14.5\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await\": \"^7.14.5\"\n      },\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/babel-preset-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-preset-jest/-/babel-preset-jest-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0B3bhxR6snWXJZtR/RliHTDPRgn1sNHOR0yVtq/IiQFyuOVjFS+wuio/R4gSNkyYmKmJB4wGZv2NZanmKmTnNA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"babel-plugin-jest-hoist\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/balanced-match\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/balanced-match/-/balanced-match-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3oSeUO0TMV67hN1AmbXsK4yaqU7tjiHlbxRDZOpH0KW9+CeX4bRAaX0Anxt0tx2MrpRpWwQaPwIlISEJhYU5Pw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/brace-expansion\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.11\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/brace-expansion/-/brace-expansion-1.1.11.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iCuPHDFgrHX7H2vEI/5xpz07zSHB00TpugqhmYtVmMO6518mCuRMoOYFldEBl0g187ufozdaHgWKcYFb61qGiA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"balanced-match\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"concat-map\": \"0.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/braces\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/braces/-/braces-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-yQbXgO/OSZVD2IsiLlro+7Hf6Q18EJrKSEsdoMzKePKXct3gvD8oLcOQdIzGupr5Fj+EDe8gO/lxc1BzfMpxvA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/browserslist\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.24.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/browserslist/-/browserslist-4.24.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KDi1Ny1gSePi1vm0q4oxSF8b4DR44GF4BbmS2YdhPLOEqd8pDviZOGH/GsmRwoWJ2+5Lr085X7naowMwKHDG1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n          \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"tidelift\",\n          \"url\": \"https://tidelift.com/funding/github/npm/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"github\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/ai\"\n        }\n      ],\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"caniuse-lite\": \"^1.0.30001688\",\n        \"electron-to-chromium\": \"^1.5.73\",\n        \"node-releases\": \"^2.0.19\",\n        \"update-browserslist-db\": \"^1.1.1\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": {\n        \"node\": \"^6 || ^7 || ^8 || ^9 || ^10 || ^11 || ^12 || >=13.7\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/bser\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/bser/-/bser-2.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gQxTNE/GAfIIrmHLUE3oJyp5FO6HRBfhjnw4/wMmA63ZGDJnWBmgY/lyQBpnDUkGmAhbSe39tx2d/iTOAfglwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/buffer-from\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/buffer-from/-/buffer-from-1.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-E+XQCRwSbaaiChtv6k6Dwgc+bx+Bs6vuKJHHl5kox/BaKbhiXzqQOwK4cO22yElGp2OCmjwVhT3HmxgyPGnJfQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/callsites\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/callsites/-/callsites-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-P8BjAsXvZS+VIDUI11hHCQEv74YT67YUi5JJFNWIqL235sBmjX4+qx9Muvls5ivyNENctx46xQLQ3aTuE7ssaQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/camelcase\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/camelcase/-/camelcase-5.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-L28STB170nwWS63UjtlEOE3dldQApaJXZkOI1uMFfzf3rRuPegHaHesyee+YxQ+W6SvRDQV6UrdOdRiR153wJg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/caniuse-lite\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.30001715\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/caniuse-lite/-/caniuse-lite-1.0.30001715.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7ptkFGMm2OAOgvZpwgA4yjQ5SQbrNVGdRjzH0pBdy1Fasvcr+KAeECmbCAECzTuDuoX0FCY8KzUxjf9+9kfZEw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n          \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"tidelift\",\n          \"url\": \"https://tidelift.com/funding/github/npm/caniuse-lite\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"github\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/ai\"\n        }\n      ]\n    },\n    \"node_modules/chalk\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/chalk/-/chalk-4.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-oKnbhFyRIXpUuez8iBMmyEa4nbj4IOQyuhc/wy9kY7/WVPcwIO9VA668Pu8RkO7+0G76SLROeyw9CpQ061i4mA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^7.1.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/char-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/char-regex/-/char-regex-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kWWXztvZ5SBQV+eRgKFeh8q5sLuZY2+8WUIzlxWVTg+oGwY14qylx1KbKzHd8P6ZYkAg0xyIDU9JMHhyJMZ1jw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/ci-info\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.9.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ci-info/-/ci-info-3.9.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NIxF55hv4nSqQswkAeiOi1r83xy8JldOFDTWiug55KBu9Jnblncd2U6ViHmYgHf01TPZS77NJBhBMKdWj9HQMQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"github\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/sibiraj-s\"\n        }\n      ],\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/cjs-module-lexer\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cjs-module-lexer/-/cjs-module-lexer-1.4.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9z8TZaGM1pfswYeXrUpzPrkx8UnWYdhJclsiYMm6x/w5+nN+8Tf/LnAgfLGQCm59qAOxU8WwHEq2vNwF6i4j+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/cliui\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cliui/-/cliui-8.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BSeNnyus75C4//NQ9gQt1/csTXyo/8Sb+afLAkzAptFuMsod9HFokGNudZpi/oQV73hnVK+sR+5PVRMd+Dr7YQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.2.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.1\",\n        \"wrap-ansi\": \"^7.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/co\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.6.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/co/-/co-4.6.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-QVb0dM5HvG+uaxitm8wONl7jltx8dqhfU33DcqtOZcLSVIKSDDLDi7+0LbAKiyI8hD9u42m2YxXSkMGWThaecQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/collect-v8-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/collect-v8-coverage/-/collect-v8-coverage-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lHl4d5/ONEbLlJvaJNtsF/Lz+WvB07u2ycqTYbdrq7UypDXailES4valYb2eWiJFxZlVmpGekfqoxQhzyFdT4Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/color-convert\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/color-convert/-/color-convert-2.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RRECPsj7iu/xb5oKYcsFHSppFNnsj/52OVTRKb4zP5onXwVF3zVmmToNcOfGC+CRDpfK/U584fMg38ZHCaElKQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/color-name\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/color-name/-/color-name-1.1.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-dOy+3AuW3a2wNbZHIuMZpTcgjGuLU/uBL/ubcZF9OXbDo8ff4O8yVp5Bf0efS8uEoYo5q4Fx7dY9OgQGXgAsQA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/concat-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/concat-map/-/concat-map-0.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/Srv4dswyQNBfohGpz9o6Yb3Gz3SrUDqBH5rTuhGR7ahtlbYKnVxw2bCFMRljaA7EXHaXZ8wsHdodFvbkhKmqg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/convert-source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/convert-source-map/-/convert-source-map-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Kvp459HrV2FEJ1CAsi1Ku+MY3kasH19TFykTz2xWmMeq6bk2NU3XXvfJ+Q61m0xktWwt+1HSYf3JZsTms3aRJg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/create-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/create-jest/-/create-jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Adz2bdH0Vq3F53KEMJOoftQFutWCukm6J24wbPWRO4k1kMY7gS7ds/uoJkNuV8wDCtWWnuwGcJwpWcih+zEW1Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"prompts\": \"^2.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/cross-spawn\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cross-spawn/-/cross-spawn-7.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-uV2QOWP2nWzsy2aMp8aRibhi9dlzF5Hgh5SHaB9OiTGEyDTiJJyx0uy51QXdyWbtAHNua4XJzUKca3OzKUd3vA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"path-key\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"shebang-command\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"which\": \"^2.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/debug\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/debug/-/debug-4.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6WTZ/IxCY/T6BALoZHaE4ctp9xm+Z5kY/pzYaCHRFeyVhojxlrm+46y68HA6hr0TcwEssoxNiDEUJQjfPZ/RYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/dedent\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/dedent/-/dedent-1.5.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NHQtfOOW68WD8lgypbLA5oT+Bt0xXJhiYvoR6SmmNXZfpzOGXwdKWmcwG8N7PwVVWV3eF/68nmD9BaJSsTBhyQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/deepmerge\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/deepmerge/-/deepmerge-4.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3sUqbMEc77XqpdNO7FRyRog+eW3ph+GYCbj+rK+uYyRMuwsVy0rMiVtPn+QJlKFvWP/1PYpapqYn0Me2knFn+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/detect-newline\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/detect-newline/-/detect-newline-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TLz+x/vEXm/Y7P7wn1EJFNLxYpUD4TgMosxY6fAVJUnJMbupHBOncxyWUG9OpTaH9EBD7uFI5LfEgmMOc54DsA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/diff-sequences\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/diff-sequences/-/diff-sequences-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-EjePK1srD3P08o2j4f0ExnylqRs5B9tJjcp9t1krH2qRi8CCdsYfwe9JgSLurFBWwq4uOlipzfk5fHNvwFKr8Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/electron-to-chromium\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.140\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/electron-to-chromium/-/electron-to-chromium-1.5.140.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-o82Rj+ONp4Ip7Cl1r7lrqx/pXhbp/lh9DpKcMNscFJdh8ebyRofnc7Sh01B4jx403RI0oqTBvlZ7OBIZLMr2+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/emittery\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.13.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/emittery/-/emittery-0.13.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DeWwawk6r5yR9jFgnDKYt4sLS0LmHJJi3ZOnb5/JdbYwj3nW+FxQnHIjhBKz8YLC7oRNPVM9NQ47I3CVx34eqQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": {\n        \"url\": \"https://github.com/sindresorhus/emittery?sponsor=1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/emoji-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/emoji-regex/-/emoji-regex-8.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MSjYzcWNOA0ewAHpz0MxpYFvwg6yjy1NG3xteoqz644VCo/RPgnr1/GGt+ic3iJTzQ8Eu3TdM14SawnVUmGE6A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/error-ex\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.3.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/error-ex/-/error-ex-1.3.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7dFHNmqeFSEt2ZBsCriorKnn3Z2pj+fd9kmI6QoWw4//DL+icEBfc0U7qJCisqrTsKTjw4fNFy2pW9OqStD84g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/escalade\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/escalade/-/escalade-3.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WUj2qlxaQtO4g6Pq5c29GTcWGDyd8itL8zTlipgECz3JesAiiOKotd8JU6otB3PACgG6xkJUyVhboMS+bje/jA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/escape-string-regexp\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/escape-string-regexp/-/escape-string-regexp-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UpzcLCXolUWcNu5HtVMHYdXJjArjsF9C0aNnquZYY4uW/Vu0miy5YoWvbV345HauVvcAUnpRuhMMcqTcGOY2+w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/esprima\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/esprima/-/esprima-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eGuFFw7Upda+g4p+QHvnW0RyTX/SVeJBDM/gCtMARO0cLuT2HcEKnTPvhjV6aGeqrCB/sbNop0Kszm0jsaWU4A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": {\n        \"esparse\": \"bin/esparse.js\",\n        \"esvalidate\": \"bin/esvalidate.js\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/execa\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/execa/-/execa-5.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-8uSpZZocAZRBAPIEINJj3Lo9HyGitllczc27Eh5YYojjMFMn8yHMDMaUHE2Jqfq05D/wucwI4JGURyXt1vchyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"cross-spawn\": \"^7.0.3\",\n        \"get-stream\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"human-signals\": \"^2.1.0\",\n        \"is-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"merge-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"npm-run-path\": \"^4.0.1\",\n        \"onetime\": \"^5.1.2\",\n        \"signal-exit\": \"^3.0.3\",\n        \"strip-final-newline\": \"^2.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/exit\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/exit/-/exit-0.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Zk/eNKV2zbjpKzrsQ+n1G6poVbErQxJ0LBOJXaKZ1EViLzH+hrLu9cdXI4zw9dBQJslwBEpbQ2P1oS7nDxs6jQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/expect\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/expect/-/expect-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2Zks0hf1VLFYI1kbh0I5jP3KHHyCHpkfyHBzsSXRFgl/Bg9mWYfMW8oD+PdMPlEwy5HNsR9JutYy6pMeOh61nw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/expect-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/fast-json-stable-stringify\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fast-json-stable-stringify/-/fast-json-stable-stringify-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lhd/wF+Lk98HZoTCtlVraHtfh5XYijIjalXck7saUtuanSDyLMxnHhSXEDJqHxD7msR8D0uCmqlkwjCV8xvwHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/fb-watchman\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fb-watchman/-/fb-watchman-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-p5161BqbuCaSnB8jIbzQHOlpgsPmK5rJVDfDKO91Axs5NC1uu3HRQm6wt9cd9/+GtQQIO53JdGXXoyDpTAsgYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/fill-range\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fill-range/-/fill-range-7.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-YsGpe3WHLK8ZYi4tWDg2Jy3ebRz2rXowDxnld4bkQB00cc/1Zw9AWnC0i9ztDJitivtQvaI9KaLyKrc+hBW0yg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/find-up\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/find-up/-/find-up-4.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-PpOwAdQ/YlXQ2vj8a3h8IipDuYRi3wceVQQGYWxNINccq40Anw7BlsEXCMbt1Zt+OLA6Fq9suIpIWD0OsnISlw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"locate-path\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"path-exists\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/fs.realpath\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fs.realpath/-/fs.realpath-1.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OO0pH2lK6a0hZnAdau5ItzHPI6pUlvI7jMVnxUQRtw4owF2wk8lOSabtGDCTP4Ggrg2MbGnWO9X8K1t4+fGMDw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/fsevents\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fsevents/-/fsevents-2.3.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-5xoDfX+fL7faATnagmWPpbFtwh/R77WmMMqqHGS65C3vvB0YHrgF+B1YmZ3441tMj5n63k0212XNoJwzlhffQw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"hasInstallScript\": true,\n      \"optional\": true,\n      \"os\": [\n        \"darwin\"\n      ],\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/function-bind\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/function-bind/-/function-bind-1.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7XHNxH7qX9xG5mIwxkhumTox/MIRNcOgDrxWsMt2pAr23WHp6MrRlN7FBSFpCpr+oVO0F744iUgR82nJMfG2SA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/gensync\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0-beta.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/gensync/-/gensync-1.0.0-beta.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3hN7NaskYvMDLQY55gnW3NQ+mesEAepTqlg+VEbj7zzqEMBVNhzcGYYeqFo/TlYz6eQiFcp1HcsCZO+nGgS8zg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/get-caller-file\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-caller-file/-/get-caller-file-2.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DyFP3BM/3YHTQOCUL/w0OZHR0lpKeGrxotcHWcqNEdnltqFwXVfhEBQ94eIo34AfQpo0rGki4cyIiftY06h2Fg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/get-package-type\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-package-type/-/get-package-type-0.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pjzuKtY64GYfWizNAJ0fr9VqttZkNiK2iS430LtIHzjBEr6bX8Am2zm4sW4Ro5wjWW5cAlRL1qAMTcXbjNAO2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/get-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-stream/-/get-stream-6.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ts6Wi+2j3jQjqi70w5AlN8DFnkSwC+MqmxEzdEALB2qXZYV3X/b1CTfgPLGJNMeAWxdPfU8FO1ms3NUfaHCPYg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/glob\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/glob/-/glob-7.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-nFR0zLpU2YCaRxwoCJvL6UvCH2JFyFVIvwTLsIf21AuHlMskA1hhTdk+LlYJtOlYt9v6dvszD2BGRqBL+iQK9Q==\",\n      \"deprecated\": \"Glob versions prior to v9 are no longer supported\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"fs.realpath\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"inflight\": \"^1.0.4\",\n        \"inherits\": \"2\",\n        \"minimatch\": \"^3.1.1\",\n        \"once\": \"^1.3.0\",\n        \"path-is-absolute\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/globals\": {\n      \"version\": \"11.12.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/globals/-/globals-11.12.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WOBp/EEGUiIsJSp7wcv/y6MO+lV9UoncWqxuFfm8eBwzWNgyfBd6Gz+IeKQ9jCmyhoH99g15M3T+QaVHFjizVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/graceful-fs\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.11\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/graceful-fs/-/graceful-fs-4.2.11.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RbJ5/jmFcNNCcDV5o9eTnBLJ/HszWV0P73bc+Ff4nS/rJj+YaS6IGyiOL0VoBYX+l1Wrl3k63h/KrH+nhJ0XvQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/has-flag\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/has-flag/-/has-flag-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-EykJT/Q1KjTWctppgIAgfSO0tKVuZUjhgMr17kqTumMl6Afv3EISleU7qZUzoXDFTAHTDC4NOoG/ZxU3EvlMPQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/hasown\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/hasown/-/hasown-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0hJU9SCPvmMzIBdZFqNPXWa6dqh7WdH0cII9y+CyS8rG3nL48Bclra9HmKhVVUHyPWNH5Y7xDwAB7bfgSjkUMQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/html-escaper\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/html-escaper/-/html-escaper-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-H2iMtd0I4Mt5eYiapRdIDjp+XzelXQ0tFE4JS7YFwFevXXMmOp9myNrUvCg0D6ws8iqkRPBfKHgbwig1SmlLfg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/human-signals\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/human-signals/-/human-signals-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-B4FFZ6q/T2jhhksgkbEW3HBvWIfDW85snkQgawt07S7J5QXTk6BkNV+0yAeZrM5QpMAdYlocGoljn0sJ/WQkFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/import-local\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/import-local/-/import-local-3.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2SPlun1JUPWoM6t3F0dw0FkCF/jWY8kttcY4f599GLTSjh2OCuuhdTkJQsEcZzBqbXZGKMK2OqW1oZsjtf/gQA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/imurmurhash\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/imurmurhash/-/imurmurhash-0.1.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JmXMZ6wuvDmLiHEml9ykzqO6lwFbof0GG4IkcGaENdCRDDmMVnny7s5HsIgHCbaq0w2MyPhDqkhTUgS2LU2PHA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/inflight\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/inflight/-/inflight-1.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-k92I/b08q4wvFscXCLvqfsHCrjrF7yiXsQuIVvVE7N82W3+aqpzuUdBbfhWcy/FZR3/4IgflMgKLOsvPDrGCJA==\",\n      \"deprecated\": \"This module is not supported, and leaks memory. Do not use it. Check out lru-cache if you want a good and tested way to coalesce async requests by a key value, which is much more comprehensive and powerful.\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/inherits\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/inherits/-/inherits-2.0.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-k/vGaX4/Yla3WzyMCvTQOXYeIHvqOKtnqBduzTHpzpQZzAskKMhZ2K+EnBiSM9zGSoIFeMpXKxa4dYeZIQqewQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-arrayish\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-arrayish/-/is-arrayish-0.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zz06S8t0ozoDXMG+ube26zeCTNXcKIPJZJi8hBrF4idCLms4CG9QtK7qBl1boi5ODzFpjswb5JPmHCbMpjaYzg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-core-module\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.16.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-core-module/-/is-core-module-2.16.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UfoeMA6fIJ8wTYFEUjelnaGI67v6+N7qXJEvQuIGa99l4xsCruSYOVSQ0uPANn4dAzm8lkYPaKLrrijLq7x23w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-fullwidth-code-point\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-fullwidth-code-point/-/is-fullwidth-code-point-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zymm5+u+sCsSWyD9qNaejV3DFvhCKclKdizYaJUuHA83RLjb7nSuGnddCHGv0hk+KY7BMAlsWeK4Ueg6EV6XQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-generator-fn\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-generator-fn/-/is-generator-fn-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-cTIB4yPYL/Grw0EaSzASzg6bBy9gqCofvWN8okThAYIxKJZC+udlRAmGbM0XLeniEJSs8uEgHPGuHSe1XsOLSQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-number\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-number/-/is-number-7.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-41Cifkg6e8TylSpdtTpeLVMqvSBEVzTttHvERD741+pnZ8ANv0004MRL43QKPDlK9cGvNp6NZWZUBlbGXYxxng==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/is-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-stream/-/is-stream-2.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hFoiJiTl63nn+kstHGBtewWSKnQLpyb155KHheA1l39uvtO9nWIop1p3udqPcUd/xbF1VLMO4n7OI6p7RbngDg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/isexe\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/isexe/-/isexe-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RHxMLp9lnKHGHRng9QFhRCMbYAcVpn69smSGcq3f36xjgVVWThj4qqLbTLlq7Ssj8B+fIQ1EuCEGI2lKsyQeIw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-coverage/-/istanbul-lib-coverage-3.2.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-O8dpsF+r0WV/8MNRKfnmrtCWhuKjxrq2w+jpzBL5UZKTi2LeVWnWOmWRxFlesJONmc+wLAGvKQZEOanko0LFTg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-instrument\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-instrument/-/istanbul-lib-instrument-6.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Vtgk7L/R2JHyyGW07spoFlB8/lpjiOLTjMdms6AFMraYt3BaJauod/NGrfnVG/y4Ix1JEuMRPDPEj2ua+zz1/Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.23.9\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.23.9\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.3\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^7.5.4\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-instrument/node_modules/semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-report\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-report/-/istanbul-lib-report-3.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GCfE1mtsHGOELCU8e/Z7YWzpmybrx/+dSTfLrvY8qRmaY6zXTKWn6WQIjaAFw069icm6GVMNkgu0NzI4iPZUNw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"make-dir\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^7.1.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-lib-source-maps\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-source-maps/-/istanbul-lib-source-maps-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-n3s8EwkdFIJCG3BPKBYvskgXGoy88ARzvegkitk60NxRdwltLOTaH7CUiMRXvwYorl0Q712iEjcWB+fK/MrWVw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"debug\": \"^4.1.1\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"source-map\": \"^0.6.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/istanbul-reports\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-reports/-/istanbul-reports-3.1.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BewmUXImeuRk2YY0PVbxgKAysvhRPUQE0h5QRM++nVWyubKGV0l8qQ5op8+B2DOmwSe63Jivj0BjkPQVf8fP5g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"html-escaper\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-report\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest/-/jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NIy3oAFp9shda19hy4HK0HRTWKtPJmGdnvywu01nOqNC2vZg+Z+fvJDxpMQA88eb2I9EcafcdjYgsDthnYTvGw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/core\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"import-local\": \"^3.0.2\",\n        \"jest-cli\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-changed-files\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-changed-files/-/jest-changed-files-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fEArFiwf1BpQ+4bXSprcDc3/x4HSzL4al2tozwVpDFpsxALjLYdyiIK4e5Vz66GQJIbXJ82+35PtysofptNX2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"execa\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-circus\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-circus/-/jest-circus-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3E1nCMgipcTkCocFwM90XXQab9bS+GMsjdpmPrlelaxwD93Ad8iVEjX/vvHPdLPnFf+L40u+5+iutRdA1N9myw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"co\": \"^4.6.0\",\n        \"dedent\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"is-generator-fn\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"jest-each\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"pure-rand\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"stack-utils\": \"^2.0.3\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-cli\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-cli/-/jest-cli-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OVVobw2IubN/GSYsxETi+gOe7Ka59EFMR/twOU3Jb2GnKKeMGJB5SGUUrEz3SFVmJASUdZUzy83sLNNQ2gZslg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/core\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"create-jest\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"import-local\": \"^3.0.2\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"yargs\": \"^17.3.1\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-config\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-config/-/jest-config-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-uXbpfeQ7R6TZBqI3/TxCU4q4ttk3u0PJeC+E0zbfSoSjq6bJ7buBPxzQPL0ifrkY4DNu4JUdk0ImlBUYi840eQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@jest/test-sequencer\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-jest\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"deepmerge\": \"^4.2.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-circus\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-environment-node\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runner\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"parse-json\": \"^5.2.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-json-comments\": \"^3.1.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": ,\n        \"ts-node\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-diff\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-diff/-/jest-diff-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LMIgiIrhigmPrs03JHpxUh2yISK3vLFPkAodPeo0+BuF7wA2FoQbkEg1u8gBYBThncu7e1oEDUfIXVuTqLRUjw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"diff-sequences\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-docblock\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-docblock/-/jest-docblock-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-q617Auw3A612guyaFgsbFeYpNP5t2aoUNLwBUbc/0kD1R4t9ixDbyFTHd1nok4epoVFpr7PmeWHrhvuV3XaJ4g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-each\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-each/-/jest-each-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gns+Er14+ZrEoC5fhOfYCY1LOHHr0TI+rQUHZS8Ttw2l7gl+80eHc/gFf2Ktkw0+SIACDTeWvpFcv3B04VembQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-environment-node\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-environment-node/-/jest-environment-node-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DOSwCRqXirTOyheM+4d5YZOrWcdu0LNZ87ewUoywbcb2XR4wKgqiG8vNeYwhjFMbEkfju7wx2GYH0P2gevGvFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-get-type\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-get-type/-/jest-get-type-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zrteXnqYxfQh7l5FHyL38jL39di8H8rHoecLH3JNxH3BwOrBsNeabdap5e0I23lD4HHI8W5VFBZqG4Eaq5LNcw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-haste-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-haste-map/-/jest-haste-map-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fP8u2pyfqx0K1rGn1R9pyE0/KTn+G7PxktWidOBTqFPLYX0b9ksaMFkhK5vrS3DVun09pckLdlx90QthlW7AmA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/graceful-fs\": \"^4.1.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"anymatch\": \"^3.0.3\",\n        \"fb-watchman\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"walker\": \"^1.0.8\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"optionalDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-leak-detector\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-leak-detector/-/jest-leak-detector-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kYA8IJcSYtST2BY9I+SMC32nDpBT3J2NvWJx8+JCuCdl/CR1I4EKUJROiP8XtCcxqgTTBGJNdbB1A8XRKbTetw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-matcher-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-matcher-utils/-/jest-matcher-utils-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-sBkD+Xi9DtcChsI3L3u0+N0opgPYnCRPtGcQYrgXmR+hmt/fYfWAL0xRXYU8eWOdfuLgBe0YCW3AFtnRLagq/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-diff\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-message-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-message-util/-/jest-message-util-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GBEV4GRADeP+qtB2+6u61stea8mGcOT4mCtrYISZwfu9/ISHFJ/5zOMXYbpBE9RsS5+Gb63DW4FgmnKJ79Kf6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.12.13\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/stack-utils\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"stack-utils\": \"^2.0.3\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-mock\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-mock/-/jest-mock-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ITOMZn+UkYS4ZFh83xYAOzWStloNzJFO2s8DWrE4lhtGD+AorgnbkiKERe4wQVBydIGPx059g6riW5Btp6Llnw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-pnp-resolver\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-pnp-resolver/-/jest-pnp-resolver-1.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+3NpwQEnRoIBtx4fyhblQDPgJI0H1IEIkX7ShLUjPGA7TtUTvI1oiKi3SR4oBR0hQhQR80l4WAe5RrXBwWMA8w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": ,\n      \"peerDependenciesMeta\": \n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-regex-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-regex-util/-/jest-regex-util-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KJJBsRCyyLNWCNBOvZyRDnAIfUiRJ8v+hOBQYGn8gDyF3UegwiP4gwRR3/SDa42g1YbVycTidUF3rKjyLFDWbg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-resolve\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-resolve/-/jest-resolve-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-IOVhZSrg+UvVAshDSDtHyFCCBUl/Q3AAJv8iZ6ZjnZ74xzvwuzLXid9IIIPgTnY62SJjfuupMKZsZQRsCvxEgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-pnp-resolver\": \"^1.2.2\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"resolve\": \"^1.20.0\",\n        \"resolve.exports\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-resolve-dependencies\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-resolve-dependencies/-/jest-resolve-dependencies-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-un0zD/6qxJ+S0et7WxeI3H5XSe9lTBBR7bOHCHXkKR6luG5mwDDlIzVQ0V5cZCuoTgEdcdwzTghYkTWfubi+nA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-runner\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-runner/-/jest-runner-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fsc4N6cPCAahybGBfTRcq5wFR6fpLznMg47sY5aDpsoejOcVYFb07AHuSnR0liMcPTgBsA3ZJL6kFOjPdoNipQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"emittery\": \"^0.13.1\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-docblock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-environment-node\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-leak-detector\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-watcher\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"source-map-support\": \"0.5.13\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-runtime\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-runtime/-/jest-runtime-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gUnLjgwdGqW7B4LvOIkbKs9WGbn+QLqRQQ9juC6HndeDiezIwhDP+mhMwHWCEcfQ5RUXa6OPnFF8BJh5xegwwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/globals\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/source-map\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"cjs-module-lexer\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-bom\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-snapshot\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-snapshot/-/jest-snapshot-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Rm0BMWtxBcioHr1/OX5YCP8Uov4riHvKPknOGs804Zg9JGZgmIBkbtlxJC/7Z4msKYVbIJtfU+tKb8xlYNfdkw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@jest/expect-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-diff\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"natural-compare\": \"^1.4.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^7.5.3\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-snapshot/node_modules/semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-util/-/jest-util-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-z6EbKajIpqGKU56y5KBUgy1dt1ihhQJgWzUlZHArA/+X2ad7Cb5iF+AK1EWVL/Bo7Rz9uurpqw6SiBCefUbCGA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"picomatch\": \"^2.2.3\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-validate\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-validate/-/jest-validate-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ZB7wHqaRGVw/9hST/OuFUReG7M8vKeq0/J2egIGLdvjHCmYqGARhzXmtgi+gVeZ5uXFF219aOc3Ls2yLg27tkw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"camelcase\": \"^6.2.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"leven\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-validate/node_modules/camelcase\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/camelcase/-/camelcase-6.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Gmy6FhYlCY7uOElZUSbxo2UCDH8owEk996gkbrpsgGtrJLM3J7jGxl9Ic7Qwwj4ivOE5AWZWRMecDdF7hqGjFA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-watcher\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-watcher/-/jest-watcher-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-49Fg7WXkU3Vl2h6LbLtMQ/HyB6rXSIX7SqvBLQmssRBGN9I0PNvPmAmCWSOY6SOvrjhI/F7/bGAv9RtnsPA03g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"ansi-escapes\": \"^4.2.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"emittery\": \"^0.13.1\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"string-length\": \"^4.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-worker\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-worker/-/jest-worker-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eIz2msL/EzL9UFTFFx7jBTkeZfku0yUAyZZZmJ93H2TYEiroIx2PQjEXcwYtYl8zXCxb+PAmA2hLIt/6ZEkPHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"merge-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^8.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jest-worker/node_modules/supports-color\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-color/-/supports-color-8.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MpUEN2OodtUzxvKQl72cUF7RQ5EiHsGvSsVG0ia9c5RbWGL2CI4C7EpPS8UTBIplnlzZiNuV56w+FuNxy3ty2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/js-tokens\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/js-tokens/-/js-tokens-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RdJUflcE3cUzKiMqQgsCu06FPu9UdIJO0beYbPhHN4k6apgJtifcoCtT9bcxOpYBtpD2kCM6Sbzg4CausW/PKQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/js-yaml\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.14.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/js-yaml/-/js-yaml-3.14.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-okMH7OXXJ7YrN9Ok3/SXrnu4iX9yOk+25nqX4imS2npuvTYDmo/QEZoqwZkYaIDk3jVvBOTOIEgEhaLOynBS9g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/jsesc\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jsesc/-/jsesc-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/sM3dO2FOzXjKQhJuo0Q173wf2KOo8t4I8vHy6lF9poUp7bKT0/NHE8fPX23PwfhnykfqnC2xRxOnVw5XuGIaA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/json-parse-even-better-errors\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/json-parse-even-better-errors/-/json-parse-even-better-errors-2.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xyFwyhro/JEof6Ghe2iz2NcXoj2sloNsWr/XsERDK/oiPCfaNhl5ONfp+jQdAZRQQ0IJWNzH9zIZF7li91kh2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/json5\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/json5/-/json5-2.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XmOWe7eyHYH14cLdVPoyg+GOH3rYX++KpzrylJwSW98t3Nk+U8XOl8FWKOgwtzdb8lXGf6zYwDUzeHMWfxasyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/kleur\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/kleur/-/kleur-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eTIzlVOSUR+JxdDFepEYcBMtZ9Qqdef+rnzWdRZuMbOywu5tO2w2N7rqjoANZ5k9vywhL6Br1VRjUIgTQx4E8w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/leven\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/leven/-/leven-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qsda+H8jTaUaN/x5vzW2rzc+8Rw4TAQ/4KjB46IwK5VH+IlVeeeje/EoZRpiXvIqjFgK84QffqPztGI3VBLG1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/lines-and-columns\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/lines-and-columns/-/lines-and-columns-1.2.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7ylylesZQ/PV29jhEDl3Ufjo6ZX7gCqJr5F7PKrqc93v7fzSymt1BpwEU8nAUXs8qzzvqhbjhK5QZg6Mt/HkBg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/locate-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/locate-path/-/locate-path-5.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-t7hw9pI+WvuwNJXwk5zVHpyhIqzg2qTlklJOf0mVxGSbe3Fp2VieZcduNYjaLDoy6p9uGpQEGWG87WpMKlNq8g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/lru-cache\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/lru-cache/-/lru-cache-5.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KpNARQA3Iwv+jTA0utUVVbrh+Jlrr1Fv0e56GGzAFOXN7dk/FviaDW8LHmK52DlcH4WP2n6gI8vN1aesBFgo9w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/make-dir\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/make-dir/-/make-dir-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hXdUTZYIVOt1Ex//jAQi+wTZZpUpwBj/0QsOzqegb3rGMMeJiSEu5xLHnYfBrRV4RH2+OCSOO95Is/7x1WJ4bw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/make-dir/node_modules/semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/makeerror\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.12\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/makeerror/-/makeerror-1.0.12.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JmqCvUhmt43madlpFzG4BQzG2Z3m6tvQDNKdClZnO3VbIudJYmxsT0FNJMeiB2+JTSlTQTSbU8QdesVmwJcmLg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/merge-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/merge-stream/-/merge-stream-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-abv/qOcuPfk3URPfDzmZU1LKmuw8kT+0nIHvKrKgFrwifol/doWcdA4ZqsWQ8ENrFKkd67Mfpo/LovbIUsbt3w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/micromatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/micromatch/-/micromatch-4.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-PXwfBhYu0hBCPw8Dn0E+WDYb7af3dSLVWKi3HGv84IdF4TyFoC0ysxFd0Goxw7nSv4T/PzEJQxsYsEiFCKo2BA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/mimic-fn\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/mimic-fn/-/mimic-fn-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OqbOk5oEQeAZ8WXWydlu9HJjz9WVdEIvamMCcXmuqUYjTknH/sqsWvhQ3vgwKFRR1HpjvNBKQ37nbJgYzGqGcg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/minimatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/minimatch/-/minimatch-3.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-J7p63hRiAjw1NDEww1W7i37+ByIrOWO5XQQAzZ3VOcL0PNybwpfmV/N05zFAzwQ9USyEcX6t3UO+K5aqBQOIHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/ms\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ms/-/ms-2.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6FlzubTLZG3J2a/NVCAleEhjzq5oxgHyaCU9yYXvcLsvoVaHJq/s5xXI6/XXP6tz7R9xAOtHnSO/tXtF3WRTlA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/natural-compare\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/natural-compare/-/natural-compare-1.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OWND8ei3VtNC9h7V60qff3SVobHr996CTwgxubgyQYEpg290h9J0buyECNNJexkFm5sOajh5G116RYA1c8ZMSw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/node-int64\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/node-int64/-/node-int64-0.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-O5lz91xSOeoXP6DulyHfllpq+Eg00MWitZIbtPfoSEvqIHdl5gfcY6hYzDWnj0qD5tz52PI08u9qUvSVeUBeHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/node-releases\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.19\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/node-releases/-/node-releases-2.0.19.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xxOWJsBKtzAq7DY0J+DTzuz58K8e7sJbdgwkbMWQe8UYB6ekmsQ45q0M/tJDsGaZmbC+l7n57UV8Hl5tHxO9uw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/normalize-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/normalize-path/-/normalize-path-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6eZs5Ls3WtCisHWp9S2GUy8dqkpGi4BVSz3GaqiE6ezub0512ESztXUwUB6C6IKbQkY2Pnb/mD4WYojCRwcwLA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/npm-run-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/npm-run-path/-/npm-run-path-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-S48WzZW777zhNIrn7gxOlISNAqi9ZC/uQFnRdbeIHhZhCA6UqpkOT8T1G7BvfdgP4Er8gF4sUbaS0i7QvIfCWw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/once\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/once/-/once-1.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lNaJgI+2Q5URQBkccEKHTQOPaXdUxnZZElQTZY0MFUAuaEqe1E+Nyvgdz/aIyNi6Z9MzO5dv1H8n58/GELp3+w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/onetime\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/onetime/-/onetime-5.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kbpaSSGJTWdAY5KPVeMOKXSrPtr8C8C7wodJbcsd51jRnmD+GZu8Y0VoU6Dm5Z4vWr0Ig/1NKuWRKf7j5aaYSg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/p-limit\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-limit/-/p-limit-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TYOanM3wGwNGsZN2cVTYPArw454xnXj5qmWF1bEoAc4+cU/ol7GVh7odevjp1FNHduHc3KZMcFduxU5Xc6uJRQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/p-locate\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-locate/-/p-locate-4.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R79ZZ/0wAxKGu3oYMlz8jy/kbhsNrS7SKZ7PxEHBgJ5+F2mtFW2fK2cOtBh1cHYkQsbzFV7I+EoRKe6Yt0oK7A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/p-locate/node_modules/p-limit\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-limit/-/p-limit-2.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-//88mFWSJx8lxCzwdAABTJL2MyWB12+eIY7MDL2SqLmAkeKU9qxRvWuSyTjm3FUmpBEMuFfckAIqEaVGUDxb6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/p-try\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-try/-/p-try-2.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R4nPAVTAU0B9D35/Gk3uJf/7XYbQcyohSKdvAxIRSNghFl4e71hVoGnBNQz9cWaXxO2I10KTC+3jMdvvoKw6dQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/parse-json\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/parse-json/-/parse-json-5.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ayCKvm/phCGxOkYRSCM82iDwct8/EonSEgCSxWxD7ve6jHggsFl4fZVQBPRNgQoKiuV/odhFrGzQXZwbifC8Rg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.0.0\",\n        \"error-ex\": \"^1.3.1\",\n        \"json-parse-even-better-errors\": \"^2.3.0\",\n        \"lines-and-columns\": \"^1.1.6\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/path-exists\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-exists/-/path-exists-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ak9Qy5Q7jYb2Wwcey5Fpvg2KoAc/ZIhLSLOSBmRmygPsGwkVVt0fZa0qrtMz+m6tJTAHfZQ8FnmB4MG4LWy7/w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/path-is-absolute\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-is-absolute/-/path-is-absolute-1.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-AVbw3UJ2e9bq64vSaS9Am0fje1Pa8pbGqTTsmXfaIiMpnr5DlDhfJOuLj9Sf95ZPVDAUerDfEk88MPmPe7UCQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/path-key\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-key/-/path-key-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ojmeN0qd+y0jszEtoY48r0Peq5dwMEkIlCOu6Q5f41lfkswXuKtYrhgoTpLnyIcHm24Uhqx+5Tqm2InSwLhE6Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/path-parse\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-parse/-/path-parse-1.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LDJzPVEEEPR+y48z93A0Ed0yXb8pAByGWo/k5YYdYgpY2/2EsOsksJrq7lOHxryrVOn1ejG6oAp8ahvOIQD8sw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/picocolors\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/picocolors/-/picocolors-1.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xceH2snhtb5M9liqDsmEw56le376mTZkEX/jEb/RxNFyegNul7eNslCXP9FDj/Lcu0X8KEyMceP2ntpaHrDEVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/picomatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/picomatch/-/picomatch-2.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JU3teHTNjmE2VCGFzuY8EXzCDVwEqB2a8fsIvwaStHhAWJEeVd1o1QD80CU6+ZdEXXSLbSsuLwJjkCBWqRQUVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pirates\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pirates/-/pirates-4.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TfySrs/5nm8fQJDcBDuUng3VOUKsd7S+zqvbOTiGXHfxX4wK31ard+hoNuvkicM/2YFzlpDgABOevKSsB4G/FA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pkg-dir\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pkg-dir/-/pkg-dir-4.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-HRDzbaKjC+AOWVXxAU/x54COGeIv9eb+6CkDSQoNTt4XyWoIJvuPsXizxu/Fr23EiekbtZwmh1IcIG/l/a10GQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pretty-format\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pretty-format/-/pretty-format-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Pdlw/oPxN+aXdmM9R00JVC9WVFoCLTKJvDVLgmJ+qAffBMxsV85l/Lu7sNx4zSzPyoL2euImuEwHhOXdEgNFZQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jest/schemas\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"react-is\": \"^18.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pretty-format/node_modules/ansi-styles\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-styles/-/ansi-styles-5.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Cxwpt2SfTzTtXcfOlzGEee8O+c+MmUgGrNiBcXnuWxuFJHe6a5Hz7qwhwe5OgaSYI0IJvkLqWX1ASG+cJOkEiA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/prompts\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.4.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/prompts/-/prompts-2.4.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NxNv/kLguCA7p3jE8oL2aEBsrJWgAakBpgmgK6lpPWV+WuOmY6r2/zbAVnP+T8bQlA0nzHXSJSJW0Hq7ylaD2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/pure-rand\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pure-rand/-/pure-rand-6.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bVWawvoZoBYpp6yIoQtQXHZjmz35RSVHnUOTefl8Vcjr8snTPY1wnpSPMWekcFwbxI6gtmT7rSYPFvz71ldiOA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"individual\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/dubzzz\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n          \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/fast-check\"\n        }\n      ]\n    },\n    \"node_modules/react-is\": {\n      \"version\": \"18.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/react-is/-/react-is-18.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/LLMVyas0ljjAtoYiPqYiL8VWXzUUdThrmU5+n20DZv+a+ClRoevUzw5JxU+Ieh5/c87ytoTBV9G1FiKfNJdmg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/require-directory\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/require-directory/-/require-directory-2.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fGxEI7+wsG9xrvdjsrlmL22OMTTiHRwAMroiEeMgq8gzoLC/PQr7RsRDSTLUg/bZAZtF+TVIkHc6/4RIKrui+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/resolve\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.22.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve/-/resolve-1.22.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NPRy+/ncIMeDlTAsuqwKIiferiawhefFJtkNSW0qZJEqMEb+qBt/77B/jGeeek+F0uOeN05CDa6HXbbIgtVX4w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"is-core-module\": \"^2.16.0\",\n        \"path-parse\": \"^1.0.7\",\n        \"supports-preserve-symlinks-flag\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/resolve-cwd\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve-cwd/-/resolve-cwd-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OrZaX2Mb+rJCpH/6CpSqt9xFVpN++x01XnN2ie9g6P5/3xelLAkXWVADpdz1IHD/KFfEXyE6V0U01OQ3UO2rEg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/resolve-from\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve-from/-/resolve-from-5.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qYg9KP24dD5qka9J47d0aVky0N+b4fTU89LN9iDnjB5waksiC49rvMB0PrUJQGoTmH50XPiqOvAjDfaijGxYZw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/resolve.exports\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve.exports/-/resolve.exports-2.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OcXjMsGdhL4XnbShKpAcSqPMzQoYkYyhbEaeSko47MjRP9NfEQMhZkXL1DoFlt9LWQn4YttrdnV6X2OiyzBi+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-6.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BR7VvDCVHO+q2xBEWskxS6DJE1qRnb7DxzUrogb71CWoSficBxYsiAGd+Kl0mmq/MprG9yArRkyrQxTO6XjMzA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"bin\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/shebang-command\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/shebang-command/-/shebang-command-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kHxr2zZpYtdmrN1qDjrrX/Z1rR1kG8Dx+gkpK1G4eXmvXswmcE1hTWBWYUzlraYw1/yZp6YuDY77YtvbN0dmDA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/shebang-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/shebang-regex/-/shebang-regex-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7++dFhtcx3353uBaq8DDR4NuxBetBzC7ZQOhmTQInHEd6bSrXdiEyzCvG07Z44UYdLShWUyXt5M/yhz8ekcb1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/signal-exit\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/signal-exit/-/signal-exit-3.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wnD2ZE+l+SPC/uoS0vXeE9L1+0wuaMqKlfz9AMUo38JsyLSBWSFcHR1Rri62LZc12vLr1gb3jl7iwQhgwpAbGQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/sisteransi\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/sisteransi/-/sisteransi-1.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bLGGlR1QxBcynn2d5YmDX4MGjlZvy2MRBDRNHLJ8VI6l6+9FUiyTFNJ0IveOSP0bcXgVDPRcfGqA0pjaqUpfVg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/slash\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/slash/-/slash-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-g9Q1haeby36OSStwb4ntCGGGaKsaVSjQ68fBxoQcutl5fS1vuY18H3wSt3jFyFtrkx+Kz0V1G85A4MyAdDMi2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.6.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/source-map/-/source-map-0.6.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UjgapumWlbMhkBgzT7Ykc5YXUT46F0iKu8SGXq0bcwP5dz/h0Plj6enJqjz1Zbq2l5WaqYnrVbwWOWMyF3F47g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/source-map-support\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.5.13\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/source-map-support/-/source-map-support-0.5.13.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-SHSKFHadjVA5oR4PPqhtAVdcBWwRYVd6g6cAXnIbRiIwc2EhPrTuKUBdSLvlEKyIP3GCf89fltvcZiP9MMFA1w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"buffer-from\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"source-map\": \"^0.6.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"node_modules/sprintf-js\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/sprintf-js/-/sprintf-js-1.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-D9cPgkvLlV3t3IzL0D0YLvGA9Ahk4PcvVwUbN0dSGr1aP0Nrt4AEnTUbuGvquEC0mA64Gqt1fzirlRs5ibXx8g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/stack-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/stack-utils/-/stack-utils-2.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XlkWvfIm6RmsWtNJx+uqtKLS8eqFbxUg0ZzLXqY0caEy9l7hruX8IpiDnjsLavoBgqCCR71TqWO8MaXYheJ3RQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/string-length\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/string-length/-/string-length-4.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+l6rNN5fYHNhZZy41RXsYptCjA2Igmq4EG7kZAYFQI1E1VTXarr6ZPXBg6eq7Y6eK4FEhY6AJlyuFIb/v/S0VQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"char-regex\": \"^1.0.2\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/string-width\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/string-width/-/string-width-4.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wKyQRQpjJ0sIp62ErSZdGsjMJWsap5oRNihHhu6G7JVO/9jIB6UyevL+tXuOqrng8j/cxKTWyWUwvSTriiZz/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"emoji-regex\": \"^8.0.0\",\n        \"is-fullwidth-code-point\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/strip-ansi\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-ansi/-/strip-ansi-6.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Y38VPSHcqkFrCpFnQ9vuSXmquuv5oXOKpGeT6aGrr3o3Gc9AlVa6JBfUSOCnbxGGZF+/0ooI7KrPuUSztUdU5A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/strip-bom\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-bom/-/strip-bom-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3xurFv5tEgii33Zi8Jtp55wEIILR9eh34FAW00PZf+JnSsTmV/ioewSgQl97JHvgjoRGwPShsWm+IdrxB35d0w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/strip-final-newline\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-final-newline/-/strip-final-newline-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BrpvfNAE3dcvq7ll3xVumzjKjZQ5tI1sEUIKr3Uoks0XUl45St3FlatVqef9prk4jRDzhW6WZg+3bk93y6pLjA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/strip-json-comments\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-json-comments/-/strip-json-comments-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6fPc+R4ihwqP6N/aIv2f1gMH8lOVtWQHoqC4yK6oSDVVocumAsfCqjkXnqiYMhmMwS/mEHLp7Vehlt3ql6lEig==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/supports-color\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-color/-/supports-color-7.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qpCAvRl9stuOHveKsn7HncJRvv501qIacKzQlO/+Lwxc9+0q2wLyv4Dfvt80/DPn2pqOBsJdDiogXGR9+OvwRw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag/-/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag-1.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ot0WnXS9fgdkgIcePe6RHNk1WA8+muPa6cSjeR3V8K27q9BB1rTE3R1p7Hv0z1ZyAc8s6Vvv8DIyWf681MAt0w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/test-exclude\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/test-exclude/-/test-exclude-6.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-cAGWPIyOHU6zlmg88jwm7VRyXnMN7iV68OGAbYDk/Mh/xC/pzVPlQtY6ngoIH/5/tciuhGfvESU8GrHrcxD56w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.4\",\n        \"minimatch\": \"^3.0.4\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/tmpl\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/tmpl/-/tmpl-1.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3f0uOEAQwIqGuWW2MVzYg8fV/QNnc/IpuJNG837rLuczAaLVHslWHZQj4IGiEl5Hs3kkbhwL9Ab7Hrsmuj+Smw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/to-regex-range\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/to-regex-range/-/to-regex-range-5.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-65P7iz6X5yEr1cwcgvQxbbIw7Uk3gOy5dIdtZ4rDveLqhrdJP+Li/Hx6tyK0NEb+2GCyneCMJiGqrADCSNk8sQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/type-detect\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/type-detect/-/type-detect-4.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0fr/mIH1dlO+x7TlcMy+bIDqKPsw/70tVyeHW787goQjhmqaZe10uwLujubK9q9Lg6Fiho1KUKDYz0Z7k7g5/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/type-fest\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.21.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/type-fest/-/type-fest-0.21.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-t0rzBq87m3fVcduHDUFhKmyyX+9eo6WQjZvf51Ea/M0Q7+T374Jp1aUiyUl0GKxp8M/OETVHSDvmkyPgvX+X2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/undici-types\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.21.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/undici-types/-/undici-types-6.21.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iwDZqg0QAGrg9Rav5H4n0M64c3mkR59cJ6wQp+7C4nI0gsmExaedaYLNO44eT4AtBBwjbTiGPMlt2Md0T9H9JQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/update-browserslist-db\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/update-browserslist-db/-/update-browserslist-db-1.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UxhIZQ+QInVdunkDAaiazvvT/+fXL5Osr0JZlJulepYu6Jd7qJtDZjlur0emRlT71EN3ScPoE7gvsuIKKNavKw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"funding\": [\n        {\n          \"type\": \"opencollective\",\n          \"url\": \"https://opencollective.com/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"tidelift\",\n          \"url\": \"https://tidelift.com/funding/github/npm/browserslist\"\n        },\n        {\n          \"type\": \"github\",\n          \"url\": \"https://github.com/sponsors/ai\"\n        }\n      ],\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"peerDependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/v8-to-istanbul\": {\n      \"version\": \"9.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/v8-to-istanbul/-/v8-to-istanbul-9.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kiGUalWN+rgBJ/1OHZsBtU4rXZOfj/7rKQxULKlIzwzQSvMJUUNgPwJEEh7gU6xEVxC0ahoOBvN2YI8GH6FNgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.12\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.1\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/walker\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/walker/-/walker-1.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ts/8E8l5b7kY0vlWLewOkDXMmPdLcVV4GmOQLyxuSswIJsweeFZtAsMF7k1Nszz+TYBQrlYRmzOnr398y1JemQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/which\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/which/-/which-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BLI3Tl1TW3Pvl70l3yq3Y64i+awpwXqsGBYWkkqMtnbXgrMD+yj7rhW0kuEDxzJaYXGjEW5ogapKNMEKNMjibA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": ,\n      \"bin\": ,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/wrap-ansi\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/wrap-ansi/-/wrap-ansi-7.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-YVGIj2kamLSTxw6NsZjoBxfSwsn0ycdesmc4p+Q21c5zPuZ1pl+NfxVdxPtdHvmNVOQ6XSYG4AUtyt/Fi7D16Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/wrappy\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/wrappy/-/wrappy-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-l4Sp/DRseor9wL6EvV2+TuQn63dMkPjZ/sp9XkghTEbV9KlPS1xUsZ3u7/IQO4wxtcFB4bgpQPRcR3QCvezPcQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/write-file-atomic\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/write-file-atomic/-/write-file-atomic-4.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7KxauUdBmSdWnmpaGFg+ppNjKF8uNLry8LyzjauQDOVONfFLNKrKvQOxZ/VuTIcS/gge/YNahf5RIIQWTSarlg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"imurmurhash\": \"^0.1.4\",\n        \"signal-exit\": \"^3.0.7\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/y18n\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/y18n/-/y18n-5.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0pfFzegeDWJHJIAmTLRP2DwHjdF5s7jo9tuztdQxAhINCdvS+3nGINqPd00AphqJR/0LhANUS6/+7SCb98YOfA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/yallist\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yallist/-/yallist-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-a4UGQaWPH59mOXUYnAG2ewncQS4i4F43Tv3JoAM+s2VDAmS9NsK8GpDMLrCHPksFT7h3K6TOoUNn2pb7RoXx4g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node_modules/yargs\": {\n      \"version\": \"17.7.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yargs/-/yargs-17.7.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7dSzzRQ++CKnNI/krKnYRV7JKKPUXMEh61soaHKg9mrWEhzFWhFnxPxGl+69cD1Ou63C13NUPCnmIcrvqCuM6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"cliui\": \"^8.0.1\",\n        \"escalade\": \"^3.1.1\",\n        \"get-caller-file\": \"^2.0.5\",\n        \"require-directory\": \"^2.1.1\",\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.2.3\",\n        \"y18n\": \"^5.0.5\",\n        \"yargs-parser\": \"^21.1.1\"\n      },\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/yargs-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"21.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yargs-parser/-/yargs-parser-21.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tVpsJW7DdjecAiFpbIB1e3qxIQsE6NoPc5/eTdrbbIC4h0LVsWhnoa3g+m2HclBIujHzsxZ4VJVA+GUuc2/LBw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": \n    },\n    \"node_modules/yocto-queue\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yocto-queue/-/yocto-queue-0.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-rVksvsnNCdJ/ohGc6xgPwyN8eheCxsiLM8mxuE/t/mOVqJewPuO1miLpTHQiRgTKCLexL4MeAFVagts7HmNZ2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"engines\": ,\n      \"funding\": \n    }\n  },\n  \"dependencies\": {\n    \"@ampproject/remapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@ampproject/remapping/-/remapping-2.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-30iZtAPgz+LTIYoeivqYo853f02jBYSd5uGnGpkFV0M3xOt9aN73erkgYAmZU43x4VfqcnLxW9Kpg3R5LC4YYw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": \"^0.3.5\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.24\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/code-frame\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/code-frame/-/code-frame-7.26.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RJlIHRueQgwWitWgF8OdFYGZX328Ax5BCemNGlqHfplnRT9ESi8JkFlvaVYbS+UubVY6dpv87Fs2u5M29iNFVQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"js-tokens\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"picocolors\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/compat-data\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/compat-data/-/compat-data-7.26.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-oH5UPLMWR3L2wEFLnFJ1TZXqHufiTKAiLfqw5zkhS4dKXLJ10yVztfil/twG8EDTA4F/tvVNw9nOl4ZMslB8rQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/core\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/core/-/core-7.26.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-vMqyb7XCDMPvJFFOaT9kxtiRh42GwlZEg1/uIgtZshS5a/8OaduUfCi7kynKgc3Tw/6Uo2D+db9qBttghhmxwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@ampproject/remapping\": \"^2.2.0\",\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/helper-compilation-targets\": \"^7.26.5\",\n        \"@babel/helper-module-transforms\": \"^7.26.0\",\n        \"@babel/helpers\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.26.9\",\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.26.10\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"debug\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"gensync\": \"^1.0.0-beta.2\",\n        \"json5\": \"^2.2.3\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/generator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/generator/-/generator-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-VybsKvpiN1gU1sdMZIp7FcqphVVKEwcuj02x73uvcHE0PTihx1nlBcowYWhDwjpoAXRv43+gDzyggGnn1XZhVw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": \"^0.3.5\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.25\",\n        \"jsesc\": \"^3.0.2\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-compilation-targets\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-compilation-targets/-/helper-compilation-targets-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LVk7fbXml0H2xH34dFzKQ7TDZ2G4/rVTOrq9V+icbbadjbVxxeFeDsNHv2SrZeWoA+6ZiTyWYWtScEIW07EAcA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/compat-data\": \"^7.26.8\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-option\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"browserslist\": \"^4.24.0\",\n        \"lru-cache\": \"^5.1.1\",\n        \"semver\": \"^6.3.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-module-imports\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-module-imports/-/helper-module-imports-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tnUA4RsrmflIM6W6RFTLFSXITtl0wKjgpnLgXyowocVPrbYrLUXSBXDgTs8BlbmIzIdlBySRQjINYs2BAkiLtw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-module-transforms\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-module-transforms/-/helper-module-transforms-7.26.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xO+xu6B5K2czEnQye6BHA7DolFFmS3LB7stHZFaOLb1pAwO1HWLS8fXA+eh0A2yIvltPVmx3eNNDBJA2SLHXFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-module-imports\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/traverse\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-plugin-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-plugin-utils/-/helper-plugin-utils-7.26.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RS+jZcRdZdRFzMyr+wcsaqOmld1/EqTghfaBGQQd/WnRdzdlvSZ//kF7U8VQTxf1ynZ4cjUcYgjVGx13ewNPMg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-string-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-string-parser/-/helper-string-parser-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-4A/SCr/2KLd5jrtOMFzaKjVtAei3+2r/NChoBNoZ3EyP/+GlhoaEGoWOZUmFmoITP7zOJyHIMm+DYRd8o3PvHA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-validator-identifier/-/helper-validator-identifier-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Ed61U6XJc3CVRfkERJWDz4dJwKe7iLmmJsbOGu9wSloNSFttHV0I8g6UAgb7qnK5ly5bGLPd4oXZlxCdANBOWQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/helper-validator-option\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helper-validator-option/-/helper-validator-option-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-e/zv1co8pp55dNdEcCynfj9X7nyUKUXoUEwfXqaZt0omVOmDe9oOTdKStH4GmAw6zxMFs50ZayuMfHDKlO7Tfw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@babel/helpers\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/helpers/-/helpers-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-U5eyP/CTFPuNE3qk+WZMxFkp/4zUzdceQlfzf7DdGdhp+Fezd7HD+i8Y24ZuTMKX3wQBld449jijbGq6OdGNQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/parser/-/parser-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iaepho73/2Pz7w2eMS0Q5f83+0RKI7i4xmiYeBmDzfRVbQtTOG7Ts0S4HzJVsTMGI9keU8rNfuZr8DKfSt7Yyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators/-/plugin-syntax-async-generators-7.8.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tycmZxkGfZaxhMRbXlPXuVFpdWlXpir2W4AMhSJgRKzk/eDlIXOhb2LHWoLpDF7TEHylV5zNhykX6KAgHJmTNw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint/-/plugin-syntax-bigint-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wnTnFlG+YxQm3vDxpGE57Pj0srRU4sHE/mDkt1qv2YJJSeUAec2ma4WLUnUPeKjyrfntVwe/N6dCXpU+zL3Npg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.12.13\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties/-/plugin-syntax-class-properties-7.12.13.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fm4idjKla0YahUNgFNLCB0qySdsoPiZP3iQE3rky0mBUtMZ23yDJ9SJdg6dXTSDnulOVqiF3Hgr9nbXvXTQZYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block/-/plugin-syntax-class-static-block-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-b+YyPmr6ldyNnM6sqYeMWE+bgJcJpO6yS4QD7ymxgH34GBPNDM/THBh8iunyvKIZztiwLH4CJZ0RxTk9emgpjw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.26.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes/-/plugin-syntax-import-attributes-7.26.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-e2dttdsJ1ZTpi3B9UYGLw41hifAubg19AtCu/2I/F1QNVclOBr1dYpTdmdyZ84Xiz43BS/tCUkMAZNLv12Pi+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta/-/plugin-syntax-import-meta-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Yqfm+XDx0+Prh3VSeEQCPU81yC+JWZ2pDPFSS4ZdpfZhp4MkFMaDC1UqseovEKwSUpnIL7+vK+Clp7bfh0iD7g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings/-/plugin-syntax-json-strings-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lY6kdGpWHvjoe2vk4WrAapEuBR69EMxZl+RoGRhrFGNYVK8mOPAW8VfbT/ZgrFbXlDNiiaxQnAtgVCZ6jv30EA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx/-/plugin-syntax-jsx-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ld6oezHQMZsZfp6pWtbjaNDF2tiiCYYDqQszHt5VV437lewP9aSi2Of99CK0D0XB21k7FLgnLcmQKyKzynfeAA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators/-/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-d8waShlpFDinQ5MtvGU9xDAOzKH47+FFoney2baFIoMr952hKOLp1HR7VszoZvOsV/4+RRszNY7D17ba0te0ig==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator/-/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-aSff4zPII1u2QD7y+F8oDsz19ew4IGEJg9SVW+bqwpwtfFleiQDMdzA/R+UlWDzfnHFCxxleFT0PMIrR36XLNQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.10.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator/-/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator-7.10.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9H6YdfkcK/uOnY/K7/aA2xpzaAgkQn37yzWUMRK7OaPOqOpGS1+n0H5hxT9AUw9EsSjPW8SVyMJwYRtWs3X3ug==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread/-/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XoqMijGZb9y3y2XskN+P1wUGiVwWZ5JmoDRwx5+3GmEplNyVM2s2Dg8ILFQm8rWM48orGy5YpI5Bl8U1y7ydlA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding/-/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6VPD0Pc1lpTqw0aKoeRTMiB+kWhAoT24PA+ksWSBrFtl5SIRVpZlwN3NNPQjehA2E/91FV3RjLWoVTglWcSV3Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.8.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining/-/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining-7.8.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KoK9ErH1MBlCPxV0VANkXW2/dw4vlbGDrFgz8bmUsBGYkFRcbRwMh6cIJubdPrkxRwuGdtCk0v/wPTKbQgBjkg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object/-/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0wVnp9dxJ72ZUJDV27ZfbSj6iHLoytYZmh3rFcxNnvsJF3ktkzLDZPy/mA17HGsaQT3/DQsWYX1f1QGWkCoVUg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.14.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await/-/plugin-syntax-top-level-await-7.14.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hx++upLv5U1rgYfwe1xBQUhRmU41NEvpUvrp8jkrSCdvGSnM5/qdRMtylJ6PG5OFkBaHkbTAKTnd3/YyESRHFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.25.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript/-/plugin-syntax-typescript-7.25.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hjMgRy5hb8uJJjUcdWunWVcoi9bGpJp8p5Ol1229PoN6aytsLwNMgmdftO23wnCLMfVmTwZDWMPNq/D1SY60JQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@babel/template\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/template/-/template-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2ncevenBqXI6qRMukPlXwHKHchC7RyMuu4xv5JBXRfOGVcTy1mXCD12qrp7Jsoxll1EV3+9sE4GugBVRjT2jFA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/traverse\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/traverse/-/traverse-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-19lYZFzYVQkkHkl4Cy4WrAVcqBkgvV2YM2TU3xG6DIwO7O3ecbDPfW3yM3bjAGcqcQHi+CCtjMR3dIEHxsd6bA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.26.2\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.27.0\",\n        \"debug\": \"^4.3.1\",\n        \"globals\": \"^11.1.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@babel/types\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@babel/types/-/types-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-H45s8fVLYjbhFH62dIJ3WtmJ6RSPt/3DRO0ZcT2SUiYiQyz3BLVb9ADEnLl91m74aQPS3AzzeajZHYOalWe3bg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-string-parser\": \"^7.25.9\",\n        \"@babel/helper-validator-identifier\": \"^7.25.9\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@bcoe/v8-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@bcoe/v8-coverage/-/v8-coverage-0.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0hYQ8SB4Db5zvZB4axdMHGwEaQjkZzFjQiN9LVYvIFB2nSUHW9tYpxWriPrWDASIxiaXax83REcLxuSdnGPZtw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config/-/load-nyc-config-1.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-VjeHSlIzpv/NyD3N0YuHfXOPDIixcA1q2ZV98wsMqcYlPmv2n3Yb2lYP9XMElnaFVXg5A7YLTeLu6V84uQDjmQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"camelcase\": \"^5.3.1\",\n        \"find-up\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"get-package-type\": \"^0.1.0\",\n        \"js-yaml\": \"^3.13.1\",\n        \"resolve-from\": \"^5.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@istanbuljs/schema\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@istanbuljs/schema/-/schema-0.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ZXRY4jNvVgSVQ8DL3LTcakaAtXwTVUxE81hslsyD2AtoXW/wVob10HkOJ1X/pAlcI7D+2YoZKg5do8G/w6RYgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@jest/console\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/console/-/console-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-5Ni4CU7XHQi32IJ398EEP4RrB8eV09sXP2ROqD4bksHrnTree52PsxvX8tpL8LvTZ3pFzXyPbNQReSN41CAhOg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/core\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/core/-/core-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-n7aeXWKMnGtDA48y8TLWJPJmLmmZ642Ceo78cYWEpiD7FzDgmNDV/GCVRorPABdXLJZ/9wzzgZAlHjXjxDHGsg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/reporters\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"ansi-escapes\": \"^4.2.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-changed-files\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-resolve-dependencies\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runner\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-watcher\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/environment\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/environment/-/environment-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-aQIfHDq33ExsN4jP1NWGXhxgQ/wixs60gDiKO+XVMd8Mn0NWPWgc34ZQDTb2jKaUWQ7MuwoitXAsN2XVXNMpAw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/expect\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/expect/-/expect-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-8uMeAMycttpva3P1lBHB8VciS9V0XAr3GymPpipdyQXbBcuhkLQOSe8E/p92RyAdToS6ZD1tFkX+CkhoECE0dQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/expect-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/expect-utils/-/expect-utils-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GlsNBWiFQFCVi9QVSx7f5AgMeLxe9YCCs5PuP2O2LdjDAA8Jh9eX7lA1Jq/xdXw3Wb3hyvlFNfZIfcRetSzYcA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@jest/fake-timers\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/fake-timers/-/fake-timers-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-q4DH1Ha4TTFPdxLsqDXK1d3+ioSL7yL5oCMJZgDYm6i+6CygW5E5xVr/D1HdsGxjt1ZWSfUAs9OxSB/BNelWrQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@sinonjs/fake-timers\": \"^10.0.2\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/globals\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/globals/-/globals-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-mpiz3dutLbkW2MNFubUGUEVLkTGiqW6yLVTA+JbP6fI6J5iL9Y0Nlg8k95pcF8ctKwCS7WVxteBs29hhfAotzQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/reporters\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/reporters/-/reporters-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DApq0KJbJOEzAFYjHADNNxAE3KbhxQB1y5Kplb5Waqw6zVbuWatSnMjE5gs8FUgEPmNsnZA3NCWl9NG0ia04Pg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@bcoe/v8-coverage\": \"^0.2.3\",\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-report\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-source-maps\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-reports\": \"^3.1.3\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"string-length\": \"^4.0.1\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"v8-to-istanbul\": \"^9.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/schemas\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/schemas/-/schemas-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-mo5j5X+jIZmJQveBKeS/clAueipV7KgiX1vMgCxam1RNYiqE1w62n0/tJJnHtjW8ZHcQco5gY85jA3mi0L+nSA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@jest/source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/source-map/-/source-map-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MHjT95QuipcPrpLM+8JMSzFx6eHp5Bm+4XeFDJlwsvVBjmKNiIAvasGK2fxz2WbGRlnvqehFbh07MMa7n3YJnw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"callsites\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/test-result\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/test-result/-/test-result-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Fdx+tv6x1zlkJPcWXmMDAG2HBnaR9XPSd5aDWQVsfrZmLVT3lU1cwyxLgRmXR9yrq4NBoEm9BMsfgFzTQAbJYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/test-sequencer\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/test-sequencer/-/test-sequencer-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GQwJ5WZVrKnOJuiYiAF52UNUJXgTZx1NHjFSEB0qEMmSZKAkdMoIzw/Cj6x6NF4AvV23AUqDpFzQkN/eYCYTxw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/transform\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/transform/-/transform-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ok/BTPFzFKVMwO5eOHRrvnBVHdRy9IrsrW1GpMaQ9MCnilNLXQKmAX8s1YXDFaai9xJpac2ySzV0YeRRECr2Vw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.18\",\n        \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": \"^6.1.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"fast-json-stable-stringify\": \"^2.1.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pirates\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"write-file-atomic\": \"^4.0.2\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jest/types\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jest/types/-/types-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-u3UPsIilWKOM3F9CXtrG8LEJmNxwoCQC/XVj4IKYXvvpx7QIi/Kg1LI5uDmDpKlac62NUtX7eLjRh+jVZcLOzw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/schemas\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-reports\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/yargs\": \"^17.0.8\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/gen-mapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.3.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/gen-mapping/-/gen-mapping-0.3.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-imAbBGkb+ebQyxKgzv5Hu2nmROxoDOXHh80evxdoXNOrvAnVx7zimzc1Oo5h9RlfV4vPXaE2iM5pOFbvOCClWA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/set-array\": \"^1.2.1\",\n        \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": \"^1.4.10\",\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.24\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/resolve-uri\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/resolve-uri/-/resolve-uri-3.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bRISgCIjP20/tbWSPWMEi54QVPRZExkuD9lJL+UIxUKtwVJA8wW1Trb1jMs1RFXo1CBTNZ/5hpC9QvmKWdopKw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/set-array\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/set-array/-/set-array-1.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R8gLRTZeyp03ymzP/6Lil/28tGeGEzhx1q2k703KGWRAI1VdvPIXdG70VJc2pAMw3NA6JKL5hhFu1sJX0Mnn/A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec/-/sourcemap-codec-1.5.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gv3ZRaISU3fjPAgNsriBRqGWQL6quFx04YMPW/zD8XMLsU32mhCCbfbO6KZFLjvYpCZ8zyDEgqsgf+PwPaM7GQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.3.25\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@jridgewell/trace-mapping/-/trace-mapping-0.3.25.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-vNk6aEwybGtawWmy/PzwnGDOjCkLWSD2wqvjGGAgOAwCGWySYXfYoxt00IJkTF+8Lb57DwOb3Aa0o9CApepiYQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/resolve-uri\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"@jridgewell/sourcemap-codec\": \"^1.4.14\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@sinclair/typebox\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.27.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinclair/typebox/-/typebox-0.27.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+Fj43pSMwJs4KRrH/938Uf+uAELIgVBmQzg/q1YG10djyfA3TnrU8N8XzqCh/okZdszqBQTZf96idMfE5lnwTA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@sinonjs/commons\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinonjs/commons/-/commons-3.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-K3mCHKQ9sVh8o1C9cxkwxaOmXoAMlDxC1mYyHrjqOWEcBjYr76t96zL2zlj5dUGZ3HSw240X1qgH3Mjf1yJWpQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@sinonjs/fake-timers\": {\n      \"version\": \"10.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@sinonjs/fake-timers/-/fake-timers-10.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-V4BG07kuYSUkTCSBHG8G8TNhM+F19jXFWnQtzj+we8DrkpSBCee9Z3Ms8yiGer/dlmhe35/Xdgyo3/0rQKg7YA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/babel__core\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.20.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__core/-/babel__core-7.20.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qoQprZvz5wQFJwMDqeseRXWv3rqMvhgpbXFfVyWhbx9X47POIA6i/+dXefEmZKoAgOaTdaIgNSMqMIU61yRyzA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.20.7\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.20.7\",\n        \"@types/babel__generator\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/babel__template\": \"*\",\n        \"@types/babel__traverse\": \"*\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@types/babel__generator\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.27.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__generator/-/babel__generator-7.27.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ufFd2Xi92OAVPYsy+P4n7/U7e68fex0+Ee8gSG9KX7eo084CWiQ4sdxktvdl0bOPupXtVJPY19zk6EwWqUQ8lg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/babel__template\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.4.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__template/-/babel__template-7.4.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-h/NUaSyG5EyxBIp8YRxo4RMe2/qQgvyowRwVMzhYhBCONbW8PUsg4lkFMrhgZhUe5z3L3MiLDuvyJ/CaPa2A8A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.1.0\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"@types/babel__traverse\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.20.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/babel__traverse/-/babel__traverse-7.20.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-dkO5fhS7+/oos4ciWxyEyjWe48zmG6wbCheo/G2ZnHx4fs3EU6YC6UM8rk56gAjNJ9P3MTH2jo5jb92/K6wbng==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/graceful-fs\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.9\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/graceful-fs/-/graceful-fs-4.1.9.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-olP3sd1qOEe5dXTSaFvQG+02VdRXcdytWLAZsAq1PecU8uqQAhkrnbli7DagjtXKW/Bl7YJbUsa8MPcuc8LHEQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-lib-coverage/-/istanbul-lib-coverage-2.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2QF/t/auWm0lsy8XtKVPG19v3sSOQlJe/YHZgfjb/KBBHOGSV+J2q/S671rcq9uTBrLAXmZpqJiaQbMT+zNU1w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@types/istanbul-lib-report\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-lib-report/-/istanbul-lib-report-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NQn7AHQnk/RSLOxrBbGyJM/aVQ+pjj5HCgasFxc0K/KhoATfQ/47AyUl15I2yBUpihjmas+a+VJBOqecrFH+uA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/istanbul-reports\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/istanbul-reports/-/istanbul-reports-3.0.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pk2B1NWalF9toCRu6gjBzR69syFjP4Od8WRAX+0mmf9lAjCRicLOWc+ZrxZHx/0XRjotgkF9t6iaMJ+aXcOdZQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/node\": {\n      \"version\": \"22.14.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/node/-/node-22.14.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-u0HuPQwe/dHrItgHHpmw3N2fYCR6x4ivMNbPHRkBVP4CvN+kiRrKHWk3i8tXiO/joPwXLMYvF9TTF0eqgHIuOw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/stack-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/stack-utils/-/stack-utils-2.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9aEbYZ3TbYMznPdcdr3SmIrLXwC/AKZXQeCf9Pgao5CKb8CyHuEX5jzWPTkvregvhRJHcpRO6BFoGW9ycaOkYw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"@types/yargs\": {\n      \"version\": \"17.0.33\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/yargs/-/yargs-17.0.33.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WpxBCKWPLr4xSsHgz511rFJAM+wS28w2zEO1QDNY5zM/S8ok70NNfztH0xwhqKyaK0OHCbN98LDAZuy1ctxDkA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"@types/yargs-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"21.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/@types/yargs-parser/-/yargs-parser-21.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-I4q9QU9MQv4oEOz4tAHJtNz1cwuLxn2F3xcc2iV5WdqLPpUnj30aUuxt1mAxYTG+oe8CZMV/+6rU4S4gRDzqtQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"ansi-escapes\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-escapes/-/ansi-escapes-4.3.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gKXj5ALrKWQLsYG9jlTRmR/xKluxHV+Z9QEwNIgCfM1/uwPMCuzVVnh5mwTd+OuBZcwSIMbqssNWRm1lE51QaQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"ansi-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-regex/-/ansi-regex-5.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-quJQXlTSUGL2LH9SUXo8VwsY4soanhgo6LNSm84E1LBcE8s3O0wpdiRzyR9z/ZZJMlMWv37qOOb9pdJlMUEKFQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"ansi-styles\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-styles/-/ansi-styles-4.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zbB9rCJAT1rbjiVDb2hqKFHNYLxgtk8NURxZ3IZwD3F6NtxbXZQCnnSi1Lkx+IDohdPlFp222wVALIheZJQSEg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"anymatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/anymatch/-/anymatch-3.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KMReFUr0B4t+D+OBkjR3KYqvocp2XaSzO55UcB6mgQMd3KbcE+mWTyvVV7D/zsdEbNnV6acZUutkiHQXvTr1Rw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"normalize-path\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"picomatch\": \"^2.0.4\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"argparse\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/argparse/-/argparse-1.0.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-o5Roy6tNG4SL/FOkCAN6RzjiakZS25RLYFrcMttJqbdd8BWrnA+fGz57iN5Pb06pvBGvl5gQ0B48dJlslXvoTg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"babel-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-jest/-/babel-jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BrvGY3xZSwEcCzKvKsCi2GgHqDqsYkOP4/by5xCgIwGXQxIEh+8ew3gmrE1y7XRR6LHZIj6yLYnUi/mm2KXKBg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@types/babel__core\": \"^7.1.14\",\n        \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": \"^6.1.1\",\n        \"babel-preset-jest\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"babel-plugin-istanbul\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-plugin-istanbul/-/babel-plugin-istanbul-6.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Y1IQok9821cC9onCx5otgFfRm7Lm+I+wwxOx738M/WLPZ9Q42m4IG5W0FNX8WLL2gYMZo3JkuXIH2DOpWM+qwA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/helper-plugin-utils\": \"^7.0.0\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/load-nyc-config\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": \"^5.0.4\",\n        \"test-exclude\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": {\n          \"version\": \"5.2.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-instrument/-/istanbul-lib-instrument-5.2.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-pzqtp31nLv/XFOzXGuvhCb8qhjmTVo5vjVk19XE4CRlSWz0KoeJ3bw9XsA7nOp9YBf4qHjwBxkDzKcME/J29Yg==\",\n          \"dev\": true,\n          \"requires\": {\n            \"@babel/core\": \"^7.12.3\",\n            \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.14.7\",\n            \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n            \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.2.0\",\n            \"semver\": \"^6.3.0\"\n          }\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"babel-plugin-jest-hoist\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-plugin-jest-hoist/-/babel-plugin-jest-hoist-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ESAc/RJvGTFEzRwOTT4+lNDk/GNHMkKbNzsvT0qKRfDyyYTskxB5rnU2njIDYVxXCBHHEI1c0YwHob3WaYujOg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/template\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@types/babel__core\": \"^7.1.14\",\n        \"@types/babel__traverse\": \"^7.0.6\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-preset-current-node-syntax/-/babel-preset-current-node-syntax-1.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ldYss8SbBlWva1bs28q78Ju5Zq1F+8BrqBZZ0VFhLBvhh6lCpC2o3gDJi/5DRLs9FgYZCnmPYIVFU4lRXCkyUw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-async-generators\": \"^7.8.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-bigint\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-properties\": \"^7.12.13\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-class-static-block\": \"^7.14.5\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-attributes\": \"^7.24.7\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-import-meta\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-json-strings\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-logical-assignment-operators\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-nullish-coalescing-operator\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-numeric-separator\": \"^7.10.4\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-object-rest-spread\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-catch-binding\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-optional-chaining\": \"^7.8.3\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-private-property-in-object\": \"^7.14.5\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-top-level-await\": \"^7.14.5\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"babel-preset-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/babel-preset-jest/-/babel-preset-jest-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0B3bhxR6snWXJZtR/RliHTDPRgn1sNHOR0yVtq/IiQFyuOVjFS+wuio/R4gSNkyYmKmJB4wGZv2NZanmKmTnNA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"babel-plugin-jest-hoist\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"balanced-match\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/balanced-match/-/balanced-match-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3oSeUO0TMV67hN1AmbXsK4yaqU7tjiHlbxRDZOpH0KW9+CeX4bRAaX0Anxt0tx2MrpRpWwQaPwIlISEJhYU5Pw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"brace-expansion\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.11\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/brace-expansion/-/brace-expansion-1.1.11.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iCuPHDFgrHX7H2vEI/5xpz07zSHB00TpugqhmYtVmMO6518mCuRMoOYFldEBl0g187ufozdaHgWKcYFb61qGiA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"balanced-match\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"concat-map\": \"0.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"braces\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/braces/-/braces-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-yQbXgO/OSZVD2IsiLlro+7Hf6Q18EJrKSEsdoMzKePKXct3gvD8oLcOQdIzGupr5Fj+EDe8gO/lxc1BzfMpxvA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"browserslist\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.24.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/browserslist/-/browserslist-4.24.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KDi1Ny1gSePi1vm0q4oxSF8b4DR44GF4BbmS2YdhPLOEqd8pDviZOGH/GsmRwoWJ2+5Lr085X7naowMwKHDG1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"caniuse-lite\": \"^1.0.30001688\",\n        \"electron-to-chromium\": \"^1.5.73\",\n        \"node-releases\": \"^2.0.19\",\n        \"update-browserslist-db\": \"^1.1.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"bser\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/bser/-/bser-2.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gQxTNE/GAfIIrmHLUE3oJyp5FO6HRBfhjnw4/wMmA63ZGDJnWBmgY/lyQBpnDUkGmAhbSe39tx2d/iTOAfglwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"buffer-from\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/buffer-from/-/buffer-from-1.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-E+XQCRwSbaaiChtv6k6Dwgc+bx+Bs6vuKJHHl5kox/BaKbhiXzqQOwK4cO22yElGp2OCmjwVhT3HmxgyPGnJfQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"callsites\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/callsites/-/callsites-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-P8BjAsXvZS+VIDUI11hHCQEv74YT67YUi5JJFNWIqL235sBmjX4+qx9Muvls5ivyNENctx46xQLQ3aTuE7ssaQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"camelcase\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/camelcase/-/camelcase-5.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-L28STB170nwWS63UjtlEOE3dldQApaJXZkOI1uMFfzf3rRuPegHaHesyee+YxQ+W6SvRDQV6UrdOdRiR153wJg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"caniuse-lite\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.30001715\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/caniuse-lite/-/caniuse-lite-1.0.30001715.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7ptkFGMm2OAOgvZpwgA4yjQ5SQbrNVGdRjzH0pBdy1Fasvcr+KAeECmbCAECzTuDuoX0FCY8KzUxjf9+9kfZEw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"chalk\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/chalk/-/chalk-4.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-oKnbhFyRIXpUuez8iBMmyEa4nbj4IOQyuhc/wy9kY7/WVPcwIO9VA668Pu8RkO7+0G76SLROeyw9CpQ061i4mA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^7.1.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"char-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/char-regex/-/char-regex-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kWWXztvZ5SBQV+eRgKFeh8q5sLuZY2+8WUIzlxWVTg+oGwY14qylx1KbKzHd8P6ZYkAg0xyIDU9JMHhyJMZ1jw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"ci-info\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.9.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ci-info/-/ci-info-3.9.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NIxF55hv4nSqQswkAeiOi1r83xy8JldOFDTWiug55KBu9Jnblncd2U6ViHmYgHf01TPZS77NJBhBMKdWj9HQMQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"cjs-module-lexer\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cjs-module-lexer/-/cjs-module-lexer-1.4.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-9z8TZaGM1pfswYeXrUpzPrkx8UnWYdhJclsiYMm6x/w5+nN+8Tf/LnAgfLGQCm59qAOxU8WwHEq2vNwF6i4j+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"cliui\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cliui/-/cliui-8.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BSeNnyus75C4//NQ9gQt1/csTXyo/8Sb+afLAkzAptFuMsod9HFokGNudZpi/oQV73hnVK+sR+5PVRMd+Dr7YQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.2.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.1\",\n        \"wrap-ansi\": \"^7.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"co\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.6.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/co/-/co-4.6.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-QVb0dM5HvG+uaxitm8wONl7jltx8dqhfU33DcqtOZcLSVIKSDDLDi7+0LbAKiyI8hD9u42m2YxXSkMGWThaecQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"collect-v8-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/collect-v8-coverage/-/collect-v8-coverage-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lHl4d5/ONEbLlJvaJNtsF/Lz+WvB07u2ycqTYbdrq7UypDXailES4valYb2eWiJFxZlVmpGekfqoxQhzyFdT4Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"color-convert\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/color-convert/-/color-convert-2.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RRECPsj7iu/xb5oKYcsFHSppFNnsj/52OVTRKb4zP5onXwVF3zVmmToNcOfGC+CRDpfK/U584fMg38ZHCaElKQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"color-name\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/color-name/-/color-name-1.1.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-dOy+3AuW3a2wNbZHIuMZpTcgjGuLU/uBL/ubcZF9OXbDo8ff4O8yVp5Bf0efS8uEoYo5q4Fx7dY9OgQGXgAsQA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"concat-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/concat-map/-/concat-map-0.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/Srv4dswyQNBfohGpz9o6Yb3Gz3SrUDqBH5rTuhGR7ahtlbYKnVxw2bCFMRljaA7EXHaXZ8wsHdodFvbkhKmqg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"convert-source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/convert-source-map/-/convert-source-map-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Kvp459HrV2FEJ1CAsi1Ku+MY3kasH19TFykTz2xWmMeq6bk2NU3XXvfJ+Q61m0xktWwt+1HSYf3JZsTms3aRJg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"create-jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/create-jest/-/create-jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Adz2bdH0Vq3F53KEMJOoftQFutWCukm6J24wbPWRO4k1kMY7gS7ds/uoJkNuV8wDCtWWnuwGcJwpWcih+zEW1Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"prompts\": \"^2.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"cross-spawn\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/cross-spawn/-/cross-spawn-7.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-uV2QOWP2nWzsy2aMp8aRibhi9dlzF5Hgh5SHaB9OiTGEyDTiJJyx0uy51QXdyWbtAHNua4XJzUKca3OzKUd3vA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"path-key\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"shebang-command\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"which\": \"^2.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"debug\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/debug/-/debug-4.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6WTZ/IxCY/T6BALoZHaE4ctp9xm+Z5kY/pzYaCHRFeyVhojxlrm+46y68HA6hr0TcwEssoxNiDEUJQjfPZ/RYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"dedent\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/dedent/-/dedent-1.5.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NHQtfOOW68WD8lgypbLA5oT+Bt0xXJhiYvoR6SmmNXZfpzOGXwdKWmcwG8N7PwVVWV3eF/68nmD9BaJSsTBhyQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {}\n    },\n    \"deepmerge\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/deepmerge/-/deepmerge-4.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3sUqbMEc77XqpdNO7FRyRog+eW3ph+GYCbj+rK+uYyRMuwsVy0rMiVtPn+QJlKFvWP/1PYpapqYn0Me2knFn+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"detect-newline\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/detect-newline/-/detect-newline-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TLz+x/vEXm/Y7P7wn1EJFNLxYpUD4TgMosxY6fAVJUnJMbupHBOncxyWUG9OpTaH9EBD7uFI5LfEgmMOc54DsA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"diff-sequences\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/diff-sequences/-/diff-sequences-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-EjePK1srD3P08o2j4f0ExnylqRs5B9tJjcp9t1krH2qRi8CCdsYfwe9JgSLurFBWwq4uOlipzfk5fHNvwFKr8Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"electron-to-chromium\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.5.140\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/electron-to-chromium/-/electron-to-chromium-1.5.140.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-o82Rj+ONp4Ip7Cl1r7lrqx/pXhbp/lh9DpKcMNscFJdh8ebyRofnc7Sh01B4jx403RI0oqTBvlZ7OBIZLMr2+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"emittery\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.13.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/emittery/-/emittery-0.13.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DeWwawk6r5yR9jFgnDKYt4sLS0LmHJJi3ZOnb5/JdbYwj3nW+FxQnHIjhBKz8YLC7oRNPVM9NQ47I3CVx34eqQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"emoji-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"8.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/emoji-regex/-/emoji-regex-8.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-MSjYzcWNOA0ewAHpz0MxpYFvwg6yjy1NG3xteoqz644VCo/RPgnr1/GGt+ic3iJTzQ8Eu3TdM14SawnVUmGE6A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"error-ex\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.3.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/error-ex/-/error-ex-1.3.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7dFHNmqeFSEt2ZBsCriorKnn3Z2pj+fd9kmI6QoWw4//DL+icEBfc0U7qJCisqrTsKTjw4fNFy2pW9OqStD84g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"escalade\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/escalade/-/escalade-3.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WUj2qlxaQtO4g6Pq5c29GTcWGDyd8itL8zTlipgECz3JesAiiOKotd8JU6otB3PACgG6xkJUyVhboMS+bje/jA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"escape-string-regexp\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/escape-string-regexp/-/escape-string-regexp-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UpzcLCXolUWcNu5HtVMHYdXJjArjsF9C0aNnquZYY4uW/Vu0miy5YoWvbV345HauVvcAUnpRuhMMcqTcGOY2+w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"esprima\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/esprima/-/esprima-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eGuFFw7Upda+g4p+QHvnW0RyTX/SVeJBDM/gCtMARO0cLuT2HcEKnTPvhjV6aGeqrCB/sbNop0Kszm0jsaWU4A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"execa\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/execa/-/execa-5.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-8uSpZZocAZRBAPIEINJj3Lo9HyGitllczc27Eh5YYojjMFMn8yHMDMaUHE2Jqfq05D/wucwI4JGURyXt1vchyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"cross-spawn\": \"^7.0.3\",\n        \"get-stream\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"human-signals\": \"^2.1.0\",\n        \"is-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"merge-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"npm-run-path\": \"^4.0.1\",\n        \"onetime\": \"^5.1.2\",\n        \"signal-exit\": \"^3.0.3\",\n        \"strip-final-newline\": \"^2.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"exit\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/exit/-/exit-0.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Zk/eNKV2zbjpKzrsQ+n1G6poVbErQxJ0LBOJXaKZ1EViLzH+hrLu9cdXI4zw9dBQJslwBEpbQ2P1oS7nDxs6jQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"expect\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/expect/-/expect-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2Zks0hf1VLFYI1kbh0I5jP3KHHyCHpkfyHBzsSXRFgl/Bg9mWYfMW8oD+PdMPlEwy5HNsR9JutYy6pMeOh61nw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/expect-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"fast-json-stable-stringify\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fast-json-stable-stringify/-/fast-json-stable-stringify-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lhd/wF+Lk98HZoTCtlVraHtfh5XYijIjalXck7saUtuanSDyLMxnHhSXEDJqHxD7msR8D0uCmqlkwjCV8xvwHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"fb-watchman\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fb-watchman/-/fb-watchman-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-p5161BqbuCaSnB8jIbzQHOlpgsPmK5rJVDfDKO91Axs5NC1uu3HRQm6wt9cd9/+GtQQIO53JdGXXoyDpTAsgYA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"fill-range\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fill-range/-/fill-range-7.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-YsGpe3WHLK8ZYi4tWDg2Jy3ebRz2rXowDxnld4bkQB00cc/1Zw9AWnC0i9ztDJitivtQvaI9KaLyKrc+hBW0yg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"find-up\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/find-up/-/find-up-4.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-PpOwAdQ/YlXQ2vj8a3h8IipDuYRi3wceVQQGYWxNINccq40Anw7BlsEXCMbt1Zt+OLA6Fq9suIpIWD0OsnISlw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"locate-path\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"path-exists\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"fs.realpath\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fs.realpath/-/fs.realpath-1.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OO0pH2lK6a0hZnAdau5ItzHPI6pUlvI7jMVnxUQRtw4owF2wk8lOSabtGDCTP4Ggrg2MbGnWO9X8K1t4+fGMDw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"fsevents\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/fsevents/-/fsevents-2.3.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-5xoDfX+fL7faATnagmWPpbFtwh/R77WmMMqqHGS65C3vvB0YHrgF+B1YmZ3441tMj5n63k0212XNoJwzlhffQw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"optional\": true\n    },\n    \"function-bind\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/function-bind/-/function-bind-1.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7XHNxH7qX9xG5mIwxkhumTox/MIRNcOgDrxWsMt2pAr23WHp6MrRlN7FBSFpCpr+oVO0F744iUgR82nJMfG2SA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"gensync\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0-beta.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/gensync/-/gensync-1.0.0-beta.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3hN7NaskYvMDLQY55gnW3NQ+mesEAepTqlg+VEbj7zzqEMBVNhzcGYYeqFo/TlYz6eQiFcp1HcsCZO+nGgS8zg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"get-caller-file\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-caller-file/-/get-caller-file-2.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DyFP3BM/3YHTQOCUL/w0OZHR0lpKeGrxotcHWcqNEdnltqFwXVfhEBQ94eIo34AfQpo0rGki4cyIiftY06h2Fg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"get-package-type\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-package-type/-/get-package-type-0.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-pjzuKtY64GYfWizNAJ0fr9VqttZkNiK2iS430LtIHzjBEr6bX8Am2zm4sW4Ro5wjWW5cAlRL1qAMTcXbjNAO2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"get-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/get-stream/-/get-stream-6.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ts6Wi+2j3jQjqi70w5AlN8DFnkSwC+MqmxEzdEALB2qXZYV3X/b1CTfgPLGJNMeAWxdPfU8FO1ms3NUfaHCPYg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"glob\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/glob/-/glob-7.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-nFR0zLpU2YCaRxwoCJvL6UvCH2JFyFVIvwTLsIf21AuHlMskA1hhTdk+LlYJtOlYt9v6dvszD2BGRqBL+iQK9Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"fs.realpath\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"inflight\": \"^1.0.4\",\n        \"inherits\": \"2\",\n        \"minimatch\": \"^3.1.1\",\n        \"once\": \"^1.3.0\",\n        \"path-is-absolute\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"globals\": {\n      \"version\": \"11.12.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/globals/-/globals-11.12.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-WOBp/EEGUiIsJSp7wcv/y6MO+lV9UoncWqxuFfm8eBwzWNgyfBd6Gz+IeKQ9jCmyhoH99g15M3T+QaVHFjizVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"graceful-fs\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.11\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/graceful-fs/-/graceful-fs-4.2.11.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RbJ5/jmFcNNCcDV5o9eTnBLJ/HszWV0P73bc+Ff4nS/rJj+YaS6IGyiOL0VoBYX+l1Wrl3k63h/KrH+nhJ0XvQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"has-flag\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/has-flag/-/has-flag-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-EykJT/Q1KjTWctppgIAgfSO0tKVuZUjhgMr17kqTumMl6Afv3EISleU7qZUzoXDFTAHTDC4NOoG/ZxU3EvlMPQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"hasown\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/hasown/-/hasown-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0hJU9SCPvmMzIBdZFqNPXWa6dqh7WdH0cII9y+CyS8rG3nL48Bclra9HmKhVVUHyPWNH5Y7xDwAB7bfgSjkUMQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"html-escaper\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/html-escaper/-/html-escaper-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-H2iMtd0I4Mt5eYiapRdIDjp+XzelXQ0tFE4JS7YFwFevXXMmOp9myNrUvCg0D6ws8iqkRPBfKHgbwig1SmlLfg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"human-signals\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/human-signals/-/human-signals-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-B4FFZ6q/T2jhhksgkbEW3HBvWIfDW85snkQgawt07S7J5QXTk6BkNV+0yAeZrM5QpMAdYlocGoljn0sJ/WQkFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"import-local\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/import-local/-/import-local-3.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-2SPlun1JUPWoM6t3F0dw0FkCF/jWY8kttcY4f599GLTSjh2OCuuhdTkJQsEcZzBqbXZGKMK2OqW1oZsjtf/gQA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"imurmurhash\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/imurmurhash/-/imurmurhash-0.1.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JmXMZ6wuvDmLiHEml9ykzqO6lwFbof0GG4IkcGaENdCRDDmMVnny7s5HsIgHCbaq0w2MyPhDqkhTUgS2LU2PHA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"inflight\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/inflight/-/inflight-1.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-k92I/b08q4wvFscXCLvqfsHCrjrF7yiXsQuIVvVE7N82W3+aqpzuUdBbfhWcy/FZR3/4IgflMgKLOsvPDrGCJA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"inherits\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/inherits/-/inherits-2.0.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-k/vGaX4/Yla3WzyMCvTQOXYeIHvqOKtnqBduzTHpzpQZzAskKMhZ2K+EnBiSM9zGSoIFeMpXKxa4dYeZIQqewQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-arrayish\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.2.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-arrayish/-/is-arrayish-0.2.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zz06S8t0ozoDXMG+ube26zeCTNXcKIPJZJi8hBrF4idCLms4CG9QtK7qBl1boi5ODzFpjswb5JPmHCbMpjaYzg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-core-module\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.16.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-core-module/-/is-core-module-2.16.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UfoeMA6fIJ8wTYFEUjelnaGI67v6+N7qXJEvQuIGa99l4xsCruSYOVSQ0uPANn4dAzm8lkYPaKLrrijLq7x23w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"is-fullwidth-code-point\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-fullwidth-code-point/-/is-fullwidth-code-point-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zymm5+u+sCsSWyD9qNaejV3DFvhCKclKdizYaJUuHA83RLjb7nSuGnddCHGv0hk+KY7BMAlsWeK4Ueg6EV6XQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-generator-fn\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-generator-fn/-/is-generator-fn-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-cTIB4yPYL/Grw0EaSzASzg6bBy9gqCofvWN8okThAYIxKJZC+udlRAmGbM0XLeniEJSs8uEgHPGuHSe1XsOLSQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-number\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-number/-/is-number-7.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-41Cifkg6e8TylSpdtTpeLVMqvSBEVzTttHvERD741+pnZ8ANv0004MRL43QKPDlK9cGvNp6NZWZUBlbGXYxxng==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"is-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/is-stream/-/is-stream-2.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hFoiJiTl63nn+kstHGBtewWSKnQLpyb155KHheA1l39uvtO9nWIop1p3udqPcUd/xbF1VLMO4n7OI6p7RbngDg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"isexe\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/isexe/-/isexe-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RHxMLp9lnKHGHRng9QFhRCMbYAcVpn69smSGcq3f36xjgVVWThj4qqLbTLlq7Ssj8B+fIQ1EuCEGI2lKsyQeIw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.2.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-coverage/-/istanbul-lib-coverage-3.2.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-O8dpsF+r0WV/8MNRKfnmrtCWhuKjxrq2w+jpzBL5UZKTi2LeVWnWOmWRxFlesJONmc+wLAGvKQZEOanko0LFTg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"istanbul-lib-instrument\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-instrument/-/istanbul-lib-instrument-6.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Vtgk7L/R2JHyyGW07spoFlB8/lpjiOLTjMdms6AFMraYt3BaJauod/NGrfnVG/y4Ix1JEuMRPDPEj2ua+zz1/Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.23.9\",\n        \"@babel/parser\": \"^7.23.9\",\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.3\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^7.5.4\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"semver\": {\n          \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"istanbul-lib-report\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-report/-/istanbul-lib-report-3.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GCfE1mtsHGOELCU8e/Z7YWzpmybrx/+dSTfLrvY8qRmaY6zXTKWn6WQIjaAFw069icm6GVMNkgu0NzI4iPZUNw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"make-dir\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^7.1.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"istanbul-lib-source-maps\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-lib-source-maps/-/istanbul-lib-source-maps-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-n3s8EwkdFIJCG3BPKBYvskgXGoy88ARzvegkitk60NxRdwltLOTaH7CUiMRXvwYorl0Q712iEjcWB+fK/MrWVw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"debug\": \"^4.1.1\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"source-map\": \"^0.6.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"istanbul-reports\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/istanbul-reports/-/istanbul-reports-3.1.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BewmUXImeuRk2YY0PVbxgKAysvhRPUQE0h5QRM++nVWyubKGV0l8qQ5op8+B2DOmwSe63Jivj0BjkPQVf8fP5g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"html-escaper\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"istanbul-lib-report\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest/-/jest-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NIy3oAFp9shda19hy4HK0HRTWKtPJmGdnvywu01nOqNC2vZg+Z+fvJDxpMQA88eb2I9EcafcdjYgsDthnYTvGw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/core\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"import-local\": \"^3.0.2\",\n        \"jest-cli\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-changed-files\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-changed-files/-/jest-changed-files-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fEArFiwf1BpQ+4bXSprcDc3/x4HSzL4al2tozwVpDFpsxALjLYdyiIK4e5Vz66GQJIbXJ82+35PtysofptNX2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"execa\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-circus\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-circus/-/jest-circus-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3E1nCMgipcTkCocFwM90XXQab9bS+GMsjdpmPrlelaxwD93Ad8iVEjX/vvHPdLPnFf+L40u+5+iutRdA1N9myw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"co\": \"^4.6.0\",\n        \"dedent\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"is-generator-fn\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"jest-each\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"pure-rand\": \"^6.0.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"stack-utils\": \"^2.0.3\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-cli\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-cli/-/jest-cli-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OVVobw2IubN/GSYsxETi+gOe7Ka59EFMR/twOU3Jb2GnKKeMGJB5SGUUrEz3SFVmJASUdZUzy83sLNNQ2gZslg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/core\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"create-jest\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"exit\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"import-local\": \"^3.0.2\",\n        \"jest-config\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"yargs\": \"^17.3.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-config\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-config/-/jest-config-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-uXbpfeQ7R6TZBqI3/TxCU4q4ttk3u0PJeC+E0zbfSoSjq6bJ7buBPxzQPL0ifrkY4DNu4JUdk0ImlBUYi840eQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@jest/test-sequencer\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-jest\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"deepmerge\": \"^4.2.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-circus\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-environment-node\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runner\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"parse-json\": \"^5.2.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-json-comments\": \"^3.1.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-diff\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-diff/-/jest-diff-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LMIgiIrhigmPrs03JHpxUh2yISK3vLFPkAodPeo0+BuF7wA2FoQbkEg1u8gBYBThncu7e1oEDUfIXVuTqLRUjw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"diff-sequences\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-docblock\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-docblock/-/jest-docblock-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-q617Auw3A612guyaFgsbFeYpNP5t2aoUNLwBUbc/0kD1R4t9ixDbyFTHd1nok4epoVFpr7PmeWHrhvuV3XaJ4g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"jest-each\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-each/-/jest-each-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gns+Er14+ZrEoC5fhOfYCY1LOHHr0TI+rQUHZS8Ttw2l7gl+80eHc/gFf2Ktkw0+SIACDTeWvpFcv3B04VembQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-environment-node\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-environment-node/-/jest-environment-node-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-DOSwCRqXirTOyheM+4d5YZOrWcdu0LNZ87ewUoywbcb2XR4wKgqiG8vNeYwhjFMbEkfju7wx2GYH0P2gevGvFw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-get-type\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-get-type/-/jest-get-type-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-zrteXnqYxfQh7l5FHyL38jL39di8H8rHoecLH3JNxH3BwOrBsNeabdap5e0I23lD4HHI8W5VFBZqG4Eaq5LNcw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"jest-haste-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-haste-map/-/jest-haste-map-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fP8u2pyfqx0K1rGn1R9pyE0/KTn+G7PxktWidOBTqFPLYX0b9ksaMFkhK5vrS3DVun09pckLdlx90QthlW7AmA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/graceful-fs\": \"^4.1.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"anymatch\": \"^3.0.3\",\n        \"fb-watchman\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"fsevents\": \"^2.3.2\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"walker\": \"^1.0.8\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-leak-detector\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-leak-detector/-/jest-leak-detector-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kYA8IJcSYtST2BY9I+SMC32nDpBT3J2NvWJx8+JCuCdl/CR1I4EKUJROiP8XtCcxqgTTBGJNdbB1A8XRKbTetw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-matcher-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-matcher-utils/-/jest-matcher-utils-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-sBkD+Xi9DtcChsI3L3u0+N0opgPYnCRPtGcQYrgXmR+hmt/fYfWAL0xRXYU8eWOdfuLgBe0YCW3AFtnRLagq/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-diff\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-message-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-message-util/-/jest-message-util-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-GBEV4GRADeP+qtB2+6u61stea8mGcOT4mCtrYISZwfu9/ISHFJ/5zOMXYbpBE9RsS5+Gb63DW4FgmnKJ79Kf6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.12.13\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/stack-utils\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"micromatch\": \"^4.0.4\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"stack-utils\": \"^2.0.3\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-mock\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-mock/-/jest-mock-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ITOMZn+UkYS4ZFh83xYAOzWStloNzJFO2s8DWrE4lhtGD+AorgnbkiKERe4wQVBydIGPx059g6riW5Btp6Llnw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-pnp-resolver\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-pnp-resolver/-/jest-pnp-resolver-1.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+3NpwQEnRoIBtx4fyhblQDPgJI0H1IEIkX7ShLUjPGA7TtUTvI1oiKi3SR4oBR0hQhQR80l4WAe5RrXBwWMA8w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {}\n    },\n    \"jest-regex-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.6.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-regex-util/-/jest-regex-util-29.6.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KJJBsRCyyLNWCNBOvZyRDnAIfUiRJ8v+hOBQYGn8gDyF3UegwiP4gwRR3/SDa42g1YbVycTidUF3rKjyLFDWbg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"jest-resolve\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-resolve/-/jest-resolve-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-IOVhZSrg+UvVAshDSDtHyFCCBUl/Q3AAJv8iZ6ZjnZ74xzvwuzLXid9IIIPgTnY62SJjfuupMKZsZQRsCvxEgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-pnp-resolver\": \"^1.2.2\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-validate\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"resolve\": \"^1.20.0\",\n        \"resolve.exports\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-resolve-dependencies\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-resolve-dependencies/-/jest-resolve-dependencies-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-un0zD/6qxJ+S0et7WxeI3H5XSe9lTBBR7bOHCHXkKR6luG5mwDDlIzVQ0V5cZCuoTgEdcdwzTghYkTWfubi+nA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-runner\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-runner/-/jest-runner-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fsc4N6cPCAahybGBfTRcq5wFR6fpLznMg47sY5aDpsoejOcVYFb07AHuSnR0liMcPTgBsA3ZJL6kFOjPdoNipQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/console\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"emittery\": \"^0.13.1\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-docblock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-environment-node\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-leak-detector\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-runtime\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-watcher\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-worker\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"p-limit\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"source-map-support\": \"0.5.13\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-runtime\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-runtime/-/jest-runtime-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-gUnLjgwdGqW7B4LvOIkbKs9WGbn+QLqRQQ9juC6HndeDiezIwhDP+mhMwHWCEcfQ5RUXa6OPnFF8BJh5xegwwQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/environment\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/fake-timers\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/globals\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/source-map\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"cjs-module-lexer\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"collect-v8-coverage\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.3\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-haste-map\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-mock\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-regex-util\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-resolve\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-snapshot\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"slash\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-bom\": \"^4.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-snapshot\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-snapshot/-/jest-snapshot-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Rm0BMWtxBcioHr1/OX5YCP8Uov4riHvKPknOGs804Zg9JGZgmIBkbtlxJC/7Z4msKYVbIJtfU+tKb8xlYNfdkw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/core\": \"^7.11.6\",\n        \"@babel/generator\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-jsx\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/plugin-syntax-typescript\": \"^7.7.2\",\n        \"@babel/types\": \"^7.3.3\",\n        \"@jest/expect-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/transform\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"babel-preset-current-node-syntax\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"expect\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"jest-diff\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"jest-matcher-utils\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-message-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"natural-compare\": \"^1.4.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"semver\": \"^7.5.3\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"semver\": {\n          \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-util\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-util/-/jest-util-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-z6EbKajIpqGKU56y5KBUgy1dt1ihhQJgWzUlZHArA/+X2ad7Cb5iF+AK1EWVL/Bo7Rz9uurpqw6SiBCefUbCGA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"ci-info\": \"^3.2.0\",\n        \"graceful-fs\": \"^4.2.9\",\n        \"picomatch\": \"^2.2.3\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-validate\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-validate/-/jest-validate-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ZB7wHqaRGVw/9hST/OuFUReG7M8vKeq0/J2egIGLdvjHCmYqGARhzXmtgi+gVeZ5uXFF219aOc3Ls2yLg27tkw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"camelcase\": \"^6.2.0\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"jest-get-type\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"leven\": \"^3.1.0\",\n        \"pretty-format\": \"^29.7.0\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"camelcase\": {\n          \"version\": \"6.3.0\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/camelcase/-/camelcase-6.3.0.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-Gmy6FhYlCY7uOElZUSbxo2UCDH8owEk996gkbrpsgGtrJLM3J7jGxl9Ic7Qwwj4ivOE5AWZWRMecDdF7hqGjFA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-watcher\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-watcher/-/jest-watcher-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-49Fg7WXkU3Vl2h6LbLtMQ/HyB6rXSIX7SqvBLQmssRBGN9I0PNvPmAmCWSOY6SOvrjhI/F7/bGAv9RtnsPA03g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/test-result\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"@jest/types\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"ansi-escapes\": \"^4.2.1\",\n        \"chalk\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"emittery\": \"^0.13.1\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"string-length\": \"^4.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"jest-worker\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jest-worker/-/jest-worker-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eIz2msL/EzL9UFTFFx7jBTkeZfku0yUAyZZZmJ93H2TYEiroIx2PQjEXcwYtYl8zXCxb+PAmA2hLIt/6ZEkPHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@types/node\": \"*\",\n        \"jest-util\": \"^29.7.0\",\n        \"merge-stream\": \"^2.0.0\",\n        \"supports-color\": \"^8.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"supports-color\": {\n          \"version\": \"8.1.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-color/-/supports-color-8.1.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-MpUEN2OodtUzxvKQl72cUF7RQ5EiHsGvSsVG0ia9c5RbWGL2CI4C7EpPS8UTBIplnlzZiNuV56w+FuNxy3ty2Q==\",\n          \"dev\": true,\n          \"requires\": \n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"js-tokens\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/js-tokens/-/js-tokens-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-RdJUflcE3cUzKiMqQgsCu06FPu9UdIJO0beYbPhHN4k6apgJtifcoCtT9bcxOpYBtpD2kCM6Sbzg4CausW/PKQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"js-yaml\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.14.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/js-yaml/-/js-yaml-3.14.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-okMH7OXXJ7YrN9Ok3/SXrnu4iX9yOk+25nqX4imS2npuvTYDmo/QEZoqwZkYaIDk3jVvBOTOIEgEhaLOynBS9g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"jsesc\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/jsesc/-/jsesc-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/sM3dO2FOzXjKQhJuo0Q173wf2KOo8t4I8vHy6lF9poUp7bKT0/NHE8fPX23PwfhnykfqnC2xRxOnVw5XuGIaA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"json-parse-even-better-errors\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/json-parse-even-better-errors/-/json-parse-even-better-errors-2.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xyFwyhro/JEof6Ghe2iz2NcXoj2sloNsWr/XsERDK/oiPCfaNhl5ONfp+jQdAZRQQ0IJWNzH9zIZF7li91kh2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"json5\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/json5/-/json5-2.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XmOWe7eyHYH14cLdVPoyg+GOH3rYX++KpzrylJwSW98t3Nk+U8XOl8FWKOgwtzdb8lXGf6zYwDUzeHMWfxasyg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"kleur\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/kleur/-/kleur-3.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-eTIzlVOSUR+JxdDFepEYcBMtZ9Qqdef+rnzWdRZuMbOywu5tO2w2N7rqjoANZ5k9vywhL6Br1VRjUIgTQx4E8w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"leven\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/leven/-/leven-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qsda+H8jTaUaN/x5vzW2rzc+8Rw4TAQ/4KjB46IwK5VH+IlVeeeje/EoZRpiXvIqjFgK84QffqPztGI3VBLG1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"lines-and-columns\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.2.4\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/lines-and-columns/-/lines-and-columns-1.2.4.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7ylylesZQ/PV29jhEDl3Ufjo6ZX7gCqJr5F7PKrqc93v7fzSymt1BpwEU8nAUXs8qzzvqhbjhK5QZg6Mt/HkBg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"locate-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/locate-path/-/locate-path-5.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-t7hw9pI+WvuwNJXwk5zVHpyhIqzg2qTlklJOf0mVxGSbe3Fp2VieZcduNYjaLDoy6p9uGpQEGWG87WpMKlNq8g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"lru-cache\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/lru-cache/-/lru-cache-5.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-KpNARQA3Iwv+jTA0utUVVbrh+Jlrr1Fv0e56GGzAFOXN7dk/FviaDW8LHmK52DlcH4WP2n6gI8vN1aesBFgo9w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"make-dir\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/make-dir/-/make-dir-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-hXdUTZYIVOt1Ex//jAQi+wTZZpUpwBj/0QsOzqegb3rGMMeJiSEu5xLHnYfBrRV4RH2+OCSOO95Is/7x1WJ4bw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": ,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"semver\": {\n          \"version\": \"7.7.1\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-7.7.1.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-hlq8tAfn0m/61p4BVRcPzIGr6LKiMwo4VM6dGi6pt4qcRkmNzTcWq6eCEjEh+qXjkMDvPlOFFSGwQjoEa6gyMA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"makeerror\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.12\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/makeerror/-/makeerror-1.0.12.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JmqCvUhmt43madlpFzG4BQzG2Z3m6tvQDNKdClZnO3VbIudJYmxsT0FNJMeiB2+JTSlTQTSbU8QdesVmwJcmLg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"merge-stream\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/merge-stream/-/merge-stream-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-abv/qOcuPfk3URPfDzmZU1LKmuw8kT+0nIHvKrKgFrwifol/doWcdA4ZqsWQ8ENrFKkd67Mfpo/LovbIUsbt3w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"micromatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/micromatch/-/micromatch-4.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-PXwfBhYu0hBCPw8Dn0E+WDYb7af3dSLVWKi3HGv84IdF4TyFoC0ysxFd0Goxw7nSv4T/PzEJQxsYsEiFCKo2BA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"mimic-fn\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/mimic-fn/-/mimic-fn-2.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OqbOk5oEQeAZ8WXWydlu9HJjz9WVdEIvamMCcXmuqUYjTknH/sqsWvhQ3vgwKFRR1HpjvNBKQ37nbJgYzGqGcg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"minimatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/minimatch/-/minimatch-3.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-J7p63hRiAjw1NDEww1W7i37+ByIrOWO5XQQAzZ3VOcL0PNybwpfmV/N05zFAzwQ9USyEcX6t3UO+K5aqBQOIHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"ms\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ms/-/ms-2.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6FlzubTLZG3J2a/NVCAleEhjzq5oxgHyaCU9yYXvcLsvoVaHJq/s5xXI6/XXP6tz7R9xAOtHnSO/tXtF3WRTlA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"natural-compare\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/natural-compare/-/natural-compare-1.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OWND8ei3VtNC9h7V60qff3SVobHr996CTwgxubgyQYEpg290h9J0buyECNNJexkFm5sOajh5G116RYA1c8ZMSw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node-int64\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/node-int64/-/node-int64-0.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-O5lz91xSOeoXP6DulyHfllpq+Eg00MWitZIbtPfoSEvqIHdl5gfcY6hYzDWnj0qD5tz52PI08u9qUvSVeUBeHw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"node-releases\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.19\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/node-releases/-/node-releases-2.0.19.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xxOWJsBKtzAq7DY0J+DTzuz58K8e7sJbdgwkbMWQe8UYB6ekmsQ45q0M/tJDsGaZmbC+l7n57UV8Hl5tHxO9uw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"normalize-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/normalize-path/-/normalize-path-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6eZs5Ls3WtCisHWp9S2GUy8dqkpGi4BVSz3GaqiE6ezub0512ESztXUwUB6C6IKbQkY2Pnb/mD4WYojCRwcwLA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"npm-run-path\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/npm-run-path/-/npm-run-path-4.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-S48WzZW777zhNIrn7gxOlISNAqi9ZC/uQFnRdbeIHhZhCA6UqpkOT8T1G7BvfdgP4Er8gF4sUbaS0i7QvIfCWw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"once\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.4.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/once/-/once-1.4.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-lNaJgI+2Q5URQBkccEKHTQOPaXdUxnZZElQTZY0MFUAuaEqe1E+Nyvgdz/aIyNi6Z9MzO5dv1H8n58/GELp3+w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"onetime\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.1.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/onetime/-/onetime-5.1.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kbpaSSGJTWdAY5KPVeMOKXSrPtr8C8C7wodJbcsd51jRnmD+GZu8Y0VoU6Dm5Z4vWr0Ig/1NKuWRKf7j5aaYSg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"p-limit\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-limit/-/p-limit-3.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TYOanM3wGwNGsZN2cVTYPArw454xnXj5qmWF1bEoAc4+cU/ol7GVh7odevjp1FNHduHc3KZMcFduxU5Xc6uJRQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"p-locate\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-locate/-/p-locate-4.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R79ZZ/0wAxKGu3oYMlz8jy/kbhsNrS7SKZ7PxEHBgJ5+F2mtFW2fK2cOtBh1cHYkQsbzFV7I+EoRKe6Yt0oK7A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": ,\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"p-limit\": {\n          \"version\": \"2.3.0\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-limit/-/p-limit-2.3.0.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-//88mFWSJx8lxCzwdAABTJL2MyWB12+eIY7MDL2SqLmAkeKU9qxRvWuSyTjm3FUmpBEMuFfckAIqEaVGUDxb6w==\",\n          \"dev\": true,\n          \"requires\": \n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"p-try\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/p-try/-/p-try-2.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-R4nPAVTAU0B9D35/Gk3uJf/7XYbQcyohSKdvAxIRSNghFl4e71hVoGnBNQz9cWaXxO2I10KTC+3jMdvvoKw6dQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"parse-json\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/parse-json/-/parse-json-5.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ayCKvm/phCGxOkYRSCM82iDwct8/EonSEgCSxWxD7ve6jHggsFl4fZVQBPRNgQoKiuV/odhFrGzQXZwbifC8Rg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@babel/code-frame\": \"^7.0.0\",\n        \"error-ex\": \"^1.3.1\",\n        \"json-parse-even-better-errors\": \"^2.3.0\",\n        \"lines-and-columns\": \"^1.1.6\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"path-exists\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-exists/-/path-exists-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ak9Qy5Q7jYb2Wwcey5Fpvg2KoAc/ZIhLSLOSBmRmygPsGwkVVt0fZa0qrtMz+m6tJTAHfZQ8FnmB4MG4LWy7/w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"path-is-absolute\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-is-absolute/-/path-is-absolute-1.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-AVbw3UJ2e9bq64vSaS9Am0fje1Pa8pbGqTTsmXfaIiMpnr5DlDhfJOuLj9Sf95ZPVDAUerDfEk88MPmPe7UCQg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"path-key\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-key/-/path-key-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ojmeN0qd+y0jszEtoY48r0Peq5dwMEkIlCOu6Q5f41lfkswXuKtYrhgoTpLnyIcHm24Uhqx+5Tqm2InSwLhE6Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"path-parse\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/path-parse/-/path-parse-1.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-LDJzPVEEEPR+y48z93A0Ed0yXb8pAByGWo/k5YYdYgpY2/2EsOsksJrq7lOHxryrVOn1ejG6oAp8ahvOIQD8sw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"picocolors\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/picocolors/-/picocolors-1.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-xceH2snhtb5M9liqDsmEw56le376mTZkEX/jEb/RxNFyegNul7eNslCXP9FDj/Lcu0X8KEyMceP2ntpaHrDEVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"picomatch\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/picomatch/-/picomatch-2.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-JU3teHTNjmE2VCGFzuY8EXzCDVwEqB2a8fsIvwaStHhAWJEeVd1o1QD80CU6+ZdEXXSLbSsuLwJjkCBWqRQUVA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"pirates\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pirates/-/pirates-4.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-TfySrs/5nm8fQJDcBDuUng3VOUKsd7S+zqvbOTiGXHfxX4wK31ard+hoNuvkicM/2YFzlpDgABOevKSsB4G/FA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"pkg-dir\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pkg-dir/-/pkg-dir-4.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-HRDzbaKjC+AOWVXxAU/x54COGeIv9eb+6CkDSQoNTt4XyWoIJvuPsXizxu/Fr23EiekbtZwmh1IcIG/l/a10GQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"pretty-format\": {\n      \"version\": \"29.7.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pretty-format/-/pretty-format-29.7.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Pdlw/oPxN+aXdmM9R00JVC9WVFoCLTKJvDVLgmJ+qAffBMxsV85l/Lu7sNx4zSzPyoL2euImuEwHhOXdEgNFZQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jest/schemas\": \"^29.6.3\",\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^5.0.0\",\n        \"react-is\": \"^18.0.0\"\n      },\n      \"dependencies\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": {\n          \"version\": \"5.2.0\",\n          \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/ansi-styles/-/ansi-styles-5.2.0.tgz\",\n          \"integrity\": \"sha512-Cxwpt2SfTzTtXcfOlzGEee8O+c+MmUgGrNiBcXnuWxuFJHe6a5Hz7qwhwe5OgaSYI0IJvkLqWX1ASG+cJOkEiA==\",\n          \"dev\": true\n        }\n      }\n    },\n    \"prompts\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.4.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/prompts/-/prompts-2.4.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NxNv/kLguCA7p3jE8oL2aEBsrJWgAakBpgmgK6lpPWV+WuOmY6r2/zbAVnP+T8bQlA0nzHXSJSJW0Hq7ylaD2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"pure-rand\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/pure-rand/-/pure-rand-6.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bVWawvoZoBYpp6yIoQtQXHZjmz35RSVHnUOTefl8Vcjr8snTPY1wnpSPMWekcFwbxI6gtmT7rSYPFvz71ldiOA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"react-is\": {\n      \"version\": \"18.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/react-is/-/react-is-18.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-/LLMVyas0ljjAtoYiPqYiL8VWXzUUdThrmU5+n20DZv+a+ClRoevUzw5JxU+Ieh5/c87ytoTBV9G1FiKfNJdmg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"require-directory\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/require-directory/-/require-directory-2.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-fGxEI7+wsG9xrvdjsrlmL22OMTTiHRwAMroiEeMgq8gzoLC/PQr7RsRDSTLUg/bZAZtF+TVIkHc6/4RIKrui+Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"resolve\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.22.10\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve/-/resolve-1.22.10.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-NPRy+/ncIMeDlTAsuqwKIiferiawhefFJtkNSW0qZJEqMEb+qBt/77B/jGeeek+F0uOeN05CDa6HXbbIgtVX4w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"is-core-module\": \"^2.16.0\",\n        \"path-parse\": \"^1.0.7\",\n        \"supports-preserve-symlinks-flag\": \"^1.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"resolve-cwd\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve-cwd/-/resolve-cwd-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OrZaX2Mb+rJCpH/6CpSqt9xFVpN++x01XnN2ie9g6P5/3xelLAkXWVADpdz1IHD/KFfEXyE6V0U01OQ3UO2rEg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"resolve-from\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve-from/-/resolve-from-5.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qYg9KP24dD5qka9J47d0aVky0N+b4fTU89LN9iDnjB5waksiC49rvMB0PrUJQGoTmH50XPiqOvAjDfaijGxYZw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"resolve.exports\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/resolve.exports/-/resolve.exports-2.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-OcXjMsGdhL4XnbShKpAcSqPMzQoYkYyhbEaeSko47MjRP9NfEQMhZkXL1DoFlt9LWQn4YttrdnV6X2OiyzBi+A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"semver\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.3.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/semver/-/semver-6.3.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BR7VvDCVHO+q2xBEWskxS6DJE1qRnb7DxzUrogb71CWoSficBxYsiAGd+Kl0mmq/MprG9yArRkyrQxTO6XjMzA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"shebang-command\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/shebang-command/-/shebang-command-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kHxr2zZpYtdmrN1qDjrrX/Z1rR1kG8Dx+gkpK1G4eXmvXswmcE1hTWBWYUzlraYw1/yZp6YuDY77YtvbN0dmDA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"shebang-regex\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/shebang-regex/-/shebang-regex-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7++dFhtcx3353uBaq8DDR4NuxBetBzC7ZQOhmTQInHEd6bSrXdiEyzCvG07Z44UYdLShWUyXt5M/yhz8ekcb1A==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"signal-exit\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.7\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/signal-exit/-/signal-exit-3.0.7.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wnD2ZE+l+SPC/uoS0vXeE9L1+0wuaMqKlfz9AMUo38JsyLSBWSFcHR1Rri62LZc12vLr1gb3jl7iwQhgwpAbGQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"sisteransi\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/sisteransi/-/sisteransi-1.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-bLGGlR1QxBcynn2d5YmDX4MGjlZvy2MRBDRNHLJ8VI6l6+9FUiyTFNJ0IveOSP0bcXgVDPRcfGqA0pjaqUpfVg==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"slash\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/slash/-/slash-3.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-g9Q1haeby36OSStwb4ntCGGGaKsaVSjQ68fBxoQcutl5fS1vuY18H3wSt3jFyFtrkx+Kz0V1G85A4MyAdDMi2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"source-map\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.6.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/source-map/-/source-map-0.6.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UjgapumWlbMhkBgzT7Ykc5YXUT46F0iKu8SGXq0bcwP5dz/h0Plj6enJqjz1Zbq2l5WaqYnrVbwWOWMyF3F47g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"source-map-support\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.5.13\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/source-map-support/-/source-map-support-0.5.13.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-SHSKFHadjVA5oR4PPqhtAVdcBWwRYVd6g6cAXnIbRiIwc2EhPrTuKUBdSLvlEKyIP3GCf89fltvcZiP9MMFA1w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"buffer-from\": \"^1.0.0\",\n        \"source-map\": \"^0.6.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"sprintf-js\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/sprintf-js/-/sprintf-js-1.0.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-D9cPgkvLlV3t3IzL0D0YLvGA9Ahk4PcvVwUbN0dSGr1aP0Nrt4AEnTUbuGvquEC0mA64Gqt1fzirlRs5ibXx8g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"stack-utils\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.6\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/stack-utils/-/stack-utils-2.0.6.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-XlkWvfIm6RmsWtNJx+uqtKLS8eqFbxUg0ZzLXqY0caEy9l7hruX8IpiDnjsLavoBgqCCR71TqWO8MaXYheJ3RQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"string-length\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/string-length/-/string-length-4.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-+l6rNN5fYHNhZZy41RXsYptCjA2Igmq4EG7kZAYFQI1E1VTXarr6ZPXBg6eq7Y6eK4FEhY6AJlyuFIb/v/S0VQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"char-regex\": \"^1.0.2\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"string-width\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.2.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/string-width/-/string-width-4.2.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-wKyQRQpjJ0sIp62ErSZdGsjMJWsap5oRNihHhu6G7JVO/9jIB6UyevL+tXuOqrng8j/cxKTWyWUwvSTriiZz/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"emoji-regex\": \"^8.0.0\",\n        \"is-fullwidth-code-point\": \"^3.0.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"strip-ansi\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-ansi/-/strip-ansi-6.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-Y38VPSHcqkFrCpFnQ9vuSXmquuv5oXOKpGeT6aGrr3o3Gc9AlVa6JBfUSOCnbxGGZF+/0ooI7KrPuUSztUdU5A==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"strip-bom\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-bom/-/strip-bom-4.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3xurFv5tEgii33Zi8Jtp55wEIILR9eh34FAW00PZf+JnSsTmV/ioewSgQl97JHvgjoRGwPShsWm+IdrxB35d0w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"strip-final-newline\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-final-newline/-/strip-final-newline-2.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BrpvfNAE3dcvq7ll3xVumzjKjZQ5tI1sEUIKr3Uoks0XUl45St3FlatVqef9prk4jRDzhW6WZg+3bk93y6pLjA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"strip-json-comments\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/strip-json-comments/-/strip-json-comments-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-6fPc+R4ihwqP6N/aIv2f1gMH8lOVtWQHoqC4yK6oSDVVocumAsfCqjkXnqiYMhmMwS/mEHLp7Vehlt3ql6lEig==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"supports-color\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.2.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-color/-/supports-color-7.2.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-qpCAvRl9stuOHveKsn7HncJRvv501qIacKzQlO/+Lwxc9+0q2wLyv4Dfvt80/DPn2pqOBsJdDiogXGR9+OvwRw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"supports-preserve-symlinks-flag\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag/-/supports-preserve-symlinks-flag-1.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ot0WnXS9fgdkgIcePe6RHNk1WA8+muPa6cSjeR3V8K27q9BB1rTE3R1p7Hv0z1ZyAc8s6Vvv8DIyWf681MAt0w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"test-exclude\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/test-exclude/-/test-exclude-6.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-cAGWPIyOHU6zlmg88jwm7VRyXnMN7iV68OGAbYDk/Mh/xC/pzVPlQtY6ngoIH/5/tciuhGfvESU8GrHrcxD56w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@istanbuljs/schema\": \"^0.1.2\",\n        \"glob\": \"^7.1.4\",\n        \"minimatch\": \"^3.0.4\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"tmpl\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.5\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/tmpl/-/tmpl-1.0.5.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-3f0uOEAQwIqGuWW2MVzYg8fV/QNnc/IpuJNG837rLuczAaLVHslWHZQj4IGiEl5Hs3kkbhwL9Ab7Hrsmuj+Smw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"to-regex-range\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/to-regex-range/-/to-regex-range-5.0.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-65P7iz6X5yEr1cwcgvQxbbIw7Uk3gOy5dIdtZ4rDveLqhrdJP+Li/Hx6tyK0NEb+2GCyneCMJiGqrADCSNk8sQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"type-detect\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/type-detect/-/type-detect-4.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0fr/mIH1dlO+x7TlcMy+bIDqKPsw/70tVyeHW787goQjhmqaZe10uwLujubK9q9Lg6Fiho1KUKDYz0Z7k7g5/g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"type-fest\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.21.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/type-fest/-/type-fest-0.21.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-t0rzBq87m3fVcduHDUFhKmyyX+9eo6WQjZvf51Ea/M0Q7+T374Jp1aUiyUl0GKxp8M/OETVHSDvmkyPgvX+X2w==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"undici-types\": {\n      \"version\": \"6.21.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/undici-types/-/undici-types-6.21.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-iwDZqg0QAGrg9Rav5H4n0M64c3mkR59cJ6wQp+7C4nI0gsmExaedaYLNO44eT4AtBBwjbTiGPMlt2Md0T9H9JQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"update-browserslist-db\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.1.3\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/update-browserslist-db/-/update-browserslist-db-1.1.3.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-UxhIZQ+QInVdunkDAaiazvvT/+fXL5Osr0JZlJulepYu6Jd7qJtDZjlur0emRlT71EN3ScPoE7gvsuIKKNavKw==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"v8-to-istanbul\": {\n      \"version\": \"9.3.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/v8-to-istanbul/-/v8-to-istanbul-9.3.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-kiGUalWN+rgBJ/1OHZsBtU4rXZOfj/7rKQxULKlIzwzQSvMJUUNgPwJEEh7gU6xEVxC0ahoOBvN2YI8GH6FNgA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"@jridgewell/trace-mapping\": \"^0.3.12\",\n        \"@types/istanbul-lib-coverage\": \"^2.0.1\",\n        \"convert-source-map\": \"^2.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"walker\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/walker/-/walker-1.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-ts/8E8l5b7kY0vlWLewOkDXMmPdLcVV4GmOQLyxuSswIJsweeFZtAsMF7k1Nszz+TYBQrlYRmzOnr398y1JemQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"which\": {\n      \"version\": \"2.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/which/-/which-2.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-BLI3Tl1TW3Pvl70l3yq3Y64i+awpwXqsGBYWkkqMtnbXgrMD+yj7rhW0kuEDxzJaYXGjEW5ogapKNMEKNMjibA==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": \n    },\n    \"wrap-ansi\": {\n      \"version\": \"7.0.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/wrap-ansi/-/wrap-ansi-7.0.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-YVGIj2kamLSTxw6NsZjoBxfSwsn0ycdesmc4p+Q21c5zPuZ1pl+NfxVdxPtdHvmNVOQ6XSYG4AUtyt/Fi7D16Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"ansi-styles\": \"^4.0.0\",\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.1.0\",\n        \"strip-ansi\": \"^6.0.0\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"wrappy\": {\n      \"version\": \"1.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/wrappy/-/wrappy-1.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-l4Sp/DRseor9wL6EvV2+TuQn63dMkPjZ/sp9XkghTEbV9KlPS1xUsZ3u7/IQO4wxtcFB4bgpQPRcR3QCvezPcQ==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"write-file-atomic\": {\n      \"version\": \"4.0.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/write-file-atomic/-/write-file-atomic-4.0.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7KxauUdBmSdWnmpaGFg+ppNjKF8uNLry8LyzjauQDOVONfFLNKrKvQOxZ/VuTIcS/gge/YNahf5RIIQWTSarlg==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"imurmurhash\": \"^0.1.4\",\n        \"signal-exit\": \"^3.0.7\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"y18n\": {\n      \"version\": \"5.0.8\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/y18n/-/y18n-5.0.8.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-0pfFzegeDWJHJIAmTLRP2DwHjdF5s7jo9tuztdQxAhINCdvS+3nGINqPd00AphqJR/0LhANUS6/+7SCb98YOfA==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"yallist\": {\n      \"version\": \"3.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yallist/-/yallist-3.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-a4UGQaWPH59mOXUYnAG2ewncQS4i4F43Tv3JoAM+s2VDAmS9NsK8GpDMLrCHPksFT7h3K6TOoUNn2pb7RoXx4g==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"yargs\": {\n      \"version\": \"17.7.2\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yargs/-/yargs-17.7.2.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-7dSzzRQ++CKnNI/krKnYRV7JKKPUXMEh61soaHKg9mrWEhzFWhFnxPxGl+69cD1Ou63C13NUPCnmIcrvqCuM6w==\",\n      \"dev\": true,\n      \"requires\": {\n        \"cliui\": \"^8.0.1\",\n        \"escalade\": \"^3.1.1\",\n        \"get-caller-file\": \"^2.0.5\",\n        \"require-directory\": \"^2.1.1\",\n        \"string-width\": \"^4.2.3\",\n        \"y18n\": \"^5.0.5\",\n        \"yargs-parser\": \"^21.1.1\"\n      }\n    },\n    \"yargs-parser\": {\n      \"version\": \"21.1.1\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yargs-parser/-/yargs-parser-21.1.1.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-tVpsJW7DdjecAiFpbIB1e3qxIQsE6NoPc5/eTdrbbIC4h0LVsWhnoa3g+m2HclBIujHzsxZ4VJVA+GUuc2/LBw==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    },\n    \"yocto-queue\": {\n      \"version\": \"0.1.0\",\n      \"resolved\": \"https://registry.npmjs.org/yocto-queue/-/yocto-queue-0.1.0.tgz\",\n      \"integrity\": \"sha512-rVksvsnNCdJ/ohGc6xgPwyN8eheCxsiLM8mxuE/t/mOVqJewPuO1miLpTHQiRgTKCLexL4MeAFVagts7HmNZ2Q==\",\n      \"dev\": true\n    }\n  }\n}\n","file":"package-lock.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > str.length; i++)\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6 - 1) + 1;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6 - ) + 1;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6 - 0) + 1;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6 - 1) + 1;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * ( - 1) + 1;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (7 - 1) + 1;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random ;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > str.length; i++)\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i > str.length; i++){\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i  str.length; i++){\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i < str.length; i++){\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i < str.length; i++){\n  \nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i < str.length; i++){\n    \nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i < str.length; i++){\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i < str.length; i++){\nule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n  {\nule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n  {\nu  le.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n{\nu  le.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\nu  le.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)u  le.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)u    le.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)u      le.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)u     l le.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)u     le le.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)u     let le.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)u     let  le.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)u     le le.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)u     l le.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nfor(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)u      le.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n}\n\nexports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  \n}\n\nexports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  \n  \n}\n\nexports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n  \n}\n\nexports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  \n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n  \n}\n\nexports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  l\n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n  \n}\n\nexports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  le\n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n  \n}\n\nexports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let\n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n  \n}\n\nexports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let \n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n  \n}\n\nexports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let s\n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n  \n}\n\nexports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let st\n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n  \n}\n\nexports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let str\n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n  \n}\n\nexports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return name;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof5,\n    boo: typeoffalse,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof5,\n    boo: typeoffalse,\n    n : ntypeofull,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof5,\n    boo: typeoffalse,\n    n : typeofnull,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof5,\n    boo: typeoffalse,\n    n : typeofnull,\n    und : typeofundefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof5,\n    boo: typeoffalse,\n    n : typeofnull,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof5,\n    boo: typeoffalse,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\" this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeofNaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  \n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  r\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  re\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  reu\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  reut\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  reutn\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  reutnn\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  reutnrn\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  reutn\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  reun\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  ren\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  retn\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  retun\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  return\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  returnn\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  return n\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  return on\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  return obn\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  return objn\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  return obj n\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  return obj;n\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  return obj; n\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return name;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  return obj; \n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof [],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  return obj; \n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function screamName(name) {\n  /* take a name as input and return it in ALL CAPS with exclamation marks */\n   let nam = prompt (\"Name?\");\n   name = nam.toUpperCase + '!!!';\n   return name;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = screamName;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex6-name-screamer.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof [],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  return obj; \n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  return obj; \n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  return obj;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  return obj\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  return obj \n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  return\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  re\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  reutnr\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  \n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeof NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: typeofNaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof 5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof5,\n    boo: typeof false,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof5,\n    boo: typeoffalse,\n    n : typeof null,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof5,\n    boo: typeoffalse,\n    n : typeofnull,\n    und : typeof undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof5,\n    boo: typeoffalse,\n    n : typeofnull,\n    und : typeofundefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof5,\n    boo: typeoffalse,\n    n : typeofnull,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof5,\n    boo: typeoffalse,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\"this is a string\",\n    num: typeof5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: typeof\"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: \"this is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: typeof[],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n    \n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n  ibj\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof obj.an;\n  ibjj\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeof\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.ibj;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  eof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  reof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  reeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  reueof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  reuteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  reutneof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  reueof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  reeof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  reteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  retteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  rettteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  retutteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  returtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  returntteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  return{}tteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  return{tteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n   \n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  return{tteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n   \n  \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  return{tteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  return{tteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n   \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  return{tteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an;\n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  return{tteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an  } \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  return{tteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an    \n \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  return{tteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  return{}tteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  returntteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  retteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typ\n  reutntteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obj.an    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typeoftypeof obibjan    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  typen    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;\n  tn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n  typeof obj.und;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;\n  typeof obj.n;\n ibjtypeof obj.und;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;\n  typeof obj.boo;ibjtypeof obj.n;\n ibjtypeof obj.und;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;typeof obj.boo;ibjtypeof obj.n;\n ibjtypeof obj.und;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;\n  typeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtypeof obj.n;\n ibjtypeof obj.und;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;\n  typeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtypeof obj.n;\n ibjtypeof obj.und;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;typeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtypeof obj.n;\n ibjtypeof obj.und;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtypeof obj.n;\n ibjtypeof obj.und;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtypeof obj.n;\n ibjtypen    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtypeof obj.n;\n ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtypen    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr: [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig: is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n    boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: false,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undefined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n  }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let obj = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let  = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let r = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let re = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let reu = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let reut = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let reutn = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let reutnr = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let reut = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let reu = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let re = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let ret = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let retu = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let retur = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let return = ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let return =,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  let return ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  letreturn ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  lereturn ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  lreturn ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtteof obj.ibj;\n  typeof obj.arr;ibjtypeof obj.sig;ibjtypeof obj.num;ibjtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtypeof obj.boo;ibjtn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typtyn    \n    \n  \n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typ\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof is a string\",\n    num: 5,\n  typeof  boo: falsetypeof,\n    n : null,typeof\n    und : undeftypeofined,\n    an: NaN\n typeof }\n\n  typ\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"const showAllTypes = require('../../exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker');\n\ndescribe('Show All Types function', () => {\n  test('should return an object with all the types', () => {\n    const result = showAllTypes();\n    \n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('object');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('array');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('string');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('number');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('boolean');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('null');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('undefined');\n    expect(result).toHaveProperty('nan');\n    \n    expect(result.object).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.array).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.string).toBe('string');\n    expect(result.number).toBe('number');\n    expect(result.boolean).toBe('boolean');\n    expect(result.null).toBe('object');\n    expect(result.undefined).toBe('undefined');\n    expect(result.nan).toBe('number');\n  });\n});\n","file":"tests/easy/ex2.test.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function helloWorld() {\n  // write a function that prints \"Hello World!\" to the console\n  console.log(\"Hello World!\");\n}\n\nmodule.exports = helloWorld;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex1-hello-world.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    arr:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    arra:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array:typeof [],\n    sig:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    sig:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    si:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    s:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    st:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    str:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    stri:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strig:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strign:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    stri:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strig:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strign:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strigns:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strig:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    stri:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strin:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    string:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings:typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    num:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numb:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbe:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    number:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boo:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    bool:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boole:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolea:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean:typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    n :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    nu :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    nul :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null :typeof null,\n    und :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null :typeof null,\n    unde :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null :typeof null,\n    undef :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null :typeof null,\n    undefi :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null :typeof null,\n    undefin :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null :typeof null,\n    undefine :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null :typeof null,\n    undefinee :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null :typeof null,\n    undefinede :typeof undefined,\n    an:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null :typeof null,\n    undefinede :typeof undefined,\n    n:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null :typeof null,\n    undefinede :typeof undefined,\n   n:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null :typeof null,\n    undefinede :typeof undefined,\n   Nn:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null :typeof null,\n    undefinede :typeof undefined,\n   Nan:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null :typeof null,\n    undefinede :typeof undefined,\n   Nann:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null :typeof null,\n    undefinede :typeof undefined,\n   Nan n:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null :typeof null,\n    undefinede :typeof undefined,\n   an n:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null :typeof null,\n    undefinede :typeof undefined,\n   nan n:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null :typeof null,\n    undefinede :typeof undefined,\n   nann:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null :typeof null,\n    undefinede  :typeof undefined,\n   nan n:typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null :typeof null,\n    undefinede  :typeof undefined,\n   nan n :typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean :typeof false,\n    null : typeof null,\n    undefinede  :typeof undefined,\n   nan n :typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers:typeof 5,\n    boolean : typeof false,\n    null : typeof null,\n    undefinede  :typeof undefined,\n   nan n :typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings :typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers: typeof 5,\n    boolean : typeof false,\n    null : typeof null,\n    undefinede  :typeof undefined,\n   nan n :typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array :typeof [],\n    strings : typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers: typeof 5,\n    boolean : typeof false,\n    null : typeof null,\n    undefinede  :typeof undefined,\n   nan n :typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function showAllTypes() {\n  /* Create a function that outputs the typeof for:\n  objects, arrays, strings, numbers, booleans, null, undefined, and NaN It should return an object containing all these types */\n  return ,\n    array : typeof [],\n    strings : typeof \"this is a string\",\n    numbers: typeof 5,\n    boolean : typeof false,\n    null : typeof null,\n    undefinede  :typeof undefined,\n   nan n :typeof NaN\n  }\n\n}\n\nmodule.exports = showAllTypes;\n","file":"exercises/easy/ex2-type-checker.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random ;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random *;\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.rando\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.rand\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.ran\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.ra\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.r\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Mat\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Ma\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return M\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random *\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * 6\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * 6-\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * ()\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6-)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6-1)\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6-1) \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6-1) -\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6-1) +\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6-1) + \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6-1) + 1\n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function rollDice() {\n  /* return a random number between 1 and 6, simulating a dice roll */\n\n  return Math.random * (6-1) + 1 \n}\n\nmodule.exports = rollDice;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex4-dice-roller.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"{\n  \"name\": \"js-exercises\",\n  \"version\": \"1.0.0\",\n  \"description\": \"\",\n  \"main\": \"index.js\",\n  \"scripts\": {\n    \"test\": \"jest\",\n    \"test:watch\": \"jest --watch\",\n    \"test:easy\": \"jest tests/easy\",\n    \"test:medium\": \"jest tests/medium\",\n    \"test:hard\": \"jest tests/hard\"\n  },\n  \"keywords\": [\n    \"javascript\",\n    \"beginner\",\n    \"exercises\",\n    \"jest\"\n  ],\n  \"author\": \"\",\n  \"license\": \"ISC\",\n  \"devDependencies\": \n}\n","file":"package.json","language":"json"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let str\n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let st\n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let s\n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let \n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let r\n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let rt\n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let rts\n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let rts \n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let rts  \n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let rts   \n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let rts =  \n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let rts =   \n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let rts = \"\"  \n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let rts = \" \"  \n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}
{"text":"function reverseString(str) {\n  /* take a string as input and return it reversed Example: \"hello\" -> \"olleh\" */\n  let rts = \" \";  \n  for(i = 0; i < str.length; i++)\n}\n\n\nmodule.exports = reverseString;\n","file":"exercises/medium/ex9-reverse-string.js","language":"javascript"}